<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <atom:link href="https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2021/08/13/users/1/web_requests/22/MorningBrew.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
 <atom:icon>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2021/08/13/favicon.ico</atom:icon>
 

 <title>MorningBrew as a feed</title>
 <description>This is a feed of recent MorningBrew articles published by Huginn</description>
 <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2021/08/13</link>
 <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 14:03:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
 <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 14:03:20 -0700</pubDate>
 <ttl>60</ttl>
 <item>
  <title>Icebreakers with...Olympic Champion Surfer Carissa Moore</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6233%2Faround_the_games_-_olympi.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I’ve been on a surf trip here but it was over 10 years ago, and I have some of the best memories from surfing this spot. What’s the world of competitive surfing like? In Tokyo, Hawaii native Carissa Moore won the gold medal for the US in surfing’s first ever Olympics. But being conscious of and in tune with your own mental health, not being afraid to ask for help, and taking the time you need to feel through that space is super important. If you could compete at any surf spot around the world, what would it be? I hope it opens up surfing to a broader audience and can bring more people in, whether that's by inspiring someone to try surfing for the first time, or motivating them to choose their own path.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/13/icebreakers-witholympic-champion-surfer-carissa-moore</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>qanda</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/13/icebreakers-witholympic-champion-surfer-carissa-moore</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 14:01:19 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Reddit’s Valuation Upvoted to $10 Billion</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6212%2Freddit_meme.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Reddit recorded $100 million in ad revenue last quarter, which is a 192% annual increase but comes nowhere near Twitter’s $1.2 billion and Facebook’s $28.6 billion. Reddit’s “still planning on going public,” Huffman told the NYT...  Big picture: Despite its outsized cultural influence, Reddit’s still just a guppy swimming among sharks.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/12/reddits-valuation-upvoted-10-billion</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>social media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/12/reddits-valuation-upvoted-10-billion</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 15:11:51 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>‘Field of Dreams’ Game Brought Thousands of Visitors to a Small Iowa Town</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F4834%2Fbaseball.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Mayor Heavens said up until now, the field hasn’t been a significant economic driver for the town despite attracting 60,000+ visitors per year. The MLB initially scheduled the game for 2020, but it was pushed back because of the pandemic. residents hope Dyersville will become a regular stop on MLB’s schedule. Looking ahead...</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/12/field-dreams-game-brought-thousands-visitors-small-iowa-town</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/12/field-dreams-game-brought-thousands-visitors-small-iowa-town</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 15:06:47 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: Friday the 13th</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/J4UsQYXFr2QjxROhZ3/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To illustrate how impressive that is, Disney initially projected that the streaming service would hit between 60 million to 90 million subscribers...</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/12/key-performance-indicators-friday-13th</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/12/key-performance-indicators-friday-13th</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 15:01:45 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Census Data Shows White Population Dropped in the US for the First Time</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6210%2Fcensus_map.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  Cities are getting bigger while rural areas empty out: “Population growth was almost entirely in metropolitan areas,” the US Census Bureau’s Marc Perry said. Still, that growth has slowed down: The US population increased 7.4% from 2010 to 2020, the lowest growth rate since the 1930s.  The government dropped the first detailed results from the 2020 count yesterday, revealing a country that’s more racially diverse, urban, and Phoenician than the previous tally a decade ago. The non-Hispanic white population dropped for the first time on record (2.6%), falling to its lowest share of the total population on record.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/12/census-data-shows-white-population-dropped-us-first-time</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>demographics</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/12/census-data-shows-white-population-dropped-us-first-time</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 14:46:52 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>‘Jeopardy!’ Announces Two New Hosts: Mayim Bialik and Mike Richards</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6200%2Fthe_two_new_jeopardy_hosts.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;She’ll run the podium for specials like the new college championship tournament next year, while Richards, a former host of the reality show Beauty and the Geek, will step in for standard shows. Bialik is known for her role in The Big Bang Theory and will be the show’s first permanent female host.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/jeopardy-announces-two-new-hosts-mayim-bialik-mike-richards?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/jeopardy-announces-two-new-hosts-mayim-bialik-mike-richards?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 03:01:49 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: August 12</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6196%2Fa_general_view_shows_a_hu.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(New York Times) Read: How to sell a ton of merch as a minor league baseball team.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/key-performance-indicators-august-12?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/key-performance-indicators-august-12?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 03:01:49 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Hackers Steal More Than $600 Million in Crypto</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/11UjO5ezHZgMHC/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On Tuesday, hackers pulled off one of the biggest heists in crypto history, stealing more than $600 million from decentralized finance (DeFi) platform Poly Network. $256 million was returned as of yesterday afternoon. Government regulators and independent companies are racing to figure out how to fight back.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/hackers-steal-600-million-crypto?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/hackers-steal-600-million-crypto?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 03:01:48 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Samsung is Doubling Down on Foldable Phones With Newest Launch</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6197%2Fsamsung_foldable_phones.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;just about everything:The higher-end Z Fold3 costs $1,800 while the Z Flip3 costs $1,000, finally putting a foldable phone in a similar price bracket as an iPhone. Only 2 million foldable phones were shipped last year out of 1.3 billion total smartphones, per research firm International Data Corp.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/samsung-doubling-foldable-phones-newest-launch?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/samsung-doubling-foldable-phones-newest-launch?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 03:01:48 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Facing Higher Gas Prices, US Asks OPEC+ to Produce More Oil</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F4493%2Fvacation.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  The group recently agreed to gradually ramp up output over the next year, but the US thinks that’s not enough to meet greater demand for gas and keep prices from taking a bite out of Americans’ wallets. An official from Saudi Arabia, the world’s biggest oil producer, said it was rich that the US was asking for more oil when it's also on a high-profile mission to curb emissions. Run the numbers on gas prices:The national average yesterday was $3.185/gallon, according to AAA. Of course, gas isn’t the only thing that’s expensive these days.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/facing-higher-gas-prices-us-asks-opec-produce-oil?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>energy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/facing-higher-gas-prices-us-asks-opec-produce-oil?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 03:01:48 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Facing Higher Gas Prices, US Asks OPEC+ to Produce More Oil</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F4493%2Fvacation.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Run the numbers: As oil prices have recovered after cratering last March, gas has gotten considerably more expensive in the US. The group recently agreed to gradually ramp up output over the next year, but the US thinks that’s not enough of a boost to meet greater demand for gas and keep prices from taking a bite out of Americans’ wallets.   will OPEC speed up its production increases? The national average yesterday was $3.185/gallon, according to AAA.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/facing-higher-gas-prices-us-asks-opec-produce-oil</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>energy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/facing-higher-gas-prices-us-asks-opec-produce-oil</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 15:16:44 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>‘Jeopardy!’ Announces Two New Hosts: Mayim Bialik and Mike Richards</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/3o72wO1WX0A3o2DQDm/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;She’ll run the podium for specials like the new college championship tournament next year, while Richards, who is a former host of the reality show Beauty and the Geek, will step in as the regular host. Bialik is known for her role in The Big Bang Theory and will be the show’s first permanent female host.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/jeopardy-announces-two-new-hosts-mayim-bialik-mike-richards</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/jeopardy-announces-two-new-hosts-mayim-bialik-mike-richards</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 15:06:52 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Hackers Steal More Than $600 Million in Crypto</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/11UjO5ezHZgMHC/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On Tuesday, hackers pulled off one of the biggest heists in crypto history, stealing more than $600 million from decentralized finance (DeFi) platform Poly Network. $256 million was returned as of yesterday afternoon. Government regulators and independent companies are racing to figure out how to fight back.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/hackers-steal-600-million-crypto</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/hackers-steal-600-million-crypto</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 15:01:43 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: August 12</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6196%2Fa_general_view_shows_a_hu.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(New York Times) Read: How to sell a ton of merch as a minor league baseball team.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/key-performance-indicators-august-12</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/key-performance-indicators-august-12</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 14:56:53 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Samsung is Doubling Down on Foldable Phones With Newest Launch</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6197%2Fsamsung_foldable_phones.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Only a few tech companies even make foldable smartphones and roughly 2 million foldable phones were shipped last year compared to 1.3 billion total smartphones worldwide, per the research firm International Data Corp.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/samsung-doubling-foldable-phones-newest-launch</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/samsung-doubling-foldable-phones-newest-launch</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 14:56:53 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Return to the office? An argument for, and against</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6193%2Fbusinesswoman_using_mobile_phone_on_escalator_in_office.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After 17 months of working at home in sweatpants amid a pandemic, should we dig out our work clothes and return to the physical workplace? And so I think we'll be much more flexible going forward when people say, Hey, can I work from home on Friday? Before COVID-19 there was a small remote office in Los Angeles, a central office in New York, and a few individuals working elsewhere around the country. But I do know that I’m going to want to continue to have work-life balance, and that includes being able to leave the home and get to the office and activate that part of my brain and identity. I think we’ve all seen firms—particularly in the finance industry—coming out and saying, OK, everyone needs to be in the office two or three days a week.  But a number of people have been like, really? Morning Brew asked three business professionals—one startup CEO, one mid-level manager at a Fortune 500 financial services company, and one large-company executive who’s about to become a parent—to share their thoughts.  So, I want to set a baseline that you're supposed to come into the office five days a week. When I'm at the office, I know that all my teammates and I are working toward the same thing. You want to be back in an office full-time, even with the baby on the way? Even if it's a different project, there’s a common bond of people working toward this shared mission and vision. I think it has something to do with not working on the same objectives.  I also ruled out hybrid and remote working because there’s far less opportunity for real face-to-face connection. And I think that’s a mistake because in the end you’re going to find a line that satisfies no one.  Throughout COVID-19 we learned that for certain types of work, some people are actually more efficient by not being disrupted in the office. And while I don’t think there are zero benefits to working in the office, where I come down pretty hard is the idea of mandating office or location time based on some arbitrary quota. A company is not a place that fits everyone, at every stage of their life. It was always understood that working from home was done occasionally, when you had a doctor’s appointment or something along those lines. More than two-thirds of them thought workers needed to be in-office at least three days per week; just 5% believed company culture would remain intact with a fully remote workforce. The argument for flexibilityBy Lauren Friend, senior director of learning and enablement, EvolveI'm a people person. The kind where you think, I'm going to walk by their desk and say hello...  My team has been fully remote for a year and a half and we've been exactly as efficient or more efficient than we were when we were in the office.  Ultimately, my biggest piece of advice for other organizations is if you put your people first, the rest is going to figure itself out. There are some people who moved during COVID-19, and that's different. He was full-time, five days a week in the office. I like to get up and move, to be in one corner of the office for this meeting and then bounce to another area for the next one.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/return-office-argument</link>
  <author>Devin Tomb</author>
  <categories>work life</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/return-office-argument</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 14:01:57 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>WeWork Teams Up With Saks Fifth Avenue For In-Store Coworking</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6175%2Fsakswork.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Bottom line: Turning stores into offices is the latest development in an ongoing quest to repurpose empty retail space, and it’s way less bizarre than when Spirit Halloween takes over an abandoned Babies R Us.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/wework-teams-saks-fifth-avenue-instore-coworking?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/wework-teams-saks-fifth-avenue-instore-coworking?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 03:01:46 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: August 11</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F2485%2Foutdoor_equinox_gym.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(The Atlantic)  Read: Grief, conspiracy theories, and one family’s search for meaning in the two decades since 9/11. NASA said making spacesuits could delay its goal of landing on the moon in 2024.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/key-performance-indicators-august-11?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/key-performance-indicators-august-11?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 03:01:46 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Soccer Icon Lionel Messi Signs With Paris in a Move That Will Reverberate Beyond the Pitch</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6174%2Ftopshot-fbl-fra-ligue1-ps.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Qatari government poured its oil money into PSG to increase the country’s global profile, turning the club into one of the richest soccer franchises in the world. Lionel Messi, considered by many the best soccer player in the world, flew to France yesterday and confirmed his stunning move from Barcelona to Paris Saint-Germain (PSG).</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/soccer-icon-lionel-messi-signs-paris-move-will-reverberate-beyond-pitch?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/soccer-icon-lionel-messi-signs-paris-move-will-reverberate-beyond-pitch?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 03:01:46 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Influencers Want You To Get Vaccinated</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6176%2Favengers.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; The video (and the only Benny Drama clip that’s appropriate to share in this newsletter) is one of many instances of US health leaders utilizing social media influencers to fight Covid-19 vaccine misinformation and encourage young people to get vaccinated.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/influencers-want-get-vaccinated?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>covid</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/influencers-want-get-vaccinated?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 03:01:46 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Senate Passes $1 Trillion Infrastructure Bill. Here's the Context.</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/3o72F8t9TDi2xVnxOE/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 3 things to know about US infrastructure spendingIt peaked with the New Deal: During the Great Depression in 1933, the federal government spent 2.96% of US GDP on infrastructure, and we haven’t hit that mark since. State and local governments accounted for nearly 78% of all US public infrastructure spending in 2017.  We say $1 trillion, but new spending accounts for $550 billion of the package, while the rest is previously approved funding. This infrastructure bill won’t do that.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/senate-passes-1-trillion-infrastructure-bill-heres-context?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>economy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/senate-passes-1-trillion-infrastructure-bill-heres-context?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 03:01:46 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>How to choose a cryptocurrency (and crypto platform)</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6177%2Ftrading_cryptocurrency_on_mobile_exchange.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;.  You can trade crypto futures via:Chicago Mercantile ExchangeBakktCrypto stocksThere are several cryptocurrency companies with publicly-traded shares that you can get your hands on. The process will likely go as follows:Sign upVerification (also known as “KYC AML,” for “know your customer” identity verification and “anti-money laundering” regulatory steps)Connect your bank accountPurchase crypto for 0.5% to 2% feeHold crypto on the platform or move it to “hot” (Internet-connected) or “cold” (disconnected) storageAnd that’s it! Ether (ETH)Ether—also sometimes called Ethereum after the name of its corresponding platform—is the second-largest digital asset, representing roughly 20% of the crypto market. ) Bitcoin is a digital form of money that can be sent worldwide for a small transaction fee and is nearly impossible to hack. Let’s say you’re an investor with experience and you don’t want to go through the hassle of handling your own cryptocurrency trades. Examples:Coinbase (COIN) — the well-known crypto exchangeMicroStrategy (MSTR) — a business services company and leading Bitcoin investorSilvergate Bank (SI) — a digital asset bankMarathon Digital (MARA) — a leading Bitcoin minerJust remember... and everybody elseSeeking crypto investment options beyond Bitcoin and Ethereum is no different than any other kind of experimental bet—in exchange for upping your risk profile considerably, you could give your portfolio exposure to bleeding-edge technology that could dominate the market in the future. com (CRO)OGs: Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Dogecoin (DOGE), Ripple (XRP)Payment tokens: Litecoin (LTC), Terra (LUNA), Stellar (XLM)NFTs: Axie Infinity (AXS), Flow (FLOW), Decentraland (MANA)In summaryIn the crypto world, Bitcoin and Ether are the GOATs. But if you’re looking into what many people would call “altcoins,” there are many paths to take. Ethereum ultimately powers a network of decentralized crypto businesses that everyone can use and nobody can take down. Choose your cryptocurrencyThe two titansTwo cryptos stand head and shoulders over the rest, representing nearly 70% of the total industry: Bitcoin and Ether.  But in a world being eaten alive by software, the allure of grabbing some digital gold amid the rush is undeniable.  Bitcoin (BTC)Created in 2009, Bitcoin is the oldest cryptocurrency and maintains a dominant market share of about half the market.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/choose-cryptocurrency-crypto-platform</link>
  <author>Mark Murdock</author>
  <categories>cryptocurrency</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/11/choose-cryptocurrency-crypto-platform</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 21:51:49 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>WeWork Teams Up With Saks Fifth Avenue For In-Store Coworking</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6175%2Fsakswork.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Bottom line: Turning stores into offices is the latest development in an ongoing quest to repurpose empty retail space, and it’s way less bizarre than when Spirit Halloween takes over an abandoned Babies R Us.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/wework-teams-saks-fifth-avenue-instore-coworking</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/wework-teams-saks-fifth-avenue-instore-coworking</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 15:06:51 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Influencers Want You To Get Vaccinated</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/BW7QHkBICEZG0/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; The video (and the only Benny Drama clip that’s appropriate to share in this newsletter) is one of many instances of US health leaders utilizing social media influencers to encourage young people to get vaccinated and fight Covid-19 vaccine misinformation.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/influencers-want-get-vaccinated</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>covid</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/influencers-want-get-vaccinated</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 15:01:52 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Soccer Icon Lionel Messi Signs With Paris in a Move That Will Reverberate Beyond the Pitch</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6174%2Ftopshot-fbl-fra-ligue1-ps.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Qatari government poured its oil money into PSG to increase the country’s global profile, turning the club into one of the richest soccer franchises in the world. Lionel Messi, considered by many the best soccer player in the world, flew to France yesterday and confirmed his stunning move from Barcelona to Paris Saint-Germain (PSG).</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/soccer-icon-lionel-messi-signs-paris-move-will-reverberate-beyond-pitch</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/soccer-icon-lionel-messi-signs-paris-move-will-reverberate-beyond-pitch</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 15:01:52 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: August 11</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F2485%2Foutdoor_equinox_gym.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(The Atlantic)  Read: Grief, conspiracy theories, and one family’s search for meaning in the two decades since 9/11. NASA said making spacesuits could delay its goal of landing on the moon in 2024.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/key-performance-indicators-august-11</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/key-performance-indicators-august-11</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 15:01:52 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Senate Passes $1 Trillion Infrastructure Bill. Here's the Context.</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/3o72F8t9TDi2xVnxOE/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 3 things to know about US infrastructure spendingIt peaked with the New Deal: During the Great Depression in 1933, the federal government spent 2.96% of US GDP on infrastructure, and we haven’t hit that mark since. State and local governments accounted for nearly 78% of all US public infrastructure spending in 2017.  We say $1 trillion, but new spending accounts for just $550 billion of the package, while the rest is previously approved funding. This infrastructure bill won’t do that.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/senate-passes-1-trillion-infrastructure-bill-heres-context</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>economy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/senate-passes-1-trillion-infrastructure-bill-heres-context</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 14:56:51 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Biggest Changes To the Post-Pandemic Workplace Will Be Invisible</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/ZlgwEg24rPhv9cju8K/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If we look at a) Sydney, Australia, and Nottingham, UK, which have intermittently resumed office work and b) US companies’ latest plans for post-pandemic office space, it’s clear most workplaces will look more like futuristic WeWorks than Mr. Nobody’s White Room. offices will likely have stricter (and more obvious) protocols when employees first return, and like what’s currently happening in Australia, they may have to toggle back and forth between fully open and shut down until Covid-19 flare-ups are under control. Google's blog shows off Camp CharlestonThe other way offices will get more fresh air to employees? Bottom line: From air filtration to green spaces, the office transformations discussed so far will be implemented to make employees feel—and actually be—safer from the spread of disease, especially Covid-19, while working at the office. Other changes will focus on accommodating newly hybrid workforcesMany workers who’ve spent the past 1+ years cooking elaborate breakfasts aren’t ready to return to microwaved oatmeal: 30% of employees would seek out a different job if their companies returned to fully in-office work following the pandemic, per a Mckinsey survey. but not so much that employees will have to battle for workspaces like they’re going full seagull on each other for kettle chips. It’s when employees “rent” a desk for the day, or hours at a time, and share it with other coworkers when they’re OOO. It depends on how many days each employee swipes in, which will vary by workplace. At Adtrak, employees will book their desks in advance through an app.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/biggest-changes-postpandemic-workplace-will-invisible</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>work</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/biggest-changes-postpandemic-workplace-will-invisible</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 13:31:52 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Word Search: Breakfast Cereal Mascots</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5925%2Fword_search_banner_image.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/word-search-breakfast-cereal-mascots</link>
  <author>Mary Tobler</author>
  <categories>games</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/10/word-search-breakfast-cereal-mascots</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 11:21:45 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>NASA Is Looking for Human Guinea Pigs for Simulated Mars Mission</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6164%2Fmars_dune_alpha_habitat.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you want to get away from it all—Covid, climate change, people who just text “hey”—NASA is giving you an opportunity to live on fake Mars for a year. If not, we hear Richard Branson is selling tickets to space for $450,000 a pop.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/nasa-looking-human-guinea-pigs-simulated-mars-mission?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>space</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/nasa-looking-human-guinea-pigs-simulated-mars-mission?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 03:01:48 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: August 10</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6163%2Ftopshot-us-fire-californi.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AMC CEO Adam Aron sang a cautious tune after his company, which got clobbered by the pandemic but staged a furious, individual investor-led comeback, beat revenue expectations last quarter. (Slate)</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/key-performance-indicators-august-10?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/key-performance-indicators-august-10?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 03:01:48 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Car Rental Industry Rebounds As the Economy Rockets Out of the Pandemic</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6165%2Fdaily_life_in_new_york_ci.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;One year after it filed for bankruptcy, the car rental company posted a 62% jump in sales and plans to relist on a major stock exchange by the end of 2021.  Zoom out: The surge in summer travel and the nationwide shortage of used cars has fueled the rebound of the rental car industry.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/car-rental-industry-rebounds-economy-rockets-pandemic?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Sherry Qin</author>
  <categories>auto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/car-rental-industry-rebounds-economy-rockets-pandemic?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 03:01:48 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Democrats Announce $3.5 Trillion Budget Plan</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5265%2Fwhite_house_budget.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  Democrats will need to find a way to raise or suspend it soon to avoid economic chaos. One high-stakes battle remains: the debt ceiling, aka the limit on the US' ability to borrow money. Unfortunately for them, Democrats could push it through later this year without any GOP support thanks to their thin majority in the Senate.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/democrats-announce-35-trillion-budget-plan?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Sherry Qin</author>
  <categories>government</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/democrats-announce-35-trillion-budget-plan?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 03:01:47 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>What You Need to Know About The UNs New Climate Report</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5370%2Fco2.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The report blamed one particular human activity for exacerbating climate change: burning fossil fuels. The Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC), an official UN task force, released a 3,949-page report from 234 scientists yesterday that called current climate change trends a “code red for humanity.” But they need to speed up those cuts dramatically, the report argued.    “This report must sound a death knell for coal and fossil fuels before they destroy our planet," UN Secretary-general Antonio Guterres said.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/need-know-uns-new-climate-report?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>climate</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/need-know-uns-new-climate-report?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 03:01:47 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>What You Need to Know About The UNs New Climate Report</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5370%2Fco2.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is our last decade to make some changes, the report argued. The Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC), an official UN task force, released a 3,949-page report from 234 scientists representing 45+ different countries yesterday morning that it called a “code red for humanity.” The report blamed one particular human activity for exacerbating climate change: burning fossil fuels. Since the IPCC’s last big report in 2013, the world has done a better job in curbing carbon emissions.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/need-know-uns-new-climate-report</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>environment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/need-know-uns-new-climate-report</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 15:36:52 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: August 10</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6163%2Ftopshot-us-fire-californi.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AMC CEO Adam Aron, sang a cautious tune after his company, which got clobbered by the pandemic but staged a furious, individual investor-led comeback, beat revenue expectations last quarter. (Slate)</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/key-performance-indicators-august-10</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/key-performance-indicators-august-10</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 15:26:49 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>NASA Is Looking for Human Guinea Pigs for Simulated Mars Mission</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6164%2Fmars_dune_alpha_habitat.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you want to get away from it all—Covid, climate change, people who just text “hey”—NASA is giving you an opportunity to live on Mars for a year. If not, we hear Richard Branson is selling tickets to space for $450,000 a pop.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/nasa-looking-human-guinea-pigs-simulated-mars-mission</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>space</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/nasa-looking-human-guinea-pigs-simulated-mars-mission</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 15:26:49 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Car Rental Industry Rebounds As the Economy Rockets Out of the Pandemic</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6165%2Fdaily_life_in_new_york_ci.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The greatest Covid comeback story: Hertz went bankrupt last June at the peak of the pandemic, weighed down by nearly $19 billion in debt, and roughly 700,000 cars parked with no one to drive them.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/car-rental-industry-rebounds-economy-rockets-pandemic</link>
  <author>Sherry Qin</author>
  <categories>car rental</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/car-rental-industry-rebounds-economy-rockets-pandemic</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 15:26:49 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Democrats Announce $3.5 Trillion Budget Plan</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5265%2Fwhite_house_budget.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;   It will address... The budget will require the backing of every Democrat in the 50-50 Senate, plus the tie breaking vote of VP Kamala Harris, to pass. Where will the money come from? The plan didn’t include lifting the debt ceiling, which would allow Uncle Sam to keep on borrowing to fund the spending.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/democrats-announce-35-trillion-budget-plan</link>
  <author>Sherry Qin</author>
  <categories>budget</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/democrats-announce-35-trillion-budget-plan</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 15:21:46 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The new office politics? An ‘existential crisis’ for some</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6166%2Fpeople_talking_in_office_hallway.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Lat speaks about a law firm that recently decreed employees must return to the office five days a week, only to be met with staff reaching out en masse to recruiters for jobs elsewhere. You may have heard of this described as the “hybrid” work environment, where some people work from home and others log on from a corporate office. The idea that office politics are winnable? “That might not be a bad thing because there are a lot of artificial deadlines of, ‘I want this on my desk first thing in the morning’ by bosses who, lo and behold, don’t read that until the afternoon or the next day,” he says.  The shift to a virtual workplace was hard on office politics, too, particularly in hidebound industries like finance and law where remote work was relatively rare before the pandemic. For example, some workers are easing their sense of urgency around work projects, Lat notes, because it proved to be a charade all along. What I’ve seen and heard from workers is that now, when a manager steps in, they’re actually getting in the way of work.” “The invisible work women have always done is finally being recognized and appreciated because men had to experience it,” says Dawn Bovasso, a freelance creative director in Boston who has written about workplace policies’ effects on women. “The old way was really exclusive, excluding a lot of people: people of color, women, the differently abled—a lot of people,” she says.  If the performative politics of pre-pandemic office life are a bowl of ice cream, the pandemic surely melted it. “This new way is going to be inclusive. If the corporate world’s reaction to the COVID-19 pandemic turned 2020 into a mad scramble for new protocols defined by adaptive office tools like Google Docs, Slack, and Zoom, then its adjustment to a tentative recovery suggests a partial return to the office and semi normalcy. “A lot of office politics is over stupid stuff and a lot of that stupid stuff is tied to the physical environment: fighting over the corner office, talking so loudly on calls that coworkers can hear them down the hall, being bad at bathroom etiquette, vaping at your desk, leaving smelly food in the break room,” he says. The virtual environment has undoubtedly given workers more power over their supervisors. “It is challenging to replicate office politics in a virtual era, which isn’t a bad thing,” says David Lat, a longtime analyst of law firm culture and himself a former top-tier recruiter. “So much of politics arises from physical interaction, so if we have less interaction we have less cause for conflict and less need for politics.” True, the completely virtual environment that many people have been working in for 17 months has hardly been a cakewalk.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/new-office-politics-existential-crisis</link>
  <author>Morning Brew</author>
  <categories>work life</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/09/new-office-politics-existential-crisis</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 15:01:57 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>

</channel>
</rss>
