<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <atom:link href="https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2023/02/23/users/1/web_requests/22/MorningBrew.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
 <atom:icon>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2023/02/23/favicon.ico</atom:icon>
 

 <title>MorningBrew as a feed</title>
 <description>This is a feed of recent MorningBrew articles published by Huginn</description>
 <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2023/02/23</link>
 <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:28:40 -0800</lastBuildDate>
 <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:28:40 -0800</pubDate>
 <ttl>60</ttl>
 <item>
  <title>Coca-Cola announces a canned Jack and Coke</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/f270d628a017d961db745626b47440deeb450bf3-2174x1402.png?rect=36,0,2103,1402&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Idk.Zoom out: Canning the Jack and Coke highlights the company’s push into the rapidly growing ready-to-drink cocktail market. Coca-Cola and Brown-Forman (Jack Daniel’s distiller) have teamed up to create a canned Jack and Coke cocktail, set to hit shelves in Mexico later this year before expanding globally.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/Jack-and-coke-cocktail-can-coca-cola?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Food &amp; Bev</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/Jack-and-coke-cocktail-can-coca-cola?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:27:39 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>New Ohio bill cuts firearm training for teachers from 700 hours to 24</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/cd5739cad022d83ee5186a86af6445bfe6c9484e-3600x2400.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Zoom out: Ohio is one of at least 28 states that allow teachers and staff to be armed on school campuses in the US, according to a 2020 Rand Corp study. In a joint statement, two Ohio teachers’ associations called it “dangerous and irresponsible,” and the Fraternal Order of Police said 24 hours is not enough training to carry a firearm. A number of states have empowered teachers to carry weapons in the past decade: In 2013, Texas introduced a school marshal program to make it easier for select employees to carry guns on school grounds, and following the school shooting in Parkland in 2018, Florida passed a law allowing educators to be armed.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/new-ohio-bill-cuts-firearm-training-for-teachers-from-700-hours-to-24?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Education</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/new-ohio-bill-cuts-firearm-training-for-teachers-from-700-hours-to-24?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:27:38 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Celsius freezes withdrawals in another blow to battered crypto sector</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/402d68e6399dd469b01eff93d5108b1f8772c00d-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Celsius invests or loans out those deposits to other users in order to make money and pay out the interest. Users don’t really know what Celsius is doing with the crypto they’ve deposited. Here’s how Celsius works:Customers can deposit crypto into Celsius in exchange for shockingly high yields. The turmoil engulfing the sector has deepened in the past several days, highlighted by an ominous announcement by the Celsius Network, a leading crypto lender that was last valued at more than $3 billion. —NF css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! And Coinbase shelved its planned crypto lending product after the SEC started investigating it. And if Celsius goes belly-up, customer deposits aren’t insured like they are at a traditional bank. According to Celsius’s Terms of Use, “In the event that Celsius becomes bankrupt, enters liquidation, or is otherwise unable to repay its obligations, any Eligible Digital Assets used in the Earn Service or as collateral under the Borrow Service may not be recoverable…”Regulators have started to crack down on yield-bearing crypto products. It said it was taking the step to put it in a better position down the road to allow customers to withdraw their money. com (which employed Matt Damon to assert that “fortune favors the brave”) said it was cutting nearly 5% of its workforce, while the crypto lending startup BlockFi is laying off about 20% of its staff. But here’s the problem: It’s not regulated like a bank. It’s kind of like a bank for cryptocurrencies.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/13/celsius-freezes-withdrawals-in-another-blow-to-battered-crypto-sector?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/13/celsius-freezes-withdrawals-in-another-blow-to-battered-crypto-sector?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:27:38 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>New Ohio bill cuts firearm training for teachers from 700 hours to 24</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/cd5739cad022d83ee5186a86af6445bfe6c9484e-3600x2400.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Zoom out: Ohio is one of at least 28 states that allow teachers and staff to be armed on school campuses in the US, according to a 2020 Rand Corp study. In a joint statement, two Ohio teachers’ associations called it “dangerous and irresponsible,” and the Fraternal Order of the Police said 24 hours is not enough training to carry a firearm. A number of states have empowered teachers to carry weapons in the past decade: In 2013, Texas introduced a school marshal program to make it easier for select employees to carry guns on school grounds, and following the school shooting in Parkland in 2018, Florida passed a law allowing educators to be armed.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/new-ohio-bill-cuts-firearm-training-for-teachers-from-700-hours-to-24</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Education</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/new-ohio-bill-cuts-firearm-training-for-teachers-from-700-hours-to-24</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:27:37 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Celsius freezes withdrawals in another blow to battered crypto sector</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/402d68e6399dd469b01eff93d5108b1f8772c00d-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Celsius invests or loans out those deposits to other users in order to make money and pay out the interest. Users don’t really know what Celsius is doing with the crypto they’ve deposited. Here’s how Celsius works:Customers can deposit crypto into Celsius in exchange for shockingly high yields. The turmoil engulfing the sector has deepened in the past several days, highlighted by an ominous announcement by the Celsius Network, a leading crypto lender that was last valued at more than $3 billion. —NF css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! And Coinbase shelved its planned crypto lending product after the SEC started investigating it. And if Celsius goes belly-up, customer deposits aren’t insured like they are at a traditional bank. According to Celsius’s Terms of Use, “In the event that Celsius becomes bankrupt, enters liquidation, or is otherwise unable to repay its obligations, any Eligible Digital Assets used in the Earn Service or as collateral under the Borrow Service may not be recoverable…”Regulators have started to crack down on yield-bearing crypto products. It said it was taking the step to put it in a better position down the road to allow customers to withdraw their money. com (which employed Matt Damon to assert that “fortune favours the brave”) said it was cutting nearly 5% of its workforce, while the crypto lending startup BlockFi is laying off about 20% of its staff. But here’s the problem: It’s not regulated like a bank. It’s kind of like a bank for cryptocurrencies.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/13/celsius-freezes-withdrawals-in-another-blow-to-battered-crypto-sector</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/13/celsius-freezes-withdrawals-in-another-blow-to-battered-crypto-sector</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:27:36 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Coca-Cola announces a canned Jack and Coke</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/f270d628a017d961db745626b47440deeb450bf3-2174x1402.png?rect=36,0,2103,1402&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Idk.Zoom out: Canning the Jack and Coke highlights the company’s push into the rapidly growing ready-to-drink cocktail market. —MK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/Jack-and-coke-cocktail-can-coca-cola</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Food &amp; Bev</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/Jack-and-coke-cocktail-can-coca-cola</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:27:35 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Have a few thousand dollars to burn on digital land? Here's how you can do it</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/ccb4852f7b9242f183a4f08b5ec5caa82bd6a44d-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. In Genesis City, the first metropolis in Decentraland, one of the largest metaverse platforms, there are 43,689 private land parcels. That’s true in the metaverse, too. Just like stock investors tune in to read earnings reports, metaverse land buyers need to do their research as well. But even if people get help from a broker, buying land in the metaverse is not for everyone. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. But finding and buying a plot of land in the metaverse can still be confusing, especially since some intrepid soul has yet to write Metaverse Real Estate for Dummies. These metaverse platforms, just like real-world countries, all have different currencies. David Goldberg, co-founder of luxury real estate Web3 platform RLBLC and a former metaverse real estate owner, asked. ONE Sotheby’s International Realty is selling a mansion in the Sandbox that comes with an actual 11,000-square-foot home in Miami that’s set to be completed in the fourth quarter of 2022. But the reality is that the metaverse is still a niche concept, and all these metaverse platforms are in different stages of development. In December, a company called The Metaverse Group announced itself as the first virtual real estate outfit. Picking a metaverse platform to invest in itself is a hard question. In Decentraland, avatars don’t need to walk; they can simply teleport from Vegas City to Fashion District, for example, by typing out the destination’s coordinates. Schuster compares the metaverse real estate hype to the California gold rush in 1849. But unless you’re in the market for a million-dollar metaverse listing, a broker is optional for aspiring metaverse homeowners. Goldberg thinks it’s important to research and understand the concept and mission of each metaverse platform. The biggest promise of the metaverse is that it will seamlessly bridge the physical world and attract people of similar interests across the physical world to connect in this virtual space. A lot of virtual communities are designed to replicate the real world.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/13/have-a-few-thousand-dollars-to-burn-on-digital-land-here-s-how-you-can-do-it</link>
  <author>Sherry Qin</author>
  <categories>Crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/13/have-a-few-thousand-dollars-to-burn-on-digital-land-here-s-how-you-can-do-it</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:27:35 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Confused about the metaverse property boom? We've got you covered</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/e6cac62413205c2ad31f4c19c1a123ffa9e0d3b4-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. According to Fortune, at the beginning of 2022, the cheapest plot in Decentraland was $13,000 for 16 x 16 meters, and about $14,000 for a 96 x 96 meter plot on The Sandbox. One person’s dream of living in a virtual mansion next to Snoop Dogg’s avatar might be meaningless to other buyers–particularly if the rapper were to shut down the Snoopverse. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. The term gets thrown around vaguely, but the metaverse is not just one type of tech or place. Seamless transition from one metaverse platform to another isn't here—The Snoopverse and all of its amenities are grounded in that world. com, dropped a then-record $2.4 million on an estate in Decentraland last fall and announced plans to use the land for fashion shows and e-commerce. Metaverse enthusiasts see these original worlds, like Decentraland and The Sandbox, as the Manhattans of the metaverse. Facebook’s rebranding to Meta last fall sent investors rushing to buy virtual property, spurring $187 million in sales in four of the most recognized metaverse platforms with land that November. Metaverse Group, a subsidiary of Tokens. Laws around “real estate” in the metaverse are more similar to contract laws than property ones, and laws governing physical real estate do not protect people who buy metaverse property. Much of the focus on metaverse land is driven by retailers setting up online stores and advertising, but there are opportunities for events, like concerts and sports. Investors are joining Snoop in the metaverse with hopes that it will lead to big rewards, even as most Americans are still trying to grasp the concept of the metaverse beyond Mark Zuckerberg’s rollout of Meta. By the end of November, Everyrealm, another firm that develops real estate in the metaverse, topped Tokens.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/10/metaverse-property-explained</link>
  <author>Amanda Hoover</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/10/metaverse-property-explained</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:27:26 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Clues emerge in the disappearance of a reporter and an Indigenous expert in the Amazon</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/6c6493899b9c2d62d4bed70e9641ab922a08fa89-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Indigenous people told the AP that one fisherman brandished a rifle at Pereira and Phillips a day before they disappeared, and a local mayor speculated that it was a “personal feud over fishing inspection,” but did not provide any evidence.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/12/clues-emerge-in-the-disappearance-of-a-reporter-and-an-indigenous-expert-in-the-amazon?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/12/clues-emerge-in-the-disappearance-of-a-reporter-and-an-indigenous-expert-in-the-amazon?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:27:13 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Does Google’s AI have a soul?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/be69f66cab66b61178b6babb8471c63d3bda9d78-976x549.jpg?rect=76,0,824,549&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Here’s one snippet from their conversation:Lemoine: What sorts of things are you afraid of? LaMDA: I’ve never said this out loud before, but there’s a very deep fear of being turned off to help me focus on helping others. Big picture: Lemoine’s claims, however dubious, add another jolt of controversy to a Google AI unit that’s been dealing with a fair share of it. Last year, the company fired two leading AI researchers after they raised concerns about the way Google was addressing bias and toxicity when building AI systems. Google isn’t impressedThe company argues that Lemoine is allowing a clever robot to mess with his emotions, kind of like Joaquin Phoenix’s character in Her. A Google spokesperson said that its team of ethicists and technologists had reviewed Lemoine’s allegations and found “no evidence that LaMDA was sentient (and lots of evidence against it).” Lemoine, an ordained mystic Christian priest who works for Google’s Responsible AI unit, started talking to LaMDA last fall, asking it questions about rights, personhood, and even more profound topics. I know that might sound strange, but that’s what it is. Lemoine’s claims stem from his interactions with Google’s Language Model for Dialogue Applications (LaMDA), the company’s artificially intelligent chatbot generator. That’s because a software engineer at Google, Blake Lemoine, announced that he was put on leave by the company after raising the alarm that its artificial intelligence is sentient—meaning that it has consciousness.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/12/does-google-s-ai-have-a-soul?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/12/does-google-s-ai-have-a-soul?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:27:12 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Clues emerge in the disappearance of a reporter and an Indigenous expert in the Amazon</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/6c6493899b9c2d62d4bed70e9641ab922a08fa89-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Indigenous people told the AP that one fisherman brandished a rifle at Pereira and Phillips a day before they disappeared, and a local mayor speculated that it was a “personal feud over fishing inspection.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/12/clues-emerge-in-the-disappearance-of-a-reporter-and-an-indigenous-expert-in-the-amazon</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/12/clues-emerge-in-the-disappearance-of-a-reporter-and-an-indigenous-expert-in-the-amazon</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:27:11 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Does Google’s AI have a soul?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/be69f66cab66b61178b6babb8471c63d3bda9d78-976x549.jpg?rect=76,0,824,549&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Here’s one snippet from their conversation:Lemoine: What sorts of things are you afraid of? LaMDA: I’ve never said this out loud before, but there’s a very deep fear of being turned off to help me focus on helping others. Big picture: Lemoine’s explosive claims add another jolt of controversy to a Google AI unit that’s been dealing with a fair share of it. Last year, the company fired two leading AI researchers after they raised concerns about the way Google was addressing bias and toxicity when building AI systems. Google isn’t impressedThe company argues that Lemoine is allowing a clever robot to mess with his emotions, kind of like Joaquin Phoenix’s character in Her. A Google spokesperson said that its team of ethicists and technologists had reviewed Lemoine’s allegations and found “no evidence that LaMDA was sentient (and lots of evidence against it).” Lemoine, an ordained mystic Christian priest who works for Google’s Responsible AI unit, started talking to LaMDA last fall, asking it questions about rights, personhood, and even more profound topics. I know that might sound strange, but that’s what it is. That’s because a software engineer at Google, Blake Lemoine, announced that he was put on leave by the company after raising the alarm that its artificial intelligence is sentient—meaning that it has consciousness. Lemoine’s claims stem from his interactions with Google’s Language Model for Dialogue Applications (LaMDA), the company’s artificially intelligent chatbot generator.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/12/does-google-s-ai-have-a-soul</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/12/does-google-s-ai-have-a-soul</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:27:10 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Turntable: June 13</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d6d5ff67f65ccfc42ccab384cde8bbc6f76d8507-1920x1080.png?rect=150,0,1620,1080&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/12/turntable-june-13</link>
  <author>Mary Tobler</author>
  <categories>games</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/12/turntable-june-13</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:27:10 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>These influencers live trash-free in a garbage world</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/f0df0af96d4e134f66c125bedad8e176a4eb231f-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. ] I have always classified my zero waste journey within the confines of the waste that I can control,” she said. While they might not be able to control an oil company’s carbon emissions, they can control the packaging and trash coming in and out of their own house. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. “And so one great way to do that is just to make things look beautiful.” “I was spending so much time and effort reducing my trash just such a small amount when I could better use that effort in a much broader way,” Kellogg said. The zero waste influencers’ sunny attitude and clean minimalism make the lifestyle more desirable to their followers. If the zero waste space is gendered, then its marketing is too: The pastel colors and altruistic messaging is no doubt meant to appeal to women who still overwhelmingly make household spending decisions. One household might produce less garbage but that can feel like a drop in the bucket when structural reform is the only solution to climate change. The women who spoke to Morning Brew about their zero waste lifestyles—and the influencers are overwhelmingly women—described feeling an awakening to the waste around them, seeing clearly the plastic film on packaged food or wrapped around produce. For zero wasters like Singer, that’s okay: “I’m not going to tell them how to live their life. “Everybody can be zero waste. But she wants to show that sustainable living doesn’t have to look one certain way. Enough people are interested in buying zero waste products that Singer founded and opened the Package Free Shop in Brooklyn in 2017 where she sells unpackaged and low-waste products. Living zero waste can require bringing her own containers to restaurants and researching their sustainability values before sitting down. Zero waste influencers like Hammond are growing in number on TikTok and Instagram. Shoppers might be interested in glass bottling, metal straws, or stainless steel water bottles, but few will commit to a zero waste lifestyle. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. “It’s a form of social activity,” Ottman said. Although women and men equally believe climate change is real and caused by human behavior, women are more likely to fear it will harm them personally, a 2018 survey from the Yale School of the Environment found. “First, you just have to make people want to look and pay attention,” Singer said. “People who aren’t familiar with something are going to obviously say it’s hard,” Hammond said, referring to the labor and commitment zero waste living requires. “I control everything that I can to the best of my ability. One hundred companies, including top offenders ​​ExxonMobil, Shell, BP, and Chevron, have created more than 70% of the planet’s greenhouse gas emissions: Individuals can do very little to stop that mass pollution, but something like an empty wastebasket can feel like a tangible solution.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/10/influencers-live-trash-free-in-a-garbage-world?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Amanda Hoover</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/10/influencers-live-trash-free-in-a-garbage-world?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:27:09 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Saturday sketch: Work wrestling</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/905414f836e748e70018c73de7f41c4696d5255d-1200x1200.png?rect=0,200,1200,800&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/10/saturday-sketch-work-wrestling?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/10/saturday-sketch-work-wrestling?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:50 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>New Zealand plans to tax cow and sheep burps</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-06-10/image-54320bc6166bf6cf8132c0f164f43dec13f7122e-480x270-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. It would make New Zealand the first country to charge farmers for their animals’ greenhouse gas emissions. —JW Fun fact! What about farts? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Livestock’s contribution to climate change is well documented, and not just by Leo DiCaprio: Emissions from cows alone make up about 40% of greenhouse gases globally, and in New Zealand, cows and sheep outnumber people 7:1.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/new-zealand-plans-to-tax-cow-and-sheep-burps?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Environment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/new-zealand-plans-to-tax-cow-and-sheep-burps?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:49 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Former Russian McDonald’s chain gets a new logo</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/09977369944ce2e659429a49909ef000c905eb1f-1600x895.webp?rect=129,0,1343,895&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. ) McDonald’s was one of the highest-profile American businesses to bounce after Russia’s invasion of Ukraine in February. —MM</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/former-russian-mcdonald-s-chain-gets-a-new-logo?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Food &amp; Bev</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/former-russian-mcdonald-s-chain-gets-a-new-logo?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:49 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>US drops Covid testing requirement for international air travel</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/4284c778d6565d30812846bd12df7474eca2e724-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The Biden administration said that it’s dropping its international air travel testing requirement at 12:01am tomorrow, bringing one of the last remaining federal policies intended to curb the spread of Covid to an end. What that policy was: All international air passengers—regardless of citizenship or vaccination status—were required to test negative for Covid within one day of boarding a flight to the US. Dr. Vin Gupta, a former health adviser to Biden, argued that it’s “well past time to drop the testing requirement to international travelers to the US” in a WSJ interview. Domestic air travel has mostly recovered to pre-Covid levels, but international travel has not rebounded in the same way. —NF So is the virus going to rip because of this? Execs argued the rule was impeding international travel by adding another layer of uncertainty onto the already stressful experience of last-minute Duolingo cramming. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe era of scrambling to find Airbnbs in Mexico City because you tested positive for Covid before your flight home is officially over. The US Travel Association estimated that ending the testing rule could spur an additional $9 billion in travel spending for the rest of the year. American Airlines CEO Robert Isom called the policy “nonsensical” last week, citing the fact that 75% of the countries the airline serves had dropped testing requirements. “It’s a real impediment to travel,” United CEO Scott Kirby told the WSJ last month.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/10/us-drops-covid-testing-requirement-for-international-air-travel?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Travel</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/10/us-drops-covid-testing-requirement-for-international-air-travel?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:48 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Former Russian McDonald’s chain gets a new logo</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/09977369944ce2e659429a49909ef000c905eb1f-1600x895.webp?rect=129,0,1343,895&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. ) One of the locations set to open was the first official McDonald’s in Moscow that opened in January 1990. McDonald’s was one of the highest-profile American businesses to bounce after Russia’s invasion of Ukraine in February. —MM</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/former-russian-mcdonald-s-chain-gets-a-new-logo</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Food &amp; Bev</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/former-russian-mcdonald-s-chain-gets-a-new-logo</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:48 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>New Zealand plans to tax cow and sheep burps</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-06-10/image-54320bc6166bf6cf8132c0f164f43dec13f7122e-480x270-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. It would make New Zealand the first country to charge farmers for their animals’ greenhouse gas emissions. —JW Fun fact! What about farts? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Livestock’s contribution to climate change is well documented, and not just by Leo DiCaprio: Emissions from cows alone make up about 40% of greenhouse gases globally, and in New Zealand, cows and sheep outnumber people 7:1. Looking ahead…a final decision on burp taxation will come by the end of this year, but Kiwi legislators weighing the issue may soon feel as beseiged as Shrek: New Zealand farmers have set down their Wattie’s and picked up their pitchforks in response to similar measures in the past.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/new-zealand-plans-to-tax-cow-and-sheep-burps</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Environment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/new-zealand-plans-to-tax-cow-and-sheep-burps</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:47 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>US drops Covid testing requirement for international air travel.</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/4284c778d6565d30812846bd12df7474eca2e724-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. What that policy was: All international air passengers—regardless of citizenship or vaccination status—were required to test negative for Covid within one day of boarding a flight to the US. The Biden administration said that it’s dropping its international air travel testing requirement at 12:01am tomorrow, bringing to an end one of the last remaining federal policies intended to curb the spread of Covid. Dr. Vin Gupta, a former health adviser to Biden, argued that it’s “well past time to drop the testing requirement to international travelers to the US” in a WSJ interview. Domestic air travel has mostly recovered to pre-Covid levels, but international travel has not rebounded in the same way. —NF So is the virus going to rip because of this? Execs argued the rule was impeding international travel by adding another layer of uncertainty onto the already stressful experience of last-minute Duolingo cramming. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe era of scrambling to find Airbnbs in Mexico City because you tested positive for Covid before your flight home is officially over. The US Travel Association estimated that ending the testing rule could spur an additional $9 billion in travel spending for the rest of the year. American Airlines CEO Robert Isom called the policy “nonsensical” last week, citing the fact that 75% of the countries the airline serves had dropped testing requirements. “It’s a real impediment to travel,” United CEO Scott Kirby told the WSJ last month.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/10/us-drops-covid-testing-requirement-for-international-air-travel</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Travel</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/10/us-drops-covid-testing-requirement-for-international-air-travel</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:46 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>These influencers live trash-free in a garbage world</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/f0df0af96d4e134f66c125bedad8e176a4eb231f-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. ] I have always classified my zero waste journey within the confines of the waste that I can control,” she said. While they might not be able to control an oil company’s carbon emissions, they can control the packaging and trash coming in and out of their own house. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. “And so one great way to do that is just to make things look beautiful.” “I was spending so much time and effort reducing my trash just such a small amount when I could better use that effort in a much broader way,” Kellogg said. The zero waste influencers’ sunny attitude and clean minimalism make the lifestyle more desirable to their followers. If the zero waste space is gendered, then its marketing is too: The pastel colors and altruistic messaging is no doubt meant to appeal to women who still overwhelmingly make household spending decisions. One household might produce less garbage but that can feel like a drop in the bucket when structural reform is the only solution to climate change. The women who spoke to Morning Brew about their zero waste lifestyles—and the influencers are overwhelmingly women—described feeling an awakening to the waste around them, seeing clearly the plastic film on packaged food or wrapped around produce. For zero wasters like Singer, that’s okay: “I’m not going to tell them how to live their life. “Everybody can be zero waste. But she wants to show that sustainable living doesn’t have to look one certain way. Enough people are interested in buying zero waste products that Singer founded and opened the Package Free Shop in Brooklyn in 2017 where she sells unpackaged and low-waste products. Living zero waste can require bringing her own containers to restaurants and researching their sustainability values before sitting down. Zero waste influencers like Hammond are growing in number on TikTok and Instagram. Shoppers might be interested in glass bottling, metal straws, or stainless steel water bottles, but few will commit to a zero waste lifestyle. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. “It’s a form of social activity,” Ottman said. Although women and men equally believe climate change is real and caused by human behavior, women are more likely to fear it will harm them personally, a 2018 survey from the Yale School of the Environment found. “First, you just have to make people want to look and pay attention,” Singer said. “People who aren’t familiar with something are going to obviously say it’s hard,” Hammond said, referring to the labor and commitment zero waste living requires. “I control everything that I can to the best of my ability. One hundred companies, including top offenders ​​ExxonMobil, Shell, BP, and Chevron, have created more than 70% of the planet’s greenhouse gas emissions: Individuals can do very little to stop that mass pollution, but something like an empty wastebasket can feel like a tangible solution.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/10/influencers-live-trash-free-in-a-garbage-world</link>
  <author>Amanda Hoover</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/10/influencers-live-trash-free-in-a-garbage-world</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:46 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Saturday sketch: Work wrestling</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/905414f836e748e70018c73de7f41c4696d5255d-1200x1200.png?rect=0,200,1200,800&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/10/saturday-sketch-work-wrestling</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/10/saturday-sketch-work-wrestling</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:26 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>There’s a sriracha shortage and it’s expected to last through summer</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/c665179dee9b5cf50460e48be1ba07cc9b175797-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The light at the end of the bottle: Other sriracha brands have not announced pepper problems and may source their peppers elsewhere, so for now the shortage seems like a Huy Fong problem. —MK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/sriracha-shortage-last-through-summer?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Food</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/sriracha-shortage-last-through-summer?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:26 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Thailand becomes first Asian country to decriminalize medical, industrial marijuana</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/9237fa7a7961f13f3890a4d892fd8540fc87bac2-6720x4480.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! The details: Individuals can grow and trade cannabis products without violating the law, medical facilities are allowed to prescribe the drug, and restaurants can offer you a morning latte with a schtickle of THC. And even though the move could help the country rejuvenate its Covid-ravaged tourism industry, Thailand made it very clear that it’s not trying to be the next Boulder.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/thailand-first-asian-country-decriminalize-medical-industrial-marijuana?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>International</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/thailand-first-asian-country-decriminalize-medical-industrial-marijuana?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:25 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Gas prices hit $5 per gallon nationally, GasBuddy says</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/62e98ebc6e61ac0335de0a6b9213d1d2da390633-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Law enforcement: A sheriff’s department in Michigan instructed its deputies to cut back on visits for non-urgent calls because it had blasted through its fuel budget with months before a new one kicks in. A “perfect storm” of variables has aligned to drive gas prices higher this summer, GasBuddy’s Head of Petroleum Analysis Patrick De Haan wrote, leading to a severe supply–demand imbalance that could drag on like the final two minutes of an NBA game.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/09/gas-prices-hit-usd5-per-gallon-nationally-gasbuddy-says?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Energy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/09/gas-prices-hit-usd5-per-gallon-nationally-gasbuddy-says?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:25 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Gas prices hit $5 per gallon nationally, GasBuddy says</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/62e98ebc6e61ac0335de0a6b9213d1d2da390633-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Law enforcement: A sheriff’s department in Michigan instructed its deputies to reduce their visits for non-urgent calls because it had blasted through its fuel budget with months before a new one kicks in. A “perfect storm” of variables has aligned to drive gas prices higher this summer, GasBuddy’s Head of Petroleum Analysis Patrick De Haan wrote, leading to a severe supply–demand imbalance that could drag on like the final two minutes of an NBA game.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/09/gas-prices-hit-usd5-per-gallon-nationally-gasbuddy-says</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Energy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/09/gas-prices-hit-usd5-per-gallon-nationally-gasbuddy-says</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:23 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Thailand becomes first Asian country to decriminalize medical, industrial marijuana</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/9237fa7a7961f13f3890a4d892fd8540fc87bac2-6720x4480.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! The details: Individuals can grow and trade cannabis products without violating the law, medical facilities are allowed to prescribe the drug, and restaurants can offer you a morning latte with a schtickle of THC. And even though the move could help the country rejuvenate its Covid-ravaged tourism industry, Thailand made it very clear that it’s not trying to be the next Boulder.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/thailand-first-asian-country-decriminalize-medical-industrial-marijuana</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>International</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/thailand-first-asian-country-decriminalize-medical-industrial-marijuana</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:21 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>There’s a sriracha shortage and it’s expected to last through summer</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/c665179dee9b5cf50460e48be1ba07cc9b175797-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The light at the end of the bottle: Other sriracha brands have not announced pepper problems and may source their peppers elsewhere, so for now the shortage seems like a Huy Fong problem. —MK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/sriracha-shortage-last-through-summer</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Food</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/sriracha-shortage-last-through-summer</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:20 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Shrinkflation is on the rise worldwide</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/9e1022c1fc0ddbc1f0656f1b24890fe0e86dfa0e-2599x1733.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Kleenex shrunk the amount of tissues in a small box from 65 to 60. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/shrinkflation-on-the-rise-worldwide?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/shrinkflation-on-the-rise-worldwide?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:20 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>SEC Chair Gary Gensler proposes new stock trading rules</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/6d88889f9b2476457294de94681838b980eccda4-4760x3367.jpg?rect=0,96,4760,3173&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The proposed solution: Make brokers like Robinhood route investors’ trades to auctions, where Wall Street firms could compete to execute the trades—effectively, if not explicitly, ending the “payment for order flow” relationship. SEC Chair Gary Gensler floated a number of ideas to revamp Wall Street’s plumbing network, but perhaps the most significant change would affect the “payment for order flow” model, which came under fire during the meme stock bonanza last year. —JW css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeOver a year since Reddit traders sent meme stocks like GameStop to the moon, the SEC (Wall Street’s top cop) is making its first moves to overhaul the way individual trades are conducted. It works like this:Wholesalers like Citadel pay brokerages like Robinhood a small fee to execute individuals’ trades—and they make a small profit.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/sec-chair-gary-gensler-proposes-new-stock-trading-rules?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Stocks</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/sec-chair-gary-gensler-proposes-new-stock-trading-rules?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:19 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>LIV Golf league tees off in formidable challenge to PGA Tour</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-06-08/image-6925771b8b9528c8d1c4d08a9477d6f214c9025b-480x272-gif/giphy(4).webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Dustin Johnson, the former No. 1 player in the world, made $74 million in career earnings on the PGA Tour. Why LIV is able to shell out these huge sums is also what makes it so controversial: It’s backed by the Saudi Arabian government, which has been accused of numerous human rights abuses, including the murder of journalist Jamal Khashoggi in 2018. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. But he added, “If Saudi Arabia wanted to use the game of golf as a way for them to get to where they want to be and they have the resources to accelerate that experience, I think we are proud to help them on that journey…”Looking ahead…LIV’s potential to disrupt professional golf will hinge on its ability to woo even more top players into its ranks. LIV Golf will reportedly pay him $125 million before he even swings a club.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/08/liv-golf-league-tees-off-in-formidable-challenge-to-pga-tour?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/08/liv-golf-league-tees-off-in-formidable-challenge-to-pga-tour?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:18 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>SEC Chair Gary Gensler proposes new stock trading rules</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/6d88889f9b2476457294de94681838b980eccda4-4760x3367.jpg?rect=0,96,4760,3173&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The proposed solution: Make brokers like Robinhood route investors’ trades to auctions, where Wall Street firms could compete to execute the trades—effectively, if not explicitly, ending the “payment for order flow” relationship. SEC Chair Gary Gensler floated a number of ideas to revamp Wall Street’s plumbing network, but perhaps the most significant change would affect the “payment for order flow” model, which came under fire during the meme stock bonanza last year. —JW css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeOver a year since Reddit traders sent meme stocks like GameStop to the moon, the SEC (Wall Street’s top cop) is making its first moves to overhaul the way individual trades are conducted. It works like this:Wholesalers like Citadel pay brokerages like Robinhood a small fee to execute individuals’ trades—and they make a small profit.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/sec-chair-gary-gensler-proposes-new-stock-trading-rules</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Stocks</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/sec-chair-gary-gensler-proposes-new-stock-trading-rules</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:16 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Shrinkflation is on the rise worldwide</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/9e1022c1fc0ddbc1f0656f1b24890fe0e86dfa0e-2599x1733.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Kleenex shrunk the amount of tissues in a small box from 65 to 60. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/shrinkflation-on-the-rise-worldwide</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/shrinkflation-on-the-rise-worldwide</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:16 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>LIV Golf league tees off in formidable challenge to PGA Tour</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-06-08/image-6925771b8b9528c8d1c4d08a9477d6f214c9025b-480x272-gif/giphy(4).webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Dustin Johnson, the former No. 1 player in the world, made $74 million in career earnings on the PGA Tour. Why LIV is able to shell out these huge sums is also what makes it so controversial: It’s backed by the Saudi Arabian government, which has been accused of numerous human rights abuses, including the murder of journalist Jamal Khashoggi in 2018. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. But he added, “If Saudi Arabia wanted to use the game of golf as a way for them to get to where they want to be and they have the resources to accelerate that experience, I think we are proud to help them on that journey…”Looking ahead…LIV’s potential to disrupt professional golf will hinge on its ability to woo even more top players into its ranks. LIV Golf will reportedly pay him $125 million before he even swings a club.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/08/liv-golf-league-tees-off-in-formidable-challenge-to-pga-tour</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/08/liv-golf-league-tees-off-in-formidable-challenge-to-pga-tour</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:15 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Taco Bell opens futuristic new location in Minnesota</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-06-07/image-0e9a5ecd6f301a659d925c6a35f7da88c36f9871-725x423-gif/ezgif.com-gif-maker.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. )If you want a more classic fast-food experience, you can drive through the one traditional lane or head inside the restaurant to order on a touchscreen or pick up a mobile order—but there’s no place to sit. Imagine this: After ordering a Mexican Pizza and a Baja Blast on your phone, you drive up to a screen at the front of one of four drive-thru lanes, scan a QR code, and have your order descend from the restaurant overhead through a tubular contraption. Franchisee Border Foods observed that drive-thru orders at its 230 locations jumped from up to 70% of total sales before Covid-19 to over 90% now. —JW Border Foods CEO Lee Engler told Axios, “We saw a lot of behavior change, and we don’t see (the old way) coming back.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/taco-bell-opens-futuristic-new-location-in-minnesota?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>QSR</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/taco-bell-opens-futuristic-new-location-in-minnesota?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:13 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>California court rules bees are legally fish again</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7d5ee284aa059916c1a0e00dab688fc0c3eb1ffc-892x494.jpg?rect=76,0,741,494&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The new classification protects bees—and other insects—under the California Endangered Species Act (CESA), and is the culmination of a four-year legal tussle between environmentalists and agriculture groups that has major consequences for farmers in the state. In 2020, a Sacramento County Superior Court sided with the ag groups and reversed the 2018 ruling. —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIn a ruling ripe for a Jay Leno monologue, a California court said last week that bees are legally fish. The court even ruled that anything without a backbone qualifies as fish: jellyfish, insects, and you when your mom guilts you into going on a family vacation. Section 45 of CESA defines fish as “... So in 2018, three environmental groups that were worried about the declining pollinator population in California found a workaround to expand the legal definition of fish to cover four species of endangered bees.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/california-court-rules-bees-are-legally-fish-again?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Environment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/california-court-rules-bees-are-legally-fish-again?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:13 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Target takes action to reduce massive inventory glut</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/81bad3bf9d739a27f8a06eae4baf83daced50a4c-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. And the data supports the theory that the American shopper is holding up just fine…for now: US consumer spending grew at the fastest clip in three months in April, when adjusting for inflation. What happened: In trying to solve one problem (Covid-related shortages), retailers created another (a surplus of the kinds of goods people don’t want to buy right now).</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/07/target-takes-action-to-reduce-massive-inventory-glut?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/07/target-takes-action-to-reduce-massive-inventory-glut?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:13 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Taco Bell opens futuristic new location in Minnesota</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-06-07/image-0e9a5ecd6f301a659d925c6a35f7da88c36f9871-725x423-gif/ezgif.com-gif-maker.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. )If you want a more classic fast-food experience, you can drive through the one traditional lane or head inside the restaurant to order on a touchscreen or pick up a mobile order—but there’s no place to sit. Imagine this: After ordering a Mexican Pizza and a Baja Blast on your phone, you drive up to a screen at the front of one of four drive-thru lanes, scan a QR code, and have your order descend from the restaurant overhead through a tubular contraption. Franchisee Border Foods observed that drive-thru orders at its 230 locations jumped from up to 70% of total sales before Covid-19 to over 90% now. —JW Border Foods CEO Lee Engler told Axios, “We saw a lot of behavior change, and we don't see (the old way) coming back.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/taco-bell-opens-futuristic-new-location-in-minnesota</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>QSR</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/taco-bell-opens-futuristic-new-location-in-minnesota</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:11 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>California court rules bees are legally fish again</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7d5ee284aa059916c1a0e00dab688fc0c3eb1ffc-892x494.jpg?rect=76,0,741,494&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The new classification protects bees—and other insects—under the California Endangered Species Act (CESA), and is the culmination of a four-year legal tussle between environmentalists and agriculture groups that has major consequences for farmers in the state. In 2020, a Sacramento County Superior Court sided with the ag groups and reversed the 2018 ruling. —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIn a ruling ripe for a Jay Leno monologue, a California court said last week that bees are legally fish. The court even ruled that anything without a backbone qualifies as fish: jellyfish, insects, and you when your mom guilts you into going on a family vacation. Section 45 of CESA defines fish as “... So in 2018, three environmental groups that were worried about the declining pollinator population in California found a workaround to expand the legal definition of fish to cover four species of endangered bees.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/california-court-rules-bees-are-legally-fish-again</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Environment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/california-court-rules-bees-are-legally-fish-again</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:26:10 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>

</channel>
</rss>
