<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <atom:link href="https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2022/04/21/users/1/web_requests/22/MorningBrew.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
 <atom:icon>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2022/04/21/favicon.ico</atom:icon>
 

 <title>MorningBrew as a feed</title>
 <description>This is a feed of recent MorningBrew articles published by Huginn</description>
 <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2022/04/21</link>
 <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 15:04:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
 <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 15:04:03 -0700</pubDate>
 <ttl>60</ttl>
 <item>
  <title>Key performance indicators: April 22</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/4c8851b21a9363fdad938565189c2c578f1a7490-2339x1081.png?rect=359,0,1622,1081&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/21/key-performance-indicators-april-22</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/21/key-performance-indicators-april-22</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 15:02:02 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>CNN+ shuts down less than a month after launch</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/67215888a77eea8359678e7325d46426e3bc4582-800x450.png?rect=63,0,675,450&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. After pulling the plug, he will likely bundle all of the company’s video offerings, including Discovery+ and HBO Max, into one app. Big picture: David Zaslav, the former CEO of Discovery and new boss of the post-merged Warner Bros. —MM But it failed to attract a big audience—fewer than 10,000 daily active users tuned into the service within the first two weeks, per CNBC. CNN+ rolled out on March 29 with big ambitions, having spent $300 million for big names like Alison Roman and Chris Wallace. Discovery said yesterday it’s shutting down the roughly three-week-old streaming service, CNN+.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/CNN-plus-shuts-down</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/CNN-plus-shuts-down</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 15:02:01 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>All eyes on the remaining Mariupol holdouts at the Azovstal plant</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/2e43ca515122796b608eee73956319c8078fb440-1024x622.jpg?rect=46,0,933,622&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The stories would have revealed that one of Kotick’s girlfriends filed a temporary restraining order against him, but a team of Facebook and Activision employees strategized to quash the reporting, according to WSJ. He’s putting up $21 billion of his own money. More than $25.5 billion of that comes through debt financing via Morgan Stanley Senior Funding and other partners. In a securities filing, Musk said he’s received $46.5 billion in commitments to help finance a potential tender offer to buy Twitter (he offered $43 billion). 🤑 Elon Musk says he’s got funding secured. Meta denies any wrongdoing by Sandberg. 💻 Sheryl Sandberg allegedly leaned on reporters.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/21/all-eyes-on-the-remaining-mariupol-holdouts-at-the-azovstal-plant</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/21/all-eyes-on-the-remaining-mariupol-holdouts-at-the-azovstal-plant</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 15:02:01 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>US air pollution levels have risen sharply: Study</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/049b3d3c3358e902999ab0ec2553917ada2eb183-1000x667.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. And, according to the study, people of color are disproportionately affected by that pollution: They are nearly four times more likely than white people to live in a county with poor air quality. The annual State of the Air report found that 63 million people lived in counties exposed to dangerous levels of deadly particulate matter pollution this year—9 million more people than the previous year. —MK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeAfter a nearly two-decadelong decline, US pollution levels have risen sharply over the past five years, according to a new report by the American Lung Association. In fact, more than 137 million Americans live in areas with poor air quality.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/air-pollution-rise-study</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Environment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/air-pollution-rise-study</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 15:02:01 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Florida legislature passes bill to revoke Disney World’s special tax district</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/37946f7477d6058dace1d612a7d22dce9cbd9a67-569x500.png?rect=0,60,569,379&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Considering there was no political discussion around Disney World’s special tax status until very recently, the move is widely seen as retaliation for Disney’s criticism of a Florida law that restricts discussion of gender identity and sexual orientation in some classrooms. Under the deal it worked out with Florida, Disney is allowed to build new structures without local approval and is exempted from certain environmental and wastewater codes. Disney’s been operating the special administrative zone, called the Reedy Creek Improvement District, for 55 years. David Ramba, executive director of the Florida Association of Special Districts, told CNBC that he hasn’t seen any special districts get dissolved that didn’t want to be dissolved, not to mention one run by a $222 billion corporation. —NF css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/21/florida-legislature-passes-bill-to-revoke-disney-world-s-special-tax-district</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/21/florida-legislature-passes-bill-to-revoke-disney-world-s-special-tax-district</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 14:46:58 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key performance indicators: April 21</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7ebfd3317fde7f77094e6526eb340bd58eedfb42-1024x577.jpg?rect=79,0,866,577&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Entrepreneur Oleg Tinkov blasted his country’s invasion of Ukraine in an Instagram post, becoming one of the few members of the Russian elite to directly criticize Putin’s invasion.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/20/key-performance-indicators-april-21?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/20/key-performance-indicators-april-21?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:31:07 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Decadal survey declares Uranus mission a priority</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/9947af341303f433d7c2abdca48bb33bc458e934-1400x700.png?rect=175,0,1050,700&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. One asteroid, Apophis, that will zoom close to Earth in 2029 might be the leading lady. The survey recommended that NASA try a dress rehearsal for defending us from space rocks by beefing up planetary defense. —MM</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/Decadal-survey-declared-Uranus-mission-priority?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Space</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/Decadal-survey-declared-Uranus-mission-priority?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:31:06 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Elon Musk hints at tender offer for Twitter</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-04-20/image-d7c13611292dd5884106b8aa82d5f6f203e92a48-480x269-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. So even if he makes a tender offer, he won’t be able to buy the shares he offers to snatch up. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. In other words, shareholders are given the option to cash out so that one individual or company can take over. Unless…Twitter’s board decides to crush its poison pill, which they might consider doing if the majority of shareholders chooses to accept Musk’s tender offer. —JW If they were to keep the poison pill in place in that scenario, they’d risk reinforcing a narrative Musk has been pushing that Twitter’s board isn’t acting in shareholders’ best interests. Scott Fitzgerald’s novel Tender Is the Night and, simultaneously, his intention to make a “tender offer” for Twitter. Okay but…What is a tender offer?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/elon-musk-twitter-tender-offer?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Social Media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/elon-musk-twitter-tender-offer?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:31:06 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Wimbledon bans players from Russia and Belarus from competing</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/39b57d5d4d6e0118c1e9c97c387f3118b66b0291-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. But according to posts about the event, poor planning on Revolve’s part led to attendees being stranded in the desert heat while waiting for shuttles. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Other Apple workers at a store in NYC said this weekend that they were collecting signatures to form a union, in the hopes of locking down a $30 minimum wage and better benefits. The iconic British tennis tournament held during the summer has banned players from both countries, which includes men’s world No. 2 Daniil Medvedev of Russia and women’s No. 4 Aryna Sabalenka of Belarus. 🎉 Revolve responds to festival fail.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/20/atlanta-apple-store-workers-file-for-first-ever-union?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde,</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/20/atlanta-apple-store-workers-file-for-first-ever-union?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:31:05 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Netflix stock collapses 36% in a warning to the streaming industry</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/36617858a2fd464d86bd6b07437d559389c58b90-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. But one does not simply lose more than one-third of your market value without inviting existential doubts about your business model. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. Given all that competition (not to mention a content budget of $17 billion annually), Netflix needs to continuously release hit TV shows like Bridgerton and Squid Game to attract and retain its customer base.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/20/netflix-stock-collapses?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/20/netflix-stock-collapses?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:31:05 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key performance indicators</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-15f02c17259d8488351f7dac69e5d74803755fcf-480x354-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Green’s comp is good for No. 1 among the 358 S&amp;P 500 companies that have disclosed 2021 pay for their CEOs, the WSJ reported. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeStat: Jeff Green, the CEO of ad tech company Trade Desk, received a pay package last year that was valued at $835 million. Delta Air Lines got blasted by health experts after its statement announcing the end of its mask mandate concluded that Covid-19 amounted to an “ordinary seasonal virus,” which is not the case. (Washington Post) Maybe if you’re an airline…don’t dip your toes into epidemiology?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/19/key-performance-indicators?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/19/key-performance-indicators?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:31:03 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Cannabis prices drop, despite inflation pressures</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/364cd152f7d968f3952efdc527509b0fea93753f-1000x667.png?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. That’s according to Headset, a cannabis analytics company that tracked sales in California, Colorado, Michigan, Nevada, Oregon, and Washington—where prices for the same products can vary wildly. In Colorado, the price of a pound of marijuana is $799, near its lowest level on record, per the state’s Department of Revenue. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeWhile other products have taken a hit from inflation, cannabis has passed. —JW Why? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Zoom out: It’s not that cannabis isn’t as affected by the same pressures causing inflation as other industries. Since cannabis isn’t legal at the federal level, supply and demand at the state level has a greater influence on its price than on those of federally legal staples like gas, milk, and eggs. In fact, cannabis is relatively cheap across the board.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/cannabis-prices-drop-despite-inflation?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/cannabis-prices-drop-despite-inflation?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:31:03 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Florida Gov. DeSantis wants to revoke Disney’s special district</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7a36c03e8538762d2b43e5dc76cf0bdc12abec83-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. On Tuesday, DeSantis asked state lawmakers to consider revoking Disney World’s special district. —MK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! FYI no, Disney World’s special district does not refer to the restaurant where they sell the massive turkey legs—it’s an administrative zone called the Reedy Creek Improvement District.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/Ron-DeSantis-disney-dont-say-gay?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Government</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/Ron-DeSantis-disney-dont-say-gay?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:31:03 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Netflix stock plunges after reporting a subscriber loss</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-04-19/image-cc923a97c025c7a27210e0f0028a8588aacebce0-480x270-gif/giphy(3).webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/19/netflix-stock-plunges-after-reporting-a-subscriber-loss?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/19/netflix-stock-plunges-after-reporting-a-subscriber-loss?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:31:03 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>After judge drops federal transportation mask mandate, a confusing new era dawns</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/114b1349e8cbc849365a5d0ffab7d4173657a525-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Then, US airlines rushed to drop their mask requirements faster than a guy in Group D lines up while first class is boarding. . Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Masks had become a major frustration for airlines, which had been lobbying to end the mandate for months. Same in Philadelphia, where a new indoor mask mandate just took effect. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIt’s been more than 36 hours since a Florida judge abruptly overturned the CDC’s federal mask mandate for transportation, and Americans are still working out the implications of that…about-face. 🙄Here’s what you need to know:In the hours after the ruling came down, the Transportation Security Administration (TSA) said it would stop enforcing the mandate on public transportation and planes. —NF</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/19/after-judge-drops-federal-transportation-mask-mandate-a-confusing-new-era-dawns?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Covid</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/19/after-judge-drops-federal-transportation-mask-mandate-a-confusing-new-era-dawns?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:31:02 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key performance indicators: February 23</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-02-22/image-5985abe5da6f46f3fad0c9313d36d2a115802f4e-432x250-gif/office.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Caesars CEO Tom Reeg told investors that the company will pull back its ad spend after hitting its customer acquisition goals for its sports betting app faster than expected. (Washington Post) Rounding out the five most valuable shows based on their streaming deals are Seinfeld ($361,000 per episode), Friends ($360,000), The Big Bang Theory ($357,000), and South Park ($348,000). To put that in terms Michael Scott would understand, Peacock paid Universal $498,000/episode for The Office in a five-year deal back in 2019.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/22/key-performance-indicators-february-23?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/22/key-performance-indicators-february-23?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:31:01 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Coinbase’s CEO claims no agency created its Super Bowl ad</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/8470eca6ac76b16ee03b606b0a5bd91cb75021a8-632x418.png?rect=3,0,627,418&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. In a self-congratulatory Twitter thread on Sunday, Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong boasted that the crypto platform turned down an agency’s ideas for the ad before brainstorming its own, because “No ad agency would have done this ad.” Coinbase’s 60-second spot—which featured a QR code that drove so much traffic that the app crashed—became the center of a squabble about which geniuses came up with the ad: Coinbase or the ad agencies it worked with. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeNearly two weeks after the Super Bowl, social media’s still buzzing about one of the ads…but the vibe has shifted. Sign up for Marketing Brew. —JWWant more marketing news? He and Rouch tweeted that the partnership was so “seamless” that Armstrong didn’t realize.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/coinbase-super-bowl-ad?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Marketing</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/coinbase-super-bowl-ad?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:31:01 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>US women’s soccer team reaches $24 million equal pay settlement with US Soccer</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/c8ce9162ea0a9269b141c0c775cd03e57aead496-1024x660.jpg?rect=17,0,990,660&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The deal: The 61 women included in the deal will receive $22 million in back pay—an acknowledgment that they were underpaid compared to the men’s team.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/us-womens-soccer-24-million-equal-pay-settlement?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Labor</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/us-womens-soccer-24-million-equal-pay-settlement?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:31:00 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>US Covid cases fall 90% from their January peak</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-02-22/image-a27715858cdc1f2e3412e3d2e9b65fb7ab780d3d-480x366-gif/plummet.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/22/us-covid-cases-fall-90-from-their-january-peak?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/22/us-covid-cases-fall-90-from-their-january-peak?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:31:00 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key performance indicators: February 22</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/426653d93332fbb1b33b1a72b77262390ac7d677-960x720.jpg?rect=0,40,960,640&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. (The New Republic) css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! A typical black bear in the western US weighs 100–300 lbs.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/21/key-performance-indicators-february-22?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/21/key-performance-indicators-february-22?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:59 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>FTC data shows ‘The Tinder Swindler’ is more common than you’d think</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/f48615c4cafbfc0f64a66327db6084b9c877f05e-1024x924.jpg?rect=0,120,1024,683&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. New data released by the FTC reveals that romance scams reached an all-time high in 2021, up nearly 80% from 2020. The biggest romance scam losses were paid out in crypto—$139 million in 2021. It’s a steep jump from 2017, when losses from such scams totaled $87 million. —MK That stat might explain why The Tinder Swindler, Netflix’s latest true-crime doc about a man accused of conning women on Tinder out of $10 million, has led the global Netflix charts since it debuted on February 2. 56,000 romance scams were reported to the FTC in 2021. According to the FTC, people have lost $1.3 billion to romance scams in the last five years—$547 million of which came (or left) in 2021. Even screentime champions in the 18–29 bracket reported 10x the amount of scams from 2017 to 2021.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/tinder-swindler-ftc-data-romance-scams?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Data privacy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/tinder-swindler-ftc-data-romance-scams?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:59 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Global health visionary Dr. Paul Farmer dies at 62</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/976c6ff6fb3547eea2e4046cb7e0d6f83e6486b6-1200x799.webp?rect=1,0,1199,799&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Also…you can learn more about Farmer in the 2017 documentary Bending the Arc.—MM Farmer, whose mission was to bring high-quality health care to low-income nations, created hospitals in Rwanda and Haiti and co-founded the global nonprofit Partners in Health. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeHarvard Medical School professor, anthropologist, and global health advocate Dr. Paul Farmer unexpectedly died in his sleep in Rwanda at 62. Tracy Kidder, the author of a book about Farmer’s inspirational work, Mountains Beyond Mountains, said Farmer “was the kind of person whose example can irritate you by making you feel you’ve never done anything as important, and yet, in his presence, those kinds of feelings tended to vanish.” In addition to his nonprofit, Farmer brought livesaving HIV drugs to Haiti, raised millions of dollars for community health care facilities around the world, wrote 12 books, and won a number of awards, including the $1 million Berggruen Prize in 2020 for reshaping our understanding of “what it means to treat health as a human right.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/global-health-visionary-dr-paul-farmer-dies-at-62?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>International</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/global-health-visionary-dr-paul-farmer-dies-at-62?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:59 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Trump’s social media app gets off to a hot, but bumpy, start</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/0c78c27f7e90ebc7638bdfc0ad1580d06a6198b6-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Truth Social, led by former Republican Rep. Devin Nunes, is one of several right-learning social apps that have launched in recent years, along with Gettr, Parler, and the more established Rumble. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/21/trump-s-social-media-app-gets-off-to-a-hot-but-bumpy-start?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/21/trump-s-social-media-app-gets-off-to-a-hot-but-bumpy-start?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:58 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Putin’s Fortress Russia may be no match for the ‘mother of all sanctions’</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/31cfba9e7d52e81a4f19d1e9dcc920d6298e26f7-1024x685.jpg?rect=0,1,1024,683&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. It built its own financial messaging system in case it gets blocked from the one used around the world, called SWIFT. Geopolitical experts say that the types of sanctions being prepared, which could block Russia from importing critical tech materials or cut off Russian banks from accessing the US dollar, will be enough to overcome Putin’s defenses and cause significant and immediate damage to the Russian economy. And investors are preparing for the worst: Russia’s benchmark stock index closed down 11% yesterday for its biggest single-day drop since Russia’s annexation of Crimea in 2014. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeAs Russia eyes moving troops further into Ukraine, Western leaders are readying economic sanctions to punish Vladimir Putin for his aggression. US lawmakers have pledged to unleash the “mother of all sanctions” in the event of a Russian invasion, and UK Prime Minister Boris Johnson suggested on Sunday that the sanctions will include cutting off Russian companies from using US dollars and British pounds, hitting them “very, very hard.” Big picture: Despite the sanction-proofing campaign, Putin’s Fortress Russia is not impenetrable. Building Fortress RussiaIf you want to sanction-proof your economy, the first place to start is padding your foreign exchange reserves, which are stockpiles of foreign currencies held by your central bank. —NF So sanctions hitting Russia’s energy sector could boomerang back to hurt the West and destabilize global energy markets.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/21/putin-s-fortress-russia-may-be-no-match-for-the-mother-of-all-sanctions?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>International</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/21/putin-s-fortress-russia-may-be-no-match-for-the-mother-of-all-sanctions?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:58 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key performance indicators: February 21</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/07db2092e7b152f0b26b0ca2b16af6f1758e72dd-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Could it be running an app store?” (Full Stack Economics) css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/20/key-performance-indicators-february-21?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/20/key-performance-indicators-february-21?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:57 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The week ahead: February 21</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-b359a998a1b4dcbf0398a92518c4845fccb1b110-440x300-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Music releases: Kanye West drops Donda 2 on the Stem Player on Tuesday, and Avril Lavigne’s new album comes out on Friday. With arctic air moving in, more than 70% of Americans in the Lower 48 states will experience below-freezing temps, and over 15 million will see below-zero temps. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Trump’s back on social media: Truth Social, former President Trump’s social media venture, could launch on the App Store today, per Reuters.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/20/the-week-ahead-february-21?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/20/the-week-ahead-february-21?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:57 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Why is Norway so dang good at the Winter Olympics?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/04b3be67d14b5996803ba0bab16e4ecf561de1d5-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Golfer Viktor Hovland and tennis player Casper Ruud are both in the top 10 of their sports globally, while Magnus Carlsen has been ranked No. 1 in chess since 2011. Instead of locking children into high-stakes competitions as youngsters, Norway invites them to dabble in a variety of sports with only one goal: have fun. Big picture: While Norway excels at winter sports, it also punches above its weight in other athletic disciplines.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/20/why-is-norway-so-dang-good-at-the-winter-olympics?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/20/why-is-norway-so-dang-good-at-the-winter-olympics?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:57 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>US leaders say Putin has already decided to invade Ukraine</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/3765dc1d764877a87f477a7acf14cceac007cfc5-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. A whistleblower leaked data on more than 18,000 Credit Suisse accounts, exposing how the Swiss bank had a list of shady clients, including alleged human rights abusers, sanctioned businessmen, and relatives of dictators. Police cleared out the remaining protesters and towed the trucks that had been blockading downtown Ottawa for three weeks. 🇨🇦 The occupation of Ottawa is over. The move, brokered by French President Emmanuel Macron, is a last-ditch diplomatic effort to avert a war that US leaders say is imminent. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}Subscribe🤝🏿 Biden sends a gCal invite: President Biden has agreed “in principle” to meet with Russian President Vladimir Putin if Putin has not already invaded Ukraine.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/20/us-leaders-say-putin-has-already-decided-to-invade-ukraine?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/20/us-leaders-say-putin-has-already-decided-to-invade-ukraine?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:56 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Carl Icahn wages unusual proxy battle with McDonald's over pork sourcing</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/b73d80d16fbaf255dd3c7752fbb97934b53ef5b5-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. “Animals are one of the things I feel really emotional about,” he told the WSJ. This story begins a decade ago, when, after getting an earful from Icahn and the Humane Society, McDonald’s announced that it would only buy pork from suppliers that stopped using gestation crates (tiny stalls) to hold pregnant pigs by 2022.10 years later, Icahn is arguing that the company has both a) shifted the goalposts and b) hasn’t moved fast enough. But Icahn’s approach with McDonald’s is very different. Icahn isn’t going about this in the typical wayKnown as the OG “corporate raider,” Icahn popularized the strategy of activist investing. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeLast Tuesday, HBO premiered a documentary on the life of Carl Icahn called Icahn: The Restless Billionaire, and just a few days later he is proving them correct. McDonald’s suppliers only move pigs out of gestation crates once they’re confirmed pregnant, which could be weeks into their 16-week pregnancies, according to Icahn. He’s not arguing that the company is undervalued because of incompetent leaders, just that it’s being unethical.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/20/carl-icahn-wages-unusual-proxy-battle-with-mcdonald-s-over-pork-sourcing?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Food</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/20/carl-icahn-wages-unusual-proxy-battle-with-mcdonald-s-over-pork-sourcing?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:56 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The infrastructure bill’s funding for wildlife crossings will save millions of animal lives</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/3c52707e571aebf6a42d9ece5a2b8cc17f68de63-1024x684.jpg?rect=0,0,1024,683&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. A Wyoming crossing built for pronghorn migration led to a 70% reduction in wildlife–vehicle collisions. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Something that’s been proven to help: wildlife crossings—bridges, underpasses, and tunnels built specifically for animals to cross major roadways. It’s the largest investment Congress has made in such projects, and environmentalists and transportation specialists alike are relieved, because…It’s pretty rough out there:Every year, there are an estimated 1 to 2 million collisions between cars and large animals in the US. 13 bears were struck and killed along just a 108-mile stretch of Highway 395 in California in 2021, the most significant peak of fatalities since records began in 2002. —MK Why? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Arizona wildlife crossings are associated with a 90% drop in collisions in a stretch utilized by migrating elk.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/wildlife-crossings-infrastructure-bill?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Environment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/wildlife-crossings-infrastructure-bill?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:55 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Make it work: What to do when you get ghosted while applying for a job?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7b6de1bb891bb0dd9e289abb0a591582a5da30e6-1503x603.png?rect=299,0,905,603&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. ) of surveyed applicants have been left on read by a prospective employer. I was asked to go through five rounds of interviews, only to get the worst possible response: none (even after following up with their recruiter). css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. What do you do when a company ghosts you with no explanation?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/18/make-it-work-what-to-do-when-you-get-ghosted-while-applying-for-a-job?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Shane Loughnane</author>
  <categories>Work life</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/18/make-it-work-what-to-do-when-you-get-ghosted-while-applying-for-a-job?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:54 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Icebreakers with…Hinge CEO Justin McLeod</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/5da2409d573dca28c60259ae16b78646f6e16766-3078x2308.jpg?rect=0,128,3078,2052&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Obviously privacy is a huge thing for us and we have to make sure that we keep all of our users’ data private. So one of those was the move to online dating. And it’s interactive, which is really effective in getting people to start a conversation. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIn light of the West Elm Caleb drama and more instances of people sharing uncensored dating app profiles on TikTok and social media, what responsibility do dating apps have to protect users' privacy? I think people also just got more thoughtful and dated with more intention. People have talked about their dating lives forever, and people will continue to talk about their dating lives. I think it’s accelerated some trends that were happening in dating already. Biggest risk I’ve ever taken…A tie between flying to Switzerland to ask my college girlfriend to call off her wedding and move back to America with me and deciding to reboot Hinge and start over. I think my peak weirdness is my obsession with ecstatic dance. Hinge added audio prompts in October; why do you think they were so popular? [The pandemic] made a lot of people reflect on their lives and think about what really mattered to them. And as a result, people got more intentional with their relationships, which I think made Hinge an especially attractive option for people. So it's about finding that sweet spot where you're giving people enough information that they can really get a sense of who you are, but not scaring people away from doing it. The other thing is people just want to be more sure before they meet up with someone in person. He launched the first version of the dating app Hinge in 2011 but, after a rocky few years, decided to scrap it and start over in 2015.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/icebreakers-with-hinge-ceo-justin-mcleod?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Q&amp;A</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/icebreakers-with-hinge-ceo-justin-mcleod?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:53 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Stock watch: February 20</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/b02f2eaf7e25e6c7499411a5770cab9fcd899d9c-1500x2000.png?rect=0,500,1500,1000&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/18/stock-watch-february-20?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Culture</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/18/stock-watch-february-20?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:52 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Saturday sketch: Winter Olympic sports that deserved more love</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d9de1b599a902e0a04726ba7d5a0814dffc40bf4-1300x1300.png?rect=0,216,1300,867&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/18/saturday-sketch-winter-olympic-sports-that-deserved-more-love?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/18/saturday-sketch-winter-olympic-sports-that-deserved-more-love?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:52 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key performance indicators: February 19</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/5daa2a2f32a1b036763df32f3d25a5f2d2273d0c-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. ) As a travel CEO, he has certain reasons to be bullish on the sector, but the data backs him up: US travel and tourism is expected to jump by 6.2% over pre-pandemic levels this year, per the World Travel &amp; Tourism Council. What made the stream so thrilling was that pilots were contending with historically intense winds generated by Eunice, one of the worst storms the UK has experienced in three decades. (New York Times) Expedia CEO Peter Kern told Bloomberg that despite higher prices, “I think people are willing to pay whatever the hell it takes to get away and go to a place they want to go.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/18/key-performance-indicators-february-19?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/18/key-performance-indicators-february-19?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:52 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Kanye West will release ‘Donda 2’ exclusively on Stem Player</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/0813ec977066ceb4009b6d858f59f2ef3f052d87-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. , and layer on effects. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/18/kanye-west-will-release-donda-2-exclusively-on-stem-player?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/18/kanye-west-will-release-donda-2-exclusively-on-stem-player?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:52 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Fed passes ban on individual stock, bond, and crypto trades</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-02-18/image-9835061582e706e4e5b75c72d657f684069a3c79-500x282-gif/hobby.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The Fed approved rules yesterday that ban regional bank presidents and other senior Fed officials from trading individual stocks, bonds, and crypto. —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! The rule change comes in response to a stock trading controversy that’s dented the Fed’s reputation.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/fed-passes-ban-on-individual-stock-bond-crypto-trades?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Fed</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/fed-passes-ban-on-individual-stock-bond-crypto-trades?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:51 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>4,000 cars adrift at sea after cargo ship fire</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/13d7975c78147a61347b71b022d0bdb677d0bf18-936x624.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The weeklong interruption began after the USDA said one of its safety inspectors was threatened over the phone (a Washington Post source said the inspector had found an illegal shipment). Over 90% of US avocados came from Mexico last year, so the fruit could have experienced a serious price jump if the ban lasted longer—and its price is already at record highs. NBC Olympics host Mike Tirico also delivered pointed criticism, saying the adults in the room “failed to protect” Valieva during this whole ordeal.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/4000-cars-adrift-at-sea-after-cargo-ship-fire?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>International</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/4000-cars-adrift-at-sea-after-cargo-ship-fire?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:51 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Roku shares dive amid broader crash of pandemic darlings</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-02-18/image-24d8ffe59425c21b8e666a141580b2d8aaf09310-350x194-gif/ezgif.com-gif-maker(1).webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Their conviction that consumer behavior would be forever changed by Covid led them to make poor decisions that dented future prospects. One might even suggest that the companies billed as pandemic winners are not only not winners, they are also losers. 2,800 job cuts, an 82% stock plunge, and one CEO later, it decided to scrap that idea. Roku is one of many companies whose epic rise in 2020 has been overshadowed by an equally epic collapse in the last year:Shopify, which represented the Covid e-commerce boom, is down 62% from its peak.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/18/roku-shares-dive-amid-broader-crash-of-pandemic-darlings?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Stocks</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/18/roku-shares-dive-amid-broader-crash-of-pandemic-darlings?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:50 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key performance indicators: February 18</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/c8d635384041917139ce957f4169982a43868783-1024x677.jpg?rect=4,0,1016,677&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. (Eater) While female participation in the Saudi workforce has nearly doubled in the last five years due to relaxed restrictions, women still need a male relative’s approval for standard activities like opening a bank account or getting married. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/17/key-performance-indicators-february-18?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/02/17/key-performance-indicators-february-18?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:30:49 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>

</channel>
</rss>
