<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <atom:link href="https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2022/06/07/users/1/web_requests/22/MorningBrew.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
 <atom:icon>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2022/06/07/favicon.ico</atom:icon>
 

 <title>MorningBrew as a feed</title>
 <description>This is a feed of recent MorningBrew articles published by Huginn</description>
 <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2022/06/07</link>
 <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:03:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
 <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:03:45 -0700</pubDate>
 <ttl>60</ttl>
 <item>
  <title>Axon pumps the brakes on taser drone it said could take down mass shooters</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/5b996d532c5d3c0c390f826e3681574cf5a63607-1524x852.png?rect=123,0,1278,852&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The hard pivot comes after Axon founder and CEO Rick Smith announced last week that the security company would start development of drones that could be operated by first responders and potentially used in schools to avoid another shooting like the recent one in Uvalde, Texas. —MM What changed? Axon’s ethics board, a group of experts in tech, privacy, and policing, sparred publicly with Smith over the idea, arguing that the drones could be used to over-police communities of color. In 2016, Smith even wrote a companion graphic novel exploring how the drone could stop a shooter. Nine members resigned yesterday over the drone plan.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/axon-pumps-brakes-on-taser-drone?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/axon-pumps-brakes-on-taser-drone?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:01:44 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Elon Musk tries to squirm out of Twitter deal</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/1e88ace89ad33182573bd0d97c83c87607e1f66c-1290x860.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Big picture: One reason for Musk’s fixation with bots might be that he encounters them far more than the average Twitter user—or even the average celebrity. If it gets tired of Musk’s lollygagging, Twitter could eventually sue to compel Musk to go through with the deal. In Musk’s most significant play yet to pull out of the deal, his lawyer sent a letter to Twitter accusing the company of denying Musk’s requests for more information about the number of fake and spam accounts on the platform. —NF Musk has repeatedly argued that Twitter has a much bigger bot problem than it discloses, and is using that as justification to scuttle (or potentially renegotiate) his $44 billion purchase. Twitter responded to Musk’s letter with a statement along the lines of, “No take-backs, pal.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/06/elon-musk-tries-out-of-twitter-deal?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/06/elon-musk-tries-out-of-twitter-deal?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:01:44 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The UK launched a major test of the 4-day workweek</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/c02f91c79600ff85f88545dfb9f8da5ee5b30322-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. In January, there were just 1,700 jobs advertising a four-day workweek in the US for every 1 million posted. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Bottom line: For all the notable trials and tests of a shorter workweek, finding a job that actually implements one is extremely rare. Trials of lighter work schedules haven’t always been successful for both employees and employers, though: A two-year trial of a six-hour workday in one of Sweden’s largest cities in 2017 left workers happier, healthier, and more productive, but the practice was deemed too expensive due to the new hires needed to fill gaps in time. More than 3,300 workers will participate in the trial, making it the largest test of the four-day workweek. A six-month program that began in the UK on Monday will test the effects of the four-day workweek on thousands of workers across 70 companies. —MK But, if you’re one of the 92% of US employees who are into the idea and don’t want to wait for trial results, you may want to consider moving to France, where a 35-hour workweek cap has been the law since 2000. The results of the trial will be announced sometime in 2023. Several industries will be involved, including banking, health care, marketing, and retail—and through interviews, surveys, and internal productivity measures, researchers will determine if we have all been clocking in on Fridays for our whole adult lives for absolutely no reason.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/4-day-workweek-UK-trial?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Labor</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/4-day-workweek-UK-trial?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:01:43 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Elon Musk tries to squirm out of Twitter deal</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/1e88ace89ad33182573bd0d97c83c87607e1f66c-1290x860.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Big picture: One reason for Musk’s fixation with bots might be that he encounters them far more than the average Twitter user—or even the average celebrity. If it gets tired of Musk’s lollygagging, Twitter could eventually sue to compel Musk to go through with the deal. In Musk’s most significant play yet to pull out of the deal, his lawyer sent a letter to Twitter accusing the company of denying Musk’s requests for more information about the number of fake and spam accounts on the platform. —NF Musk has repeatedly argued that Twitter has a much bigger bot problem than it discloses, and is using that as justification to scuttle (or potentially renegotiate) his $44 billion purchase. Twitter responded to Musk’s letter with a statement along the lines of, “No take-backs, pal.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/06/elon-musk-tries-out-of-twitter-deal</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/06/elon-musk-tries-out-of-twitter-deal</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 15:11:36 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Axon pumps the brakes on taser drone it said could take down mass shooters</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/15a5864a9dc948189ef98e0bcf0aa95757d61d8f-2100x1200.jpg?rect=150,0,1800,1200&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The hard pivot comes after Axon founder and CEO Rick Smith announced last week that the security company would start development of drones that could be operated by first responders and potentially used in schools to avoid another shooting like the recent one in Uvalde, Texas. The plan, one of several “maybe add more weapons?” —MM What changed? The board, a group of experts in tech, privacy, and policing, sparred publicly with Smith over the idea, arguing that the drones could be used to over-police communities of color. -type solutions to mass shootings, caused nine members of the company’s ethics board to resign yesterday.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/axon-pumps-brakes-on-taser-drone</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/axon-pumps-brakes-on-taser-drone</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 15:11:36 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The UK launched a major test of the 4-day workweek</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/c02f91c79600ff85f88545dfb9f8da5ee5b30322-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. In January, there were just 1,700 jobs advertising a four-day workweek in the US for every 1 million posted. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Trials of lighter work schedules haven’t always been successful for both employees and employers, though: A two-year trial of a six-hour workday in one of Sweden’s largest cities in 2017 left workers happier, healthier, and more productive, but the practice was deemed too expensive due to the new hires needed to fill gaps in time. More than 3,300 workers will participate in the trial, making it the largest test of the four-day workweek. A six-month program that began in the UK on Monday will test the effects of the four-day workweek on thousands of workers across 70 companies. —MK But, if you’re one of the 92% of US employees who are into the idea and don’t want to wait for trial results, you may want to consider moving to France, where a 35-hour workweek cap has been the law since 2000. 🤞Fingers crossed🤞The concept of a four-day workweek is decades-old, but legitimate tests of it are somewhat recent. The results of the trial will be announced sometime in 2023. Several industries will be involved, including banking, health care, marketing, finance, and retail—and through interviews, surveys, and internal productivity measures, researchers will determine if we have all been clocking in on Fridays for our whole adult lives for absolutely no reason.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/4-day-workweek-UK-trial</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Labor</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/4-day-workweek-UK-trial</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 14:56:42 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>"It ain't rocket science": How one FoodToker is making a career as a content creator</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/1b91e7c4181dca8717c0ae9c5d148da3d7440235-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Today’s dish is shrimp tempura udon and food content creator H Woo Lee is explaining how to make it from scratch in a behind-the-scenes video. Lee says he and TikToker Sam Way were the first ones to create ASMR cooking videos for TikTok.Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. His videos are relaxing and stylish, concealing the hours of work he puts into creating TikToks for his 1 million followers. No one can taste my food,” Lee said. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. Like a lot of food influencers, Lee isn’t a professional chef. His ultimate goal is to open a restaurant one day so his fans can finally taste his food. “There’s only one way for anyone to differentiate themselves. It’s like a miniature store,” Kar Brulhart, a creator strategist said. “In-person dining, and like being a chef,” Lee said, “that’s my craft.” The 23 year old’s main channel has 92.6 million subscribers and makes at least $3 million per month from YouTube ads alone, per the analytics service SocialBlade. Creators like Lee are ditching the Instagram filters, highly posed pictures, and stylized lattes for content that feels more authentic. Lee compares being a content creator to being an Uber driver: He has the freedom to set his own work schedule, which is what he wanted for himself. These days successful creators are very knowledgeable in their respective fields while coming across as down to earth, but they deliver professional-grade content that is strategically planned and carefully edited, like Lee’s cooking videos. The rise of TikTok stars makes mastery of the app seem like an easy, glamorous, and highly rewarding side hustle, but for most creators, like Lee, that’s simply not true. “There’s so many creators coming into this space now,” Lee explained to Morning Brew. As a full-time creator, Lee makes ASMR-style videos (or to get technical: Autonomous Sensory Meridian) that feature elaborate dishes, like prosciutto arugula pizza and Peking duck, to stand out from his TikTok competitors. But first, he needs to continue producing good food and even better content until Gordon Ramsay comes knocking. It’s a laborious process that, for TikTok, was edited into a tidy 60-second video emphasizing the sounds of his kitchen: the boil of the broth, the sizzle of cooking oil, and Lee’s slurps as he eats his final product. He’s not just cooking intricate meals—he’s also his own planner, cameraman, video editor, and social media manager. His very first viral video had 10.6 millions of views, but even after being a full-time creator for almost a year and half, he still can’t recreate the recipe to that success every time.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/05/it-ain-t-rocket-science-how-one-foodtoker-is-making-a-career-as-a-content-creator</link>
  <author>Sherry Qin</author>
  <categories>Social Media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/05/it-ain-t-rocket-science-how-one-foodtoker-is-making-a-career-as-a-content-creator</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 10:01:55 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The inglorious return of cheese rolling</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/872c7320d9abf27b96a9c29be99d52e1e0767f65-1024x532.jpg?rect=113,0,798,532&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. This year that glory belonged to Chris Anderson, the Joey Chestnut of extreme cheese rolling. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeMillennials have done crazy things for a cheese board, but they’ve got nothing on the “athletes” who competed in this weekend’s cheese rolling extreme sporting event in England. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! The more you know: The centuries-old cheese rolling event is thought to have originated from a pagan festival celebrating the onset of spring. It was Anderson’s 23rd cheese title—but also his last.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/05/the-inglorious-return-of-cheese-rolling?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/05/the-inglorious-return-of-cheese-rolling?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:01:43 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>New York moves to put a moratorium on some bitcoin mining permits</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/2d15b8a7bdedc0e7961e65cd26d92a895ed1f9c5-6000x4200.jpg?rect=0,100,6000,4000&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. New York’s state Senate passed a bill on Friday that would ban new permits across the state for bitcoin mining facilities that use carbon-based power. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeUpstate New York offers a wonderful range of activities, from hiking in the Adirondacks to inhaling a garbage plate in Rochester.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/05/new-york-moratorium-bitcoin-mining?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/05/new-york-moratorium-bitcoin-mining?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:01:43 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Apple prepares for a world after smartphones</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-42cc771ffc4130746e9caadcb5c38d8cbbe9b220-480x269-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. What we know about Apple’s AR and VR playZuck’s obsession with the metaverse gets all the headlines, but Apple CEO Tim Cook has been hyping up mixed reality—the mashup of physical and virtual words—for at least six years. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. And that underlying computing platform is really what Apple wants to get right before its headset launch. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/05/apple-prepares-for-a-world-after-smartphones?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/05/apple-prepares-for-a-world-after-smartphones?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:01:42 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The inglorious return of cheese rolling</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/872c7320d9abf27b96a9c29be99d52e1e0767f65-1024x532.jpg?rect=113,0,798,532&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. This year the glory belonged to Chris Anderson, the Joey Chestnut of extreme cheese rolling. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeMillennials have done crazy things for a cheese board, but they’ve got nothing on the “athletes” who competed in this weekend’s cheese rolling extreme sporting event in England. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! The more you know: The centuries-old cheese rolling festival is thought to have originated from a pagan festival celebrating the onset of spring. It was Anderson’s 23rd cheese title—but also his last.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/05/the-inglorious-return-of-cheese-rolling</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/05/the-inglorious-return-of-cheese-rolling</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 15:36:42 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>New York moves to put a moratorium on some bitcoin mining permits</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/2d15b8a7bdedc0e7961e65cd26d92a895ed1f9c5-6000x4200.jpg?rect=0,100,6000,4000&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. New York’s state Senate passed a bill on Friday that would ban new permits across the state for bitcoin mining facilities that use carbon-based power. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeUpstate New York offers a wonderful range of activities, from hiking in the Adirondacks to inhaling a garbage plate in Rochester.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/05/new-york-moratorium-bitcoin-mining</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/05/new-york-moratorium-bitcoin-mining</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 15:36:42 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Apple prepares for a world after smartphones</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-42cc771ffc4130746e9caadcb5c38d8cbbe9b220-480x269-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. What we know about Apple’s AR and VR playZuck’s obsession with the metaverse gets all the headlines, but Apple CEO Tim Cook has been hyping up mixed reality—the mashup of physical and virtual words—for at least six years. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. And that underlying computing platform is really what Apple wants to get right before its headset launch. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/05/apple-prepares-for-a-world-after-smartphones</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/05/apple-prepares-for-a-world-after-smartphones</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 15:21:41 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Turntable: June 6</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d6d5ff67f65ccfc42ccab384cde8bbc6f76d8507-1920x1080.png?rect=150,0,1620,1080&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/turntable-june-6</link>
  <author>Mary Tobler</author>
  <categories>games</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/turntable-june-6</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 10:46:45 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>NASA taps two companies to develop lunar spacesuits</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d0fa9f7bc4d52a6931e12099236c1baf9219e795-3840x2939.jpg?rect=0,189,3840,2560&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. NASA will test the companies’ suits in 2025, and then decide whether to fund one or both designs. One major reason for the holdup is that the necessary spacesuits won’t be ready on time. It’s been a leading aerospace supplier for decades and has supplied spacesuits to NASA before. Hoping to finally fix its spacesuit production snags, NASA announced this week that it awarded contracts to two teams led by private companies, Axiom Space and Collins Aerospace, to make its suits. NASA’s outsourcing is a tacit admission that its own work developing lunar suits in-house for 15 years has been too costly and time-consuming: As of August 2021, NASA’s spacesuit production schedule has suffered more than 20 months of delays. Construction of the rocket and the lunar lander have been set back by Covid-19 supply and labor challenges, as well as a legal scuffle between NASA and Jeff Bezos’s Blue Origin after NASA chose Elon Musk’s SpaceX to build the lander. In the end, the whole endeavor was such a slog that NASA finally decided to bring in Axiom Space and Collins Aerospace to help outfit its astronauts. Meanwhile, newcomer Axiom Space was founded in 2016 with the goal of building the first private space station. So, constructing a spacesuit is a Sisyphean task to start with, and NASA faced major hurdles trying to produce them in-house:1. Last year, NASA only received 77% of the funding it requested for part of the lunar program, resulting in a $69 million budget shortfall for suit development and a delay of at least three months. Looking ahead…even if NASA astronauts get the right gear to go to the moon in time, the lunar mission has to overcome several other major obstacles. *sigh*—JW What’s the holdup, exactly?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/nasa-taps-two-companies-to-develop-lunar-spacesuits?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Space</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/nasa-taps-two-companies-to-develop-lunar-spacesuits?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 00:01:42 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Make it work: This is goodbye (for now)</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7b6de1bb891bb0dd9e289abb0a591582a5da30e6-1503x603.png?rect=299,0,905,603&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. If you were following along, I hope you stumbled across something useful that you were able to apply to your own professional journey. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. Whispering farewell (but not in a weird way),Shane</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/make-it-work-this-is-goodbye-for-now?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Shane Loughnane</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/make-it-work-this-is-goodbye-for-now?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 00:01:42 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Icebreakers with entrepreneur and reality TV star Bethenny Frankel</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/c5d0ccc2093fbcefc34b1be0bbdb8cbc72153086-1024x675.jpg?rect=6,0,1013,675&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. That’s not in line with who I am and I don’t have to do that anymore. I don’t consider winning to be hitting a home run every time you get up to the plate. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. Meaning, when I was on reality television, I was having disputes and talking about things that I don’t necessarily care about and in a lot of unnecessary drama that is created by a circumstance on television. But Frankel isn’t just a TV star—she’s also a super savvy businessperson. My first time trying to get on The Apprentice, I think, “I’ve made it” and they tell me, "You didn’t make it.” I consider winning how you handle it. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/icebreakers-with-entrepreneur-and-reality-tv-star-bethenny-frankel?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Entrepreneurship</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/icebreakers-with-entrepreneur-and-reality-tv-star-bethenny-frankel?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 00:01:41 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Stock watch: June 5</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/64c9a47a9775b70b66f3393543a59281361dbe0b-1500x2000.png?rect=0,500,1500,1000&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/stock-watch-june-5?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Culture</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/stock-watch-june-5?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 00:01:38 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Saturday sketch: Get back in here</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/a66ed56fe7ad8d49a36fff0d3723eb5fd2703269-1080x1080.jpg?rect=0,180,1080,720&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/saturday-sketch-get-back-in-here?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/saturday-sketch-get-back-in-here?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:01:39 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Study: Moderate coffee drinkers show lower mortality rates</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-06-03/image-7572b65531dc265590363d5f07fb7767faef3955-245x135-gif/coffee_crop.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. ) had a lower mortality rate than people who didn’t drink any coffee. A study published this week in the journal Annals of Internal Medicine found that people who drink 1.5 to 3.5 cups of coffee a day (even if they add a little bit of sugar to it! —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! But it doesn’t conclusively prove that coffee itself is the panacea:Dr. Christina Wee, an associate professor at Harvard Medical School and the deputy editor of the journal, told the NYT that other characteristics of coffee drinkers could be contributing to their lower mortality rate, such as diet and exercise. The researchers, who studied 171,000 people in the UK over a seven-year period, found that coffee drinkers were 30% less likely to die during the study period than the coffee-less.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/study-moderate-coffee-drinkers-show-lower-mortality-rates?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Food &amp; Bev</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/study-moderate-coffee-drinkers-show-lower-mortality-rates?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:01:38 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Russia invaded Ukraine 100 days ago</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/baf55ad764b4eebe3b404581a2596e912423948d-3500x2336.jpg?rect=0,1,3500,2333&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. But it appears to be fading from many Americans’ radars: Social media interactions on news articles about Ukraine have decreased from 109 million in the first week of the war to 4.8 million last week, per Axios. On Thursday, Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky said that Russia has increased its territorial control to 20%. Zelensky said this week that 60–100 Ukrainian soldiers are dying every day in the conflict, in addition to the tens of thousands of civilians who have been killed since Feb. 24, per Ukrainian estimates. But, despite failing in its initial aims to topple the Ukrainian government, Russia appears set on defending the territory it has already seized. —JW So where do we stand? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeYesterday marked 100 days since Russia invaded Ukraine in a brazen move that has shaken up the post-Cold War geopolitical order, caused economic hardships all over the globe, and displaced millions of people from their homes.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/russia-invaded-ukraine-100-days-ago?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>International</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/russia-invaded-ukraine-100-days-ago?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:01:38 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>CEOs are warning of a recession; the economic data isn’t saying the same</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/f258687cf8d80a14edd8e3835716abe943e7b674-1024x668.jpg?rect=11,0,1002,668&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. While some leading CEOs are sounding the alarm on a recession, the actual economic data isn’t saying the same thing. Musk is one of several prominent execs who has recently said that the fight against inflation + the war in Ukraine are about to send the economy into the Bad Place. It showed the US economy added a meaty 390,000 jobs last month and the unemployment rate held steady at a super low 3.6%.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/ceos-are-warning-of-a-recession?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Economy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/ceos-are-warning-of-a-recession?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:01:38 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Study: Moderate coffee drinkers show lower mortality rates</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-06-03/image-7572b65531dc265590363d5f07fb7767faef3955-245x135-gif/coffee_crop.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. ) had a lower mortality rate than people who didn’t drink any coffee. But it doesn’t conclusively prove that coffee itself is what Ponce de Leon was seeking. The researchers, who studied 171,000 people in the UK over a seven-year period, found that coffee drinkers were 30% less likely to die during the study period than the coffee-less. —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! A study published this week in the journal Annals of Internal Medicine found that people who drink 1.5 to 3.5 cups of coffee a day (even if they add a little bit of sugar to it! Dr. Christina Wee, an associate professor at Harvard Medical School and the deputy editor of the journal, told the NYT that other characteristics of coffee drinkers could be contributing to their lower mortality rate, such as diet and exercise.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/study-moderate-coffee-drinkers-show-lower-mortality-rates</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Food &amp; Bev</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/study-moderate-coffee-drinkers-show-lower-mortality-rates</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 15:01:38 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Russia invaded Ukraine 100 days ago</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/baf55ad764b4eebe3b404581a2596e912423948d-3500x2336.jpg?rect=0,1,3500,2333&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Before it launched its invasion, Russia controlled 7% of Ukraine— including Crimea, which Russia annexed in 2014. But it appears to be fading from many Americans’ radars: Social media interactions on news articles about Ukraine have decreased from 109 million in the first week of the war to 4.8 million last week, per Axios. —JW So where do we stand? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! On Thursday, Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky said that Russia has increased its control to 20%.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/russia-invaded-ukraine-100-days-ago</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>International</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/russia-invaded-ukraine-100-days-ago</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 15:01:37 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>CEOs are warning of a recession; the economy data isn’t so sure</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/f258687cf8d80a14edd8e3835716abe943e7b674-1024x668.jpg?rect=11,0,1002,668&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. While some leading CEOs are sounding the alarm on a recession, the actual economic data isn’t saying the same thing. Musk is one of several prominent execs who has recently said that the fight against inflation + the war in Ukraine are about to send the economy into the Bad Place.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/ceos-are-warning-of-a-recession</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Economy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/ceos-are-warning-of-a-recession</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 14:46:38 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>NASA taps two companies to develop lunar spacesuits</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7367cd242e8ecfd101249b416649fbd124c88912-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. NASA will test the companies’ suits in 2025, and then decide whether to fund one or both designs. One major reason for the holdup is that the necessary spacesuits won’t be ready on time. It’s been a leading aerospace supplier for decades and has supplied spacesuits to NASA before. Hoping to finally fix its spacesuit production snags, NASA announced this week that it awarded contracts to two teams led by private companies, Axiom Space and Collins Aerospace, to make its suits. NASA’s outsourcing is a tacit admission that its own work developing lunar suits in-house for 15 years has been too costly and time-consuming: As of August 2021, NASA’s spacesuit production schedule has suffered more than 20 months of delays. Construction of the rocket and the lunar lander have been set back by Covid-19 supply and labor challenges, as well as a legal scuffle between NASA and Jeff Bezos’s Blue Origin after NASA chose Elon Musk’s SpaceX to build the lander. In the end, the whole endeavor was such a slog that NASA finally decided to bring in Axiom Space and Collins Aerospace to help outfit its astronauts. Meanwhile, newcomer Axiom Space was founded in 2016 with the goal of building the first private space station. So, constructing a spacesuit is a Sisyphean task to start with, and NASA faced major hurdles trying to produce them in-house:1. Last year, NASA only received 77% of the funding it requested for part of the lunar program, resulting in a $69 million budget shortfall for suit development and a delay of at least three months. Looking ahead…even if NASA astronauts get the right gear to go to the moon in time, the lunar mission has to overcome several other major obstacles. *sigh*—JW What’s the holdup, exactly?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/nasa-taps-two-companies-to-develop-lunar-spacesuits</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Space</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/nasa-taps-two-companies-to-develop-lunar-spacesuits</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 14:31:37 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Saturday sketch: Get back in here</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/a66ed56fe7ad8d49a36fff0d3723eb5fd2703269-1080x1080.jpg?rect=0,180,1080,720&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/saturday-sketch-get-back-in-here</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/saturday-sketch-get-back-in-here</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 14:16:45 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Icebreakers with entrepreneur and reality TV star Bethenny Frankel</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/c5d0ccc2093fbcefc34b1be0bbdb8cbc72153086-1024x675.jpg?rect=6,0,1013,675&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. That’s not in line with who I am and I don’t have to do that anymore. I don’t consider winning to be hitting a home run every time you get up to the plate. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. Meaning, when I was on reality television, I was having disputes and talking about things that I don’t necessarily care about and in a lot of unnecessary drama that is created by a circumstance on television. But Frankel isn’t just a TV star—she’s also a super savvy businessperson. My first time trying to get on The Apprentice, I think, “I’ve made it” and they tell me, "You didn’t make it.” I consider winning how you handle it. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/icebreakers-with-entrepreneur-and-reality-tv-star-bethenny-frankel</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Entrepreneurship</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/icebreakers-with-entrepreneur-and-reality-tv-star-bethenny-frankel</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 13:46:41 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Make it work: This is goodbye (for now)</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7b6de1bb891bb0dd9e289abb0a591582a5da30e6-1503x603.png?rect=299,0,905,603&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. If you were following along, I hope you stumbled across something useful that you were able to apply to your own professional journey. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. Whispering farewell (but not in a weird way),Shane</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/make-it-work-this-is-goodbye-for-now</link>
  <author>Shane Loughnane</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/make-it-work-this-is-goodbye-for-now</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 13:31:40 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Stock watch: June 5</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/64c9a47a9775b70b66f3393543a59281361dbe0b-1500x2000.png?rect=0,500,1500,1000&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/stock-watch-june-5</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Culture</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/03/stock-watch-june-5</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 13:01:41 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>White House interns will be paid for the first time in history</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/396e6ae1f33a4dbaba163b6823b572e3b8902afa-778x384.png?rect=101,0,576,384&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe White House said yesterday it would start paying its interns for the first time in history. This was set in motion in March, when President Biden signed a spending bill that set aside $4.5 million to pay White House interns, and bumped funding for Senate intern pay from $6 million in FY 2021 to $7 million. For the upcoming fall session, White House interns will make $750 a week.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/white-house-interns-will-be-paid-for-the-first-time-in-history?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Government</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/white-house-interns-will-be-paid-for-the-first-time-in-history?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:01:37 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>CNN’s new boss wants network to cut back its use of the “breaking news” banner</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/0a60b1579a79d3b6cb9e09bdc7d37f538a2b6826-1200x900.jpg?rect=0,50,1200,800&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIn a move a bit like asking Batman to cut back on using the Batman voice, new CNN boss Chris Licht sent a memo to staffers indicating that the network needs to tamp down its use of “breaking news” graphics. —MK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! “It has become such a fixture on every channel and network that its impact has become lost on the audience,” Licht’s memo said of the label, which is also used heavily on other cable news channels and, as any Twitter user knows, on 99% of journalism tweets. Zoom out: This move comes about two months after CNN and the rest of WarnerMedia’s properties were acquired by Discovery and combined under the newly formed Warner Bros. In the acquisition, Licht became Chairman &amp; CEO of CNN Global.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/CNN-breaking-news-guidelines?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/CNN-breaking-news-guidelines?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:01:37 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Gun reform front and center in</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/bfbd681a8ccde1647bd19d670a1a19f117f8e0f3-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribePresident Biden made sure of that by delivering a rare prime-time address to the nation last night, urging Congress to pass laws that could help curb the gun violence that’s sweeping the country. President Biden’s prime-time address also reflects the government’s greater focus on the issue. What’s not on the table: an assault weapons ban. The House could vote on it next week, but even if it gets through the chamber, it’s expected to be quashed by the evenly split Senate (where it would need 10 Republican votes, or 60 total, to pass). —NF “For God’s sake, how much more carnage are we willing to accept?” css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Police said the shooter was targeting the surgeon who had recently performed his back surgery. Those measures include expanding background checks, buttressing school security, and implementing red flag laws that allow law enforcement to take guns away from people deemed high-risk of harming themselves or others. So what’s on the table? Biden rarely interrupts your evening TV binge to make a speech, having done it only for annual addresses to Congress and remarks on the one-year anniversary of the Covid pandemic.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/02/gun-reform-inches-along-in-dc?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/02/gun-reform-inches-along-in-dc?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:01:36 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Gun reform inches along in DC</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/138f1afe44f9b53579be9a5c0e4aa0464b73e49a-7293x4864.jpg?rect=0,1,7293,4862&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. President Biden’s primetime address also reflects the government’s greater focus on the issue. What’s not on the table: an assault weapons ban. The House could vote on it next week, but even if it gets through the chamber, it’s expected to be quashed by the evenly split Senate (where it would need 10 Republican votes, or 60 total, to pass). —NF css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Police said that he was targeting the surgeon who had recently performed his back surgery.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/02/gun-reform-inches-along-in-dc</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/02/gun-reform-inches-along-in-dc</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 14:46:37 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>White House interns will be paid for the first time in history</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/396e6ae1f33a4dbaba163b6823b572e3b8902afa-778x384.png?rect=101,0,576,384&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe White House said yesterday it would start paying its interns for the first time in history. This was set in motion in March, when President Biden signed a spending bill that set aside $4.5 million to pay White House interns, and bumped funding for Senate intern pay from $6 million in FY 2021 to $7 million. While white students make up about 52% of the undergrad population in the US, they accounted for 76% of paid Congressional interns in 2019. For the upcoming fall session, White House interns will make $750 a week.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/white-house-interns-will-be-paid-for-the-first-time-in-history</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Government</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/white-house-interns-will-be-paid-for-the-first-time-in-history</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 14:46:37 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>CNN’s new boss wants network to cut back its use of the “breaking news” banner</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/0a60b1579a79d3b6cb9e09bdc7d37f538a2b6826-1200x900.jpg?rect=0,50,1200,800&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIn a move a bit like asking Batman to cut back on using the Batman voice, new CNN boss Chris Licht sent a memo to staffers indicating that the network needs to tamp down its use of “breaking news” graphics. —MK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! “It has become such a fixture on every channel and network that its impact has become lost on the audience,” Licht’s memo said of the label, which is also used heavily on other cable news channels and, as any Twitter user knows, on 99% of journalism tweets. Zoom out: This move comes about two months after CNN and the rest of WarnerMedia’s properties were acquired by Discovery and combined under the umbrella of the newly formed Warner Bros. In the acquisition, Licht became Chairman &amp; CEO of CNN Global.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/CNN-breaking-news-guidelines</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/CNN-breaking-news-guidelines</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 14:46:36 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Las Vegas chapels receive cease-and-desists for Elvis-themed weddings</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/26624f599fb00c68dbb0908a4fe8007fa8487977-5528x3664.jpg?rect=16,0,5496,3664&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Zoom out: ABG could be preparing for a resurgence of Elvis enthusiasm over the new Baz Luhrmann biopic, Elvis, which is set to release June 24. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe group that licenses Elvis Presley merch, Authentic Brands Group (ABG), sent cease-and-desist letters last month to a number of Las Vegas chapels in an attempt to quash their Elvis-themed weddings. —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! But ABG does claim the rights to the artist’s name and likeness, as well as the words “Elvis,” “Elvis Presley,” and “The King of Rock and Roll.” How many people want Elvis to marry them? Melody Willis-Williams, president of Vegas Weddings and Viva Las Vegas Weddings, told the Las Vegas Review Journal that she does thousands of sequined, “Burning Love”-esque weddings every year. The details: Nevada law says ABG can’t stop Elvis impersonators from shaking their hips any more than parents in the ’60s. The trademark battle poses a threat to the small chapels’ post-pandemic recovery and Vegas’s $2 billion wedding industry.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/cease-and-desists-for-elvis-themed-weddings?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/cease-and-desists-for-elvis-themed-weddings?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:01:40 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Canada decriminalized the possession of some drugs in British Columbia</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/f139db4ba3d00a66e6d450f1942c79e19ccf6413-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. British Columbia declared overdose deaths from fentanyl—a synthetic opioid that’s 50x stronger than heroin—a public health emergency in 2016. —JW css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Drug arrests have plummeted in Oregon, with no evidence of an increase in drug-related crime, as some critics feared. In the years since, and especially since the start of the pandemic, overdose deaths have surged in the area. Canada can glimpse its future in OregonIn a departure from the federal government’s punitive war-on-drugs policies, Oregon became the first US state to decriminalize the possession of a small amount of most drugs in 2020. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeCanada has decriminalized the possession of small amounts of opioids, methamphetamine, MDMA, and cocaine in the province of British Columbia. But proponents of decriminalization say more time is needed for the policy to achieve its intended results. However, there’s also little evidence decriminalization has caused users to seek help. The new policy will run for three years to help determine if destigmatizing drugs results in more users seeking help.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/canada-decriminalized-the-possession-of-some-drugs-in-british-columbia?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Health</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/canada-decriminalized-the-possession-of-some-drugs-in-british-columbia?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:01:40 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>NFT industry hit with first insider trading charges</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-06-01/image-82f99d03eb0debfcdece199a48164080eb1e3079-480x262-gif/giphy(3).webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The former head of product at leading NFT marketplace OpenSea was charged with wire fraud and money laundering linked to the insider trading of NFTs, or non-fungible tokens. Once it was alerted of these transactions, OpenSea basically admitted that insider trading was taking place, and in September asked Chastain to leave the company after an investigation. Why it matters: OpenSea is by far the largest NFT marketplace, with 65% market share. —NF css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Therefore, a credibility hit to OpenSea is a credibility hit to the entire NFT industry. (As of March, Chastain was working on a new NFT project, Oval. Nathaniel Chastain found that out yesterday. It all started last September, when OpenSea users noticed something fishy was going on with crypto wallets belonging to Chastain.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/01/insider-trading-comes-to-nfts?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/01/insider-trading-comes-to-nfts?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:01:40 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Canada decriminalized the possession of some drugs in British Columbia</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/2e2d923055b0092399a3a4c8861eecb92c66349a-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. British Columbia declared overdose deaths from fentanyl—a synthetic opioid that’s 50x stronger than heroin—a public health emergency in 2016. —JW css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Drug arrests have plummeted in Oregon, with no evidence of an increase in drug-related crime, as some critics feared. In the years since, and especially since the start of the pandemic, overdose deaths have surged in the area. Canada can glimpse its future in OregonIn a departure from the federal government’s punitive war-on-drugs policies, Oregon became the first US state to decriminalize the possession of a small amount of most drugs in 2020. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeCanada has decriminalized the possession of small amounts of opioids, methamphetamine, MDMA, and cocaine in the province of British Columbia. But proponents of decriminalization say more time is needed for the policy to achieve its intended results. However, there’s also little evidence decriminalization has caused users to seek help. The new policy will run for three years to help determine if destigmatizing drugs results in more users seeking help.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/canada-decriminalized-the-possession-of-some-drugs-in-british-columbia</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Health</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/canada-decriminalized-the-possession-of-some-drugs-in-british-columbia</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 15:16:40 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>

</channel>
</rss>
