<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <atom:link href="https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2023/04/01/users/1/web_requests/22/MorningBrew.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
 <atom:icon>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2023/04/01/favicon.ico</atom:icon>
 

 <title>MorningBrew as a feed</title>
 <description>This is a feed of recent MorningBrew articles published by Huginn</description>
 <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2023/04/01</link>
 <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 11:03:56 -0700</lastBuildDate>
 <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 11:03:56 -0700</pubDate>
 <ttl>60</ttl>
 <item>
  <title>Inside Jobs: Calligrapher Michelle Marquis</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d8fb48cc18130c86d97ae5ebabdc03d710202cb6-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. My right hand is one of my most important assets. The one thing that I’ve learned from the past couple years is that universally everyone loves to see their name written, especially if someone else took the time to write it. I keep it manicured, especially if I’m doing calligraphy in person. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. Do people ever not realize your work is calligraphy at first and think it’s just printed out? What’s one thing that someone who doesn’t do calligraphy professionally wouldn’t know? One of my first projects was a man who contacted me because he actually had lost some mobility in his arm, so he had a hard time writing. Calligraphy can look so perfect. So, especially with day-to-day phone and computer usage, I try to make sure that I take extra good care of my right hand. It’s really a case-by-case basis.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/4Bp?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Career Building</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/4Bp?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 11:01:55 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Twitter said it will begin getting rid of verification for nonpaying users</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/0c33aec0d7f8b9689725ad93f30b09a2da68d9eb-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. That should make for an interesting feed: One researcher found that roughly half of the 220,000 Twitter Blue subscribers have less than 1,000 followers. Today Twitter will start phasing out the verification badge for anyone unwilling to pay $8 a month for Twitter Blue.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/4B0?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Social Media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/4B0?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 11:01:50 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Italy temporarily banned ChatGPT over AI concerns</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/c78c857682e7f0429f68fb2fa8cc002132ba2250-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeYesterday, Italy’s data protection authority temporarily banned ChatGPT—and not because the AI chatbot may have told one user he could slather his pasta in Flamin’ Hot Cheetos salsa. AI chatbots *do* have a lot of data in their trunkThe ban stems from a recent accidental leak of user conversations with ChatGPT. The regulator is primarily concerned that ChatGPT collects and stores Italian users’ personal data without their permission. Determining what data out of that info glut belongs to Italian citizens if necessary would be…complicated. But things could get even thornier if the regulator also decides to delve into the other kind of data the system stores. Not only regulators are concerned about AI’s new-found popularity: More than 1,000 tech leaders and experts signed a controversial open letter this week calling for a six-month pause on sophisticated AI projects. AI systems like ChatGPT make huge sweeps of the internet and feed all that info into their underlying algorithms. —JW</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/4AU?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/4AU?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 11:01:49 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>If you invested in tech stocks last quarter, congrats</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fstorage.morningbrew.com%2Fgif%2F2023-03-31%2Fimage-738aa440668676a8ab94d0194ed8a59c02060006-360x240-gif%2Fvolitile-markets-0323_360.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=70'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Large banks are feeling the pinch of rising interest rates: Global merger and acquisition deals suffered the biggest first-quarter decline since 2001, according to data analyzed by the Financial Times. The S&amp;P 500 gained 7%, and the Dow Jones Industrial Average gained 0.4%. Smaller institutions were most badly injured by the bank panic: The SPRD S&amp;P Regional Banking ETF, which consists of non-behemoth banks, had more than a quarter of its value wiped out in Q1. Top of the classWall Street rewarded tech companies’ layoffs and other cost cutting measures, giving tech stocks a resurgence. —SK</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/4AO?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Sam Klebanov</author>
  <categories>Finance</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/4AO?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 11:01:49 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Plot twist in Disney–DeSantis brawl</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fstorage.morningbrew.com%2Fgif%2F2023-03-30%2Fimage-7eb0bcac2c7f6cac28157b11b92b039ed1277ef5-435x290-gif%2Fdisney-via-giphy-0323.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=70'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Bewildered board members only learned about these agreements this week, and one said they planned to “correct” Disney’s behind-the-scenes sleight of hand. When the board was still Disney-controlled, it entered into restrictive covenants for the land that:Bar the new board from using the Disney name or any of the company’s IP, including Mickey Mouse. For 55 years, the state allowed Disney to make its own rules for developing the land where its theme parks sit. The company quietly entered agreements that rendered the board Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis hand-picked to govern the special tax district surrounding Disney World nearly powerless. —AR Give Disney the right to review any proposed changes to properties in the district. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIt looks like Disney has added a new character to the Magic Kingdom: the troll. With the new board in place, it looked like DeSantis had won…until Disney pulled a Mulan-like switcheroo. But after the company criticized the so-called “Don’t Say Gay” bill, DeSantis installed his own board to run the district.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/30/plot-twist-in-disney-desantis-brawl</link>
  <author>Abigail Rubenstein</author>
  <categories>Business News</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/30/plot-twist-in-disney-desantis-brawl</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 10:57:12 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Gwyneth Paltrow found not at fault over ski collision</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/4a8f12e0beefcef61334d9d2f4c09b7e9340d0ab-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/gwyneth-paltrow-ski-accident-trial-is-all-over-the-internet</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/gwyneth-paltrow-ski-accident-trial-is-all-over-the-internet</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 10:57:11 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Russia arrests an American journalist for alleged espionage</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/9bcef9d7c284e0bc0da6b9f376764af23fe76164-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeAn American reporter for the Wall Street Journal, Evan Gershkovich, was arrested Wednesday in the city of Yekaterinburg for allegedly investigating Russian military secrets for the US. When asked if Russia would consider a prisoner swap for Gershkovich—like the recent trade of Russian arms dealer Viktor Bout for WNBA player Brittney Griner—Russian Deputy Foreign Minister Sergei Ryabkov said it’s too early to consider. It’s the first time an American journalist has been detained on espionage charges in Russia since the Cold War and signals escalating tensions between the rival countries as Russia’s war in Ukraine drags on. —JW css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/30/russia-arrests-american-journalist</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>International</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/30/russia-arrests-american-journalist</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 10:57:05 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>It happened: Trump indicted by New York grand jury</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/937137dcde690f8cc169c9104aa2b7c5406a73b5-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. In a first for a former US president, Donald Trump was indicted on criminal charges by a New York grand jury yesterday, his lawyers and prosecutors said. No one actually knows yet. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. He’s being investigated in three other criminal probes, including one over his alleged mishandling of classified documents. Charges are sometimes kept under wraps until the defendant makes their first appearance in court (known as an arraignment).</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/30/trump-indicted-new-york-grand-jury</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Government</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/30/trump-indicted-new-york-grand-jury</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 10:57:04 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>What’s it like to make music for Pikachu and friends?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/251cf3e920c7e284acca77607b848a338374171d-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. In his early days pursuing music, Ed Goldfarb spent a good chunk of his life taking on side gigs—from playing organs in church to performing country tunes for famous NASCAR drivers in a luxury penthouse. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. ) It is not an exaggeration that I easily held 15 discrete musical jobs in the course of a given week between the ages of 18 and 33, easy. I’ve probably written 13 to 15 hours of music just for Pokémon in the last decade. With Pokémon, the way that anime scores are done is sort of weird. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. But these days, he spends most of his time in his Novato, California, home composing music for film and TV—including the Pokémon franchise. By the end of the first season, you have a library of music that, if you got food poisoning, your assistant could cut in some score. If it’s a new thing, I do exactly what you said: I watch the movie without music.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3oy?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3oy?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 23:01:45 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>New study finds that money does, in fact, buy happiness</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fstorage.morningbrew.com%2Fgif%2F2023-03-08%2Fimage-e196ef46c8ad308f4cea2e25fcb36510b6a326e7-253x169-gif%2FParamountPictures-0323.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=70'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Millionaires and billionaires might be even happier: The study’s authors didn’t have conclusive data for salaries beyond that range (those folks are probably too blissed out to take surveys). A new study found that happiness rises with income—even accelerating at levels beyond $100,000 per year up to $500,000 per year. —MK This new information upends an oft-cited 2010 study that found happiness plateaued near a salary of $75,000, or ~$103k today, after inflation. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeForget being rich in friendships, folks, it’s time to 10x that salary and start a side hustle dropshipping iPhone cases.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3o5?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Wealth</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3o5?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 23:01:39 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The bond market is flashing a recession warning light</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fstorage.morningbrew.com%2Fgif%2F2023-03-08%2Fimage-a6e9607bc6004284240250934a1de60146cf7a91-1500x1000-gif%2F230308_RecessionIsComing.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=70'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Still, one big recession warning signal reared its head this week. A yield curve inversion has happened before every recession since the 1960s, so it’s definitely a more reliable prognosticator than your friend who has “a system” for their March Madness bracket. —AR When Jerome Powell told lawmakers Tuesday that recent strong economic data meant interest rates would likely climb higher than previously expected, it sent the markets into a tizzy, pushing the US Treasury yield curve to its deepest inversion since 1981. What does it have to do with a recession? It signifies that investors expect interest rates to rise in the near term but that those hikes will ultimately damage the economy, forcing rates back down over time. It’s considered an inversion whenever the short-term yield eclipses the long-term yield. And that means…the yield for 2-year Treasury bonds exceeded the yield for 10-year ones—by a lot.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3o0?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Abigail Rubenstein</author>
  <categories>Economy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3o0?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 23:01:39 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Adidas is still floating ideas to part with $1.3b worth of Yeezy inventory</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/529b300594b4ce70c70cf6d495e278c22266999d-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. No one knows how to get rid of itDuring an earnings call yesterday, the new Adidas CEO Bjørn Gulden made it clear that ditching its unwanted Yeezy stock is a top priority. Even if Adidas rebrands the items and sells them, Ye is still promised a cut of the profits. —MM The most likely option? The company is also cutting dividends as it figures out how to replace its $1.5 billion Ye collab. Even bigger picture: The company expects an operating loss of over $730 million this year. The last time Adidas reported an annual loss, George H. However, the company is sort of stuck between a rock and an antisemitic sneaker:Burning or trashing the gear would be unsustainable. Gulden vaguely upvoted this solution in yesterday’s call, saying, “If we sell it, I promise that the people who have been hurt by this will also get something good out of this.”</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3nV?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3nV?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 23:01:39 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Study finds a popular sugar substitute might be bad for your heart</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/a9bcfe78c5463f288d6ffa7fe9618b1734ec4697-720x480.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. In the meantime, one of the study’s authors, Dr. Stanley Hazen, is telling his patients to skip the sweetener and opt for a couple of drops of honey or a pinch of sugar instead. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeA recent study published in Nature Medicine found that the sugar alternative erythritol is associated with an increased risk of heart issues and strokes. —SK It’s also unclear how worried folks without medical conditions should be, as the study mostly followed a population already prone to heart disease (due to conditions like diabetes or high blood pressure). While erythritol is linked to health issues, it does not necessarily cause them. Erythritol was also tied to an increased risk of blood clots in mice and human blood samples. Scientists explored the link between levels of different chemicals in the blood and the risk of heart disease. What did the study find?</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3lh?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Sam Klebanov</author>
  <categories>Health</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3lh?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 23:01:52 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Slack is introducing AI assistant that can write messages for you</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fstorage.morningbrew.com%2Fgif%2F2023-03-07%2Fimage-09d1118f6fd362a387d4205c91c59b6f62f0d598-480x270-gif%2Frobot.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=70'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3lc?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>AI</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3lc?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 23:01:51 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The DOJ is aiming to split up JetBlue’s Spirit takeover</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/76558150ae074ccc053e7cfec2c0826fd3aacdb7-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. And, according to the DOJ, Spirit getting scooped up would eliminate about half of all ultra-low-cost seats in the industry, sending ticket prices (which are already skyrocketing) up even further. Zoom out: The last big merger in the airline industry happened in 2016 when Alaska Airlines acquired Virgin America. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe Biden administration is continuing its full-court press against airline consolidation. According to airlines. —MK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! According to internal company documents that the DOJ cites in its complaint, when Spirit starts flying a given route, average fares fall by 17%. JetBlue has claimed that by increasing its size with the purchase of Spirit, it could better compete with the “big four” airlines: United, Delta, American, and Southwest. org, there have been 21 completed US airline mergers since 2001.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3l4?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Travel</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3l4?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 23:01:50 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Municipalities across the US are naming their snowplows</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/b05d5b80ba70653f7f60c76a6d2452d1689919e3-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. All 240 plows operated by Transport Scotland now have names. Madison isn’t the only city with named plows. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeA storm drain? —MK Where’d this come from? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! The idea of naming municipal equipment seems to have been spawned in Scotland, where a 2006 primary school contest to name gritters (snowplows) caught on in a big way. But a storm drain officially named Stormy Drainels?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/snowplow-name-contest</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Government</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/snowplow-name-contest</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 07:36:54 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>This company discovered a (disc) diamond in the rough</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/1525375b2d7712c264d1721d58053bf3a7b67200-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;They generally look to companies like Dymicron for these solutions so they can partner or acquire to distribute them. Learn more about investing in their disc replacements. The Triadyme®-C implant eliminates the primary long-term issue with traditional disc replacements: wear debris. So, how many carats are in each disc replacement? Using a tri-lobe design, this artificial disc is molded from human-made diamond that never wears out (💎 really are forever). The Triadyme®-C disc replacement shows powerful potential: It’s already available outside the US and on its way to FDA approval stateside. No other disc on the market can provide this combination of zero wear debris and the exceptional biomechanics that our innovative tri-lobe design offers. And that’s a diamond worth noticing. But beyond that, additional degeneration can develop if the motion of an artificial disc doesn’t closely align with a patient’s natural movement. Now we can generate a whole new fan base of people and bring on investors who can help us solve the problem of degenerative disc disease. How do Dymicron’s discs improve the patient experience? You can help Dymicron bring this solution to those in need. That’s the exciting part of what the SEC and Congress have done with the Jumpstart Our Business Startups Act. It created equity crowdfunding opportunities so we can raise capital through interested retail investors.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/02/dymicron-diamond-disc-replacement</link>
  <author>Morning Brew</author>
  <categories>Health Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/02/dymicron-diamond-disc-replacement</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 07:36:54 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>E-bike batteries are exploding, setting buildings on fire</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/33fd32b5c316a54b21717e3d864cf6d34bcb6097-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. The number of blazes has been rising in tandem with the number of e-bikes sold: The US imported over 1 million last year, a gear shift up from 880,000 in 2021 and 450,000 in 2020, according to the Light Electric Vehicle Association. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Lithium-ion batteries were the fourth leading cause of fire deaths in NYC last year, per the FDNY. It’s the latest in a string of fires started by the lithium-ion batteries in electric bikes and scooters. It’s about the batteries. There’s a solution in the worksThe New York City Council approved several bills last week that 1) add new safety and certification standards for micromobility vehicles 2) launch educational campaigns on safe usage and 3) restrict the use and sale of secondhand batteries. They’ve caused at least 30 fires, 40 injuries, and two deaths in NYC this year as of Feb. 27, according to the New York Fire Department. —JW The fires they cause are nightmarish: Lithium-ion battery fires can engulf a room in about 15 seconds, per the UL Fire Safety Research Institute. These batteries are safe unless they’re faulty or damaged, and e-bikes and e-scooters are subject to a lot of hard use hauling commuters and delivery workers up and over NYC’s bridges. The problem is especially evident in New York City, where on Sunday an e-bike battery sparked an hourslong blaze at a Bronx grocery store that injured seven.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/06/e-bike-batteries-are-exploding-fire</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Transportation</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/06/e-bike-batteries-are-exploding-fire</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 07:36:53 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Municipalities across the US are naming their snowplows</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/b05d5b80ba70653f7f60c76a6d2452d1689919e3-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. All 240 plows operated by Transport Scotland now have names. Madison isn’t the only city with named plows. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeA storm drain? —MK Where’d this come from? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! The idea of naming municipal equipment seems to have been spawned in Scotland, where a 2006 primary school contest to name gritters (snowplows) caught on in a big way. But a storm drain officially named Stormy Drainels?</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3h6?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Government</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3h6?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 23:02:00 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Air travel might be getting bumpier</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/dd5a07e9e92accd8f27aafa64f3e1477da0cadcf-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. It’s also elevating the risk of clear-air turbulence, which appears out of the blue and gives pilots little time to order passengers to buckle up. Only 146 people were seriously injured by severe turbulence between 2009 and 2021, per the Federal Aviation Administration—and most were not wearing their seatbelts. —SK Airplanes are designed to withstand intense shaking, while pilots are trained to safely navigate intense wind…even if your plane meatloaf sticks to the aircraft ceiling. Are the skies becoming more treacherous? Last week alone, turbulence was responsible for: at least seven injuries aboard a transatlantic Lufthansa red-eye, the aborted landing of a North Carolina-bound Southwest flight, and a passenger death on a business jet traveling between New Hampshire and Virginia. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Extreme turbulence is still very rare and not usually dangerous. But in general, you should still be more concerned about the prospect of a canceled flight than a shaky one.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3g_?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Sam Klebanov</author>
  <categories>Travel</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3g_?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 23:01:59 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>E-bike batteries are exploding, setting buildings on fire</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/33fd32b5c316a54b21717e3d864cf6d34bcb6097-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. The number of blazes has been rising in tandem with the number of e-bikes sold: The US imported over 1 million last year, a gear shift up from 880,000 in 2021 and 450,000 in 2020, according to the Light Electric Vehicle Association. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Lithium-ion batteries were the fourth leading cause of fire deaths in NYC last year, per the FDNY. It’s the latest in a string of fires started by the lithium-ion batteries in electric bikes and scooters. It’s about the batteries. There’s a solution in the worksThe New York City Council approved several bills last week that 1) add new safety and certification standards for micromobility vehicles 2) launch educational campaigns on safe usage and 3) restrict the use and sale of secondhand batteries. They’ve caused at least 30 fires, 40 injuries, and two deaths in NYC this year as of Feb. 27, according to the New York Fire Department. —JW The fires they cause are nightmarish: Lithium-ion battery fires can engulf a room in about 15 seconds, per the UL Fire Safety Research Institute. These batteries are safe unless they’re faulty or damaged, and e-bikes and e-scooters are subject to a lot of hard use hauling commuters and delivery workers up and over NYC’s bridges. The problem is especially evident in New York City, where on Sunday an e-bike battery sparked an hourslong blaze at a Bronx grocery store that injured seven.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3gU?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Transportation</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3gU?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 23:01:59 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Walgreens won’t sell popular abortion pill in some states after legal threat</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fstorage.morningbrew.com%2Fgif%2F2023-03-03%2Fimage-b9528178921f7af5faf3b5dbe954a7e18c885157-1500x1000-gif%2Fwalgreens-abortion-pill-02.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=70'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Walgreens, the second-largest pharmacy chain in the US, said it would work to become one of those pharmacies but quickly saw pushback from anti-abortion lawmakers. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeWalgreens said Thursday that it will not distribute abortion pills in 20 states, including several where abortion is legal. —MM Medication abortions account for more than half of all legal abortions in the US, and mifepristone is part of a popular two-drug protocol. So now, the company says it won’t sell the pills in those states, either in its stores or by mail, even though the FDA also said mifepristone could be mailed to states with abortion bans.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/walgreens-abortion-pill-states-legal-threat</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Healthcare</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/walgreens-abortion-pill-states-legal-threat</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 09:01:58 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Amazon hits pause on 2nd headquarters</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/c9e0a78ce05910fbb75d2145a52ef30bbd6c215d-720x480.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. And it’s just one of the many ominous signs for the commercial real estate market since people no longer go into the office every workday. The company has put an indefinite hold on breaking ground for the swanky office park known as PenPlace, which would encompass three 22-story towers and a sleek helix-shaped building. —SK The company is also reducing its physical footprint elsewhere. And headcount is unlikely to skyrocket any time soon: Amazon began laying off 18,000 employees in January (the steepest job cuts in its history). But for now, it’s not short on office space: Its employees still spend a lot of time working from home, even after a recent companywide mandate required them to return to the office three days a week. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeAmazon’s HQ2 is starting to look more like HQ1.5. Other Big Tech companies like Meta and Twitter have also slimmed down their real estate footprint to save money. Earlier this year, it vacated an office tower in its hometown, Seattle.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/03/amazon-hits-pause-on-2nd-headquarters</link>
  <author>Sam Klebanov</author>
  <categories>Business News</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/03/amazon-hits-pause-on-2nd-headquarters</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 09:01:58 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>More companies are selling a ‘first-class’ experience</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fstorage.morningbrew.com%2Fgif%2F2022-10-31%2Fimage-ccbce6eabc93dcadc3be194600aa319775afcc60-479x270-gif%2Fgiphy.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=70'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. A Le Creuset instead of a regular ol’ Dutch oven? Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. Big picture: The urge to focus on premium products could result in fewer options for lower-income Americans, who spend a greater share of their income on essentials like housing and food, the NYT notes.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/05/more-companies-are-selling-a-first-class-experience</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Business News</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/05/more-companies-are-selling-a-first-class-experience</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 09:01:57 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>ChatGPT not a hit on college campuses...yet</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/77ffa803aec547c3fa9c8a9ab224615119379196-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. And while overall ChatGPT adoption is low on college campuses, it has gained power users. 56% of respondents who haven’t used ChatGPT said the primary reason why is that they’ve not had a use for it. 25% of the students who’ve used ChatGPT have it bookmarked on their web browser. And the students who said they do fire up ChatGPT…don’t use it all that much, as 55% of respondents who said they’ve used ChatGPT do so “almost never.” Uses for ChatGPTAmong the students who do use ChatGPT…what are they using it for? For giggles: 71% of students who’ve used ChatGPT said they use it in part for entertainment or just for fun. 17% of students who’ve heard of ChatGPT said they have direct knowledge of friends using ChatGPT to cheat. Of course, ChatGPT was released just a few months ago—so in a sense it is also quite remarkable that 60% of college students have heard of it. In our poll, the majority said no, but it’s still notable that 20% of students who’ve heard of ChatGPT said the chatbot has influenced their career thinking. As Google: 32% of students who’ve used ChatGPT said they use it in part for quick answers to simple questions, and 31% to understand complex topics. So, why aren’t college students using ChatGPT? For…cheating? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/05/chatgpt-not-a-hit-on-college-campuses-yet</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/05/chatgpt-not-a-hit-on-college-campuses-yet</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 09:01:55 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>ChatGPT not a hit on college campuses...yet</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/77ffa803aec547c3fa9c8a9ab224615119379196-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. And while overall ChatGPT adoption is low on college campuses, it has gained power users. 56% of respondents who haven’t used ChatGPT said the primary reason why is that they’ve not had a use for it. 25% of the students who’ve used ChatGPT have it bookmarked on their web browser. And the students who said they do fire up ChatGPT…don’t use it all that much, as 55% of respondents who said they’ve used ChatGPT do so “almost never.” Uses for ChatGPTAmong the students who do use ChatGPT…what are they using it for? For giggles: 71% of students who’ve used ChatGPT said they use it in part for entertainment or just for fun. 17% of students who’ve heard of ChatGPT said they have direct knowledge of friends using ChatGPT to cheat. Of course, ChatGPT was released just a few months ago—so in a sense it is also quite remarkable that 60% of college students have heard of it. In our poll, the majority said no, but it’s still notable that 20% of students who’ve heard of ChatGPT said the chatbot has influenced their career thinking. As Google: 32% of students who’ve used ChatGPT said they use it in part for quick answers to simple questions, and 31% to understand complex topics. So, why aren’t college students using ChatGPT? For…cheating? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3d5?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3d5?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 22:01:54 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>More companies are selling a ‘first-class’ experience</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fstorage.morningbrew.com%2Fgif%2F2022-10-31%2Fimage-ccbce6eabc93dcadc3be194600aa319775afcc60-479x270-gif%2Fgiphy.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=70'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. A Le Creuset instead of a regular ol’ Dutch oven? Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. Big picture: The urge to focus on premium products could result in fewer options for lower-income Americans, who spend a greater share of their income on essentials like housing and food, the NYT notes.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3cX?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Business News</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3cX?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 22:01:52 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Gov’t cash for chipmakers comes with contentious strings attached</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/cb9566448aff6a2a8e900bbe26bdf5e7155256c4-6016x4016.jpg?rect=0,2,6016,4011&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The Biden administration appears to be using the CHIPS and Science Act to kill an entire flock of birds with one stone. One policy think tank called the childcare requirement “a pragmatic move” since it’ll help companies recruit women amid a shortage of affordable childcare. He warns that the Biden administration infusing the program with social goals will raise costs for chip manufacturers. A spokesperson for the Commerce Department told Morning Brew that workforce considerations are just one part of the holistic process for doling out funding, which gives “most weight” in an application to “national and economic security.” The law aims to spur semiconductor manufacturing in the US, but its $39 billion subsidy program, which the Commerce Department presented this week, puts strict conditions on companies looking to access the funds. The Commerce Department will take companies’ willingness to refrain from stock buybacks into account, and some recipients of federal cash will have to share windfall profits with the government. The WSJ’s Chief Economics Commentator Greg Ip called the requirements “mission creep” and argued that they might undercut the competitiveness of the US chips subsidies, noting that Canada, the EU, and Japan are also offering cash to lure in chipmakers. —SK Chips vs. The Commerce Department says the rules will help create the “large, skilled, and diverse workforce” that companies need to churn out chips. childcare: what critics are sayingCritics have dubbed the Biden Administration’s implementation of the CHIPS Act “industrial social policy,” contending that it’s a Trojan horse for progressive measures unrelated to the main purpose of the program: making the US into a major chip producer.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3aj?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Sam Klebanov</author>
  <categories>Government</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3aj?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 19:01:58 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Brew Classifieds: Week of February 27</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/3e37b6a7a51f7ff299b63367b250872326ac26d9-1500x375.png?rect=469,0,563,375&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. On eBay, a single box is selling for as much as $79.99. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. —MM SOMETHING BLUE: The US marriage rate has fallen nearly 60% in the last 50 years as people have delayed the storied tradition of their uncle getting blackout drunk near their friends, or skipped it altogether.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3a3?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Business News</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/3a3?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 19:01:57 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Eli Lilly finally gives in to insulin price-cut pressure</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d98f254a0a119b064648e1e0b58f19e3a3452ac7-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeSome diabetic Americans will soon be able to spend less than their monthly internet bill to pick up life-saving medicine. It also said it would cap insulin costs at $35/month when people pay out-of-pocket for the drug. Insulin-makers like Eli Lilly have received growing social and political pressure over the last few years to make insulin more affordable. Drugmaker Eli Lilly said yesterday it would slash the list prices for its two most prescribed insulin products, Humalog and Humulin, by 70%. If you’re feeling a little déjà vu…you’re probably thinking of the viral tweet from November written by Sean Morrow, who paid $8 for a blue checkmark in order to impersonate Eli Lilly and announce that “insulin is free now.” —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Lilly is getting ahead of DC dramaThe Inflation Reduction Act included a $35 monthly insulin price cap for seniors on Medicare, and in his State of the Union address last month, President Biden called for expanding that cap to everyone.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/eli-lilly-gives-into-insulin-price-cut-pressure</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Healthcare</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/eli-lilly-gives-into-insulin-price-cut-pressure</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 19:01:55 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Whiskey fungus is out of control around Jack Daniel’s barrelhouses in Tennessee</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/b930a149eae0818f6bcd76ef840669640bf2abea-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. An out-of-control, soot-like whiskey fungus is spreading in Tennessee and causing a rift between residents and famed whiskey-maker Jack Daniel’s. —MK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Residents are asking for Jack Daniel’s to fund an environmental study to see if the vapors or fungus harm humans, and install an air filtration system to slow their spread.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/whiskey-fungus-jack-daniels-tennessee</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Food &amp; Bev</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/whiskey-fungus-jack-daniels-tennessee</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 19:01:54 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Californians recover from almost-record snowfall as another storm heads their way</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/2b7684a72c31bbf6ec14a32e36657604c8effa45-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Big picture: California’s wet and wild winter has freed up half of the state from drought, according to data from the US Drought Monitor. Mountain High in Southern California averages 67 inches of snowfall every season.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/californians-recover-from-snowfall</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Climate Change</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/californians-recover-from-snowfall</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 19:01:54 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Chinese apps face restrictions, but US consumers keep downloading</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/969d1c597d5d1e768a3b74836ca7a7f6747dbedc-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Experts can’t agree on whether Chinese apps are a threatAn exec at the think tank founded by former Google CEO Eric Schmidt wrote last month that all of these uber-popular Chinese apps, including the messenger WeChat and game apps from Tencent, “could pose similar challenges [to TikTok], particularly with respect to data harvesting, data exploitation, and—possibly—covert influence.” Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The top three free apps on Apple’s App Store yesterday were Temu, CapCut, and TikTok, while Google Play’s were Temu, TikTok, and Street Fighter: Duel—with Chinese fast-fashion company Shein chilling at No. 4. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIt’s no secret that the government considers TikTok a national security threat. —JW</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/02/chinese-apps-face-restrictions</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/03/02/chinese-apps-face-restrictions</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 19:01:52 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>BriAnna Garza can teach you how to shoot a basketball</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/c56e3a650780c5acd72231b034b8aa56766eb33c-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Kyrie Irving is excellent at his free throws because he’s able to get into a kind of spiritual place. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. What’s the one thing amateur basketball players should work on in the gym to improve their shot? Last year I did a six-month study of watching every single catch-and-shoot in the NBA with 33,000 data points. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. The free throw is so strange because there’s no other shot in basketball like it. How do you coach free throws and how much is mental over technique? So no one shot is going to look exactly the same. If you’re gonna work on one thing, get that down. And there’s a reason Garza thinks deeply about basketball shots—she makes a living from doing it.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/32I?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/32I?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:31:54 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Facing criticism, TikTok announces a screen time limit for users under 18</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fstorage.morningbrew.com%2Fgif%2F2023-03-01%2Fimage-ea1506f0afb94e570652af819534eb797a06b0da-1500x1000-gif%2Ftiktok-watch-timer-0323.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=70'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/33P?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Social Media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/33P?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:31:48 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Elon Musk unveils ‘master plan’ for Tesla</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/e531e8e335457092568974a26d20c52b5b536d1d-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. ) of robots Tesla’s been building to do human labor eventually. Musk, who recently reclaimed the title of world’s richest person thanks to a $310 billion surge in Tesla stock, called it his “Master Plan 3” (with a straight face) and tried to sell investors on Tesla’s super-long-term goals.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/33J?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Auto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/33J?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:31:47 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Eli Lilly finally gives in to insulin price-cut pressure</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d98f254a0a119b064648e1e0b58f19e3a3452ac7-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeSome diabetic Americans will soon be able to spend less than their monthly internet bill to pick up life-saving medicine. It also said it would cap insulin costs at $35/month when people pay out-of-pocket for the drug. Insulin-makers like Eli Lilly have received growing social and political pressure over the last few years to make insulin more affordable. Drugmaker Eli Lilly said yesterday it would slash the list prices for its two most prescribed insulin products, Humalog and Humulin, by 70%. If you’re feeling a little déjà vu…you’re probably thinking of the viral tweet from November written by Sean Morrow, who paid $8 for a blue checkmark in order to impersonate Eli Lilly and announce that “insulin is free now.” —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Lilly is getting ahead of DC dramaThe Inflation Reduction Act included a $35 monthly insulin price cap for seniors on Medicare, and in his State of the Union address last month, President Biden called for expanding that cap to everyone.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/33B?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Healthcare</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/33B?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:31:46 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>A brief history of EPCOT: Walt Disney's failed city of tomorrow</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/c90b51339c62636046e99d6e22b38891774c0bfa-768x494.png?rect=14,0,741,494&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Brilliant), Walt Disney conceived of a master-planned city that would exist as one pillar of the Disney World complex in Florida. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. All citizens of the Jetsons-esque city would be working for the Disney company or businesses that worked with Disney. The backstory: Walt Disney was often frustrated with modern city living.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/10/01/a-brief-history-of-the-epcot-center-and-what-it-was-meant-to-be</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/10/01/a-brief-history-of-the-epcot-center-and-what-it-was-meant-to-be</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:31:45 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Stock Watch: October 3</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/9f519b0cd86d03d3e4cb36b371b46423b17d0236-1500x2000.png?rect=0,500,1500,1000&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/10/01/stock-watch-october-3</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Culture</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/10/01/stock-watch-october-3</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:31:42 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Government Shutdown Averted, but Big Battles Loom for Biden's Agenda</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/2a6f770af9886e096d1dd90ee86e4cdde8f00cac-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. It's stuck in the mud as Democrats have struggled to round up support for their package that would pour unprecedented sums into health care, education, and climate. This bill also includes billions of dollars for Afghan refugee resettlement and aid for communities hit by recent hurricanes.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/09/30/government-shutdown-averted-but-big-battles-loom-for-biden-s-agenda</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Government</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/09/30/government-shutdown-averted-but-big-battles-loom-for-biden-s-agenda</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:31:42 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>

</channel>
</rss>
