<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <atom:link href="https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2021/06/01/users/1/web_requests/22/MorningBrew.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
 <atom:icon>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2021/06/01/favicon.ico</atom:icon>
 

 <title>MorningBrew as a feed</title>
 <description>This is a feed of recent MorningBrew articles published by Huginn</description>
 <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2021/06/01</link>
 <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 14:43:56 -0700</lastBuildDate>
 <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 14:43:56 -0700</pubDate>
 <ttl>60</ttl>
 <item>
  <title>Hack Shuts Down JBS Meat Processing Operations</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5305%2Fcow.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; If operations do remain on pause for more than a few days, the hiccup could turn into a real headache for JBS customers like supermarkets and fast food chains that require a continuous supply of meat. The JBS incident comes just weeks after hackers forced the shutdown of the Colonial Pipeline and disrupted gas supplies up the East Coast.  Extra bad timingWhile wholesale meat prices remained mostly stable yesterday, extended disruption from the cyberattack could send meat prices—already on the rise—soaring even higher.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/01/hack-shuts-jbs-meat-processing-operations</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>food</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/01/hack-shuts-jbs-meat-processing-operations</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 14:41:55 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Oil Prices Surge to Highest Levels Since Covid Began</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/l0HlHSB8v5yRtBlHW/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;At one point the price of oil plunged into negative territory—meaning someone would pay you to take possession of their oil barrel.  What happened: The powerful oil cartel OPEC and its allies agreed to gradually increase oil production. Yesterday, oil prices hit their highest levels since the pandemic began.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/01/oil-prices-surge-highest-levels-since-covid-began</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>energy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/01/oil-prices-surge-highest-levels-since-covid-began</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 14:41:55 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Stock Analysis 101</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5302%2Fchart.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You can find company financials through the SEC EDGAR portal. If the same company is trading at $20 per share, the PE ratio is 20. It’s more about finding patterns in the stock price that investors can exploit. Here are some signs of a company with a blossoming future:Lasting edge in the market: You want to invest in a company that has some competitive advantage in its sector. It’s the same thing with picking stocks: You want to invest in companies that are part of a growing industry. It’s OK if you’re feeling this way, because there’s more to a stock price than the numbers. Vincent Glode, a finance professor at the University of Pennsylvania, told the Brew that looking beyond the numbers can help you feel more confident about the stock. You won’t find any analysis there, so head over to a site like Yahoo Finance to see what investors are thinking. Chat with a financial advisor about the most responsible way to fit stock trading into your portfolio. Then, move onto valuation ratios, which compare a company’s financial results to its price in the market. Do your own researchAt first, financial statements can look like they’re written in Klingon. Financial market experts agree that identifying stocks that’ll beat the overall market is hard. Review the numbersNo matter your approach, it’s a good idea to take a look at the company’s financials before investing. In general, you want a quick ratio higher than 1. They care less about the company’s intrinsic value and more about how the stock price will shift in the future. See what analysts—and even your friends—are saying about the company’s future in qualitative terms. Fundamental analysis involves determining the company’s intrinsic value from the bottom up, from examining historical financial statements to imagining the company’s future. Analysts often associate industries with specific ratios that best depict a company’s financials.  Put it all togetherThis is where investment analysts take their research, create a financial model, and forecast the company’s future financials before making a trading decision. That’s why you often see higher trading volume around earnings reports. Analysts from major financial institutions put out their predictions ahead of companies’ earnings announcements, and a company’s goal is for these metrics to meet or exceed analyst expectations. Much of what’s built into a company’s stock price is investors’ expectations of the future, from new product lines to shifting market conditions. Investment analysts have already crunched the numbers, so you can put away your TI-83. If the company’s market cap—or total value in the market—is $50 million and sales were $5 million for the last 12-month period, the PSR is 10. “Psychological views of companies can last a very long time.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/01/stock-analysis-101</link>
  <author>Ryan Lasker</author>
  <categories>markets</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/01/stock-analysis-101</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 10:12:00 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Week Ahead: June 1</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5297%2Fbridge_in_virginia.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Infrastructure: This week will be pivotal for the big infrastructure proposal President Biden has laid out. It may be short, but it is packed. Facebook's F8 developer conference begins tomorrow.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/week-ahead-june-1?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>calendar</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/week-ahead-june-1?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 03:02:02 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: June 1</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5296%2Fford_f-150.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Roughly 20% of all gun buyers in the US last year were first-time owners, and now, 39% of American households own guns, up from 32% in 2016. (Morning Brew)</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/key-performance-indicators-june-1?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/key-performance-indicators-june-1?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 03:02:02 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Nestlé Rethinks Health Strategy Following Leaked Report</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5300%2Fnestle.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Unfortunately for Nestlé's PR team...   An internal presentation reported by the FT found that 63% of Nestlé products don't meet a "recognized definition of health" (in this case, at least 3.5/5 stars on Australia's health rating system).</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/nestl-rethinks-health-strategy-following-leaked-report?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>food and bev</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/nestl-rethinks-health-strategy-following-leaked-report?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 03:02:02 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Naomi Osaka, Highest-Earning Female Athlete in the World, Drops Out of French Open</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5299%2Ffrench_open_tennis_rolan.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Other athletes said they respected Osaka’s initial decision to avoid the press, but pointed out that answering questions in front of a hot mic is just part of the job. Tennis legend Billie Jean King said that professional athletes have a responsibility to talk to the media.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/naomi-osaka-highestearning-female-athlete-world-drops-french-open?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/naomi-osaka-highestearning-female-athlete-world-drops-french-open?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 03:02:01 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>China Adopts Three-Child Policy Rule to Boost Population</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/cAMfDqovnTpqDhm1OR/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; The US population grew at its slowest rate since the Great Depression from 2010–2020, and its birth rate declined for the sixth straight year last year.  Why it matters: Declining population growth has profound implications for a country's economic success.     Zoom out: While many parts of the world face stagnant population growth, others are making up for it. Bottom line: As much as the Chinese government wants to grow the country's share of the world population, it might be fighting a losing battle.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/china-adopts-threechild-policy-rule-boost-population?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>demographics</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/china-adopts-threechild-policy-rule-boost-population?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 03:02:01 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Naomi Osaka, Highest-Earning Female Athlete in the World, Drops Out of French Open</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5299%2Ffrench_open_tennis_rolan.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Other athletes said they respected Osaka’s initial decision to avoid the press, but pointed out that answering questions in front of a hot mic is just part of the job. Tennis legend Billie Jean King said that professional athletes have a responsibility to talk to the media.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/naomi-osaka-highestearning-female-athlete-world-drops-french-open</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/naomi-osaka-highestearning-female-athlete-world-drops-french-open</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 14:31:57 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Week Ahead: June 1</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5297%2Fbridge_in_virginia.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Infrastructure: This week will be pivotal for the big infrastructure proposal President Biden has laid out. It may be short, but it is packed. Facebook's F8 developer conference begins tomorrow.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/week-ahead-june-1</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>calendar</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/week-ahead-june-1</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 14:26:57 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: June 1</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5296%2Fford_f-150.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Roughly 20% of all gun buyers in the US last year were first-time owners, and now, 39% of American households own guns, up from 32% in 2016. (Morning Brew)</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/key-performance-indicators-june-1</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/key-performance-indicators-june-1</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 14:21:57 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>China Adopts Three-Child Policy Rule to Boost Population</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/cAMfDqovnTpqDhm1OR/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; The US population grew at its slowest rate since the Great Depression from 2010–2020, and its birth rate declined for the sixth straight year last year.     Zoom out: While many parts of the world face stagnant population growth, others are making up for it.  Why it matters: Declining population growth has profound implications for a country's future economic success. Bottom line: As much as the Chinese government wants to grow the country's share of the world population, it might be fighting a losing battle.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/china-adopts-threechild-policy-rule-boost-population</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>demographics</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/china-adopts-threechild-policy-rule-boost-population</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 14:16:56 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Nestlé Rethinks Health Strategy Following Leaked Report</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5300%2Fnestle.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In response, Nestlé said it’s updating nutrition standards and its health strategy. Unfortunately for Nestlé's PR team... Baby Ruths aren’t going anywhere, though: "Confectionary and chocolate address a deep human need and are going to be here to stay," CEO Mark Schneider said last year.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/nestl-rethinks-health-strategy-following-leaked-report</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>food and bev</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/nestl-rethinks-health-strategy-following-leaked-report</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 14:16:56 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Brew Mini: Comic Book Bros</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhAQABAIAAAAAAAP///yH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAABAAEAAAIBRAA7'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/brew-mini-comic-book-bros</link>
  <author>Mary Tobler</author>
  <categories>games</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/brew-mini-comic-book-bros</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 10:41:59 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Exclusive: Post-Pandemic, Summer Travel Trends to Watch</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5066%2Froad_trip_big_sur.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Of the top 20 most popular flight deals Scott's Cheap Flights sent subscribers over the last two months, multiple were roundtrips to Hawaii and Alaska. 39% of travelers said they're concerned about travel costs. While more travelers are looking to get their delayed Eurotrip on, domestic travel is still the name of the game this summer, Keyes said. When countries announce they're reopening borders for US travelers, there's a predictable spike in flight searches to that destination, according to Keyes. Almost 60% said the frequency of their summer travel plans is similar to pre-pandemic levels. Of the 30% of respondents who work remotely at least one day a week, 42% said it's positively impacted their ability to travel.  Some people don't know what they're doing yetDue to pandemic uncertainty, many travelers have waited until closer to their intended travel date to book.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/exclusive-postpandemic-summer-travel-trends-watch</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>travel</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/exclusive-postpandemic-summer-travel-trends-watch</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 22:07:00 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Business Trends to Watch This Summer</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5295%2Fsummer_2021_preview.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But there are other consumer trends I'm excited to watch this summer.  —Neal FreymanCryptoMaybe I'm on Twitter too much, but cryptocurrency, and more specifically cryptocurrency regulation, is the top business topic I'll be watching this summer. Vaccine inequality In just six months, the US has vaccinated over half its adult population, a remarkable feat considering how much we seemed to lag other countries in controlling the virus last year. Is home fitness here to stay even as gyms reopen? Let us know if we missed any. I think the big thing to watch is whether supply chains getting back to normal will cause the inflation scaries to subside. In the last two months, there have been gas, lumber, chip, ketchup, worker, and boba shortages, just to name a few that had accompanying Morning Brew pieces. Inflation data over the summer will reveal whether this quirkiness is more permanent than officials had thought.  —Yiran Yu  Btw, have you experienced the awkwardness of a post-Covid hug/handshake? After soaring more than 400% in 2020, Peloton's stock is down almost 24% this year. Maybe.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/business-trends-watch-summer</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>trends</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/business-trends-watch-summer</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 22:07:00 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>So You Survived a Year of Virtual School…Now What?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F1977%2Fback_to_school_shopping.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;—Fatima Ali, Brew U Campus Ambassador, University of Wisconsin, Class of 2021)Here are some resources to get you to be your most productive self:How to Track Your Networking with Notion (Medium)2020's Most Popular Coursera Courses (Coursera)How to Find a Hobby (The New York Times)The 10 Most Popular TEDx talks (Ted)Relax and Self-Care“I would say to just ride the wave and try not to force anything too much. I wish I would’ve taken more time prior to this to explore alternative careers and network with people in different industries, and I highly encourage other college students to do so before deciding what exactly they want to do.” —Colleen McFall, Morning Brew Intern, Temple University, Class of 2022“Explore people, projects, and career paths that interest you... College students have endured one of the most exhaustive school years ever due to the pandemic, and finally now have the chance to relax, breathe, and celebrate. Coming into college I didn’t know what I wanted to use my major for. —Kate Schiliro, Morning Brew fulfillment, New York University, Class of 2020“Don’t stress as much. —Joshua Botkin, Morning Brew Intern, University of Cincinnati, Class of 2023Here are some resources for your career exploration:Marketing Brew’s Internship Guide. (Morning Brew)How to Cold Email Your Way into Your Dream Job. (Morning Brew)How to Get an Internship During Covid. (Morning Brew)2021 Grad’s Guide to Getting Hired.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/29/survived-year-virtual-schoolnow</link>
  <author>Yiran Yu</author>
  <categories>career</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/29/survived-year-virtual-schoolnow</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 04:52:03 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Police Raid a Bitcoin Mining Operation On Accident</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5293%2Forvault_north-western_fr.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;That’s why British police accidentally busted a cryptocurrency mining operation earlier this month, thinking it was an illegal cannabis farm. Zoom out: While stealing electricity is illegal in the UK, mining bitcoin is a-okay.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/police-raid-bitcoin-mining-operation-accident?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/police-raid-bitcoin-mining-operation-accident?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 03:02:00 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: May 29</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5294%2Fpresident_trump_holds_mak.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(Emerging Tech Brew) Read: Your guide to the cloud. In 2017, Neymar joined the French club Paris Saint-Germain for an unheard-of transfer fee of ~$260 million.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/key-performance-indicators-may-29?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/key-performance-indicators-may-29?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 03:02:00 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Vaccine Tracker: May 29</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F4204%2Fvaccine_tracker.JPG&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Also this week, Ohio announced the first winner of its $1 million vaccine lottery: 22-year-old Abbigail Bugenske.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/vaccine-tracker-may-29?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>covid</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/vaccine-tracker-may-29?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 03:02:00 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Memorial Day Weekend Will be Huge Test for Travel</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F955%2F747.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; A majority of the 37 million people expected to travel at least 50 miles from home will be driving, per AAA. and possible jail time. It also extended its zero-tolerance policy for safety violations and added fines...</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/memorial-day-weekend-travel-will-huge-test-travel?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>travel</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/memorial-day-weekend-travel-will-huge-test-travel?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 03:02:00 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Costco Sees Inflationary Pressures, but Will Restart Free Samples</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F4188%2Fcostco.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Overall, the company said that price inflation at the selling level, excluding gasoline, was 2.5%–3.5%, much higher than in March. Costco was one of the first US retailers to mandate masks in early May 2020. Costco is the only place where you can simultaneously buy seven-pound tubs of Nutella and learn about the state of the post-pandemic economy. And probably come back in two minutes and hope you forget our face. But hey, we’ll take it. And samples will be given behind plexiglass screens.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/costco-sees-inflationary-pressures-will-restart-free-samples?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/costco-sees-inflationary-pressures-will-restart-free-samples?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 03:02:00 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Brew Crossword: Perfect Pitch</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhAQABAIAAAAAAAP///yH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAABAAEAAAIBRAA7'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/brew-crossword-perfect-pitch</link>
  <author>Mary Tobler</author>
  <categories>games</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/brew-crossword-perfect-pitch</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 14:47:00 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Costco Sees Inflationary Pressures, but Will Restart Free Samples</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F4188%2Fcostco.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Overall, the company said that price inflation at the selling level, excluding gasoline, was 2.5%–3.5%, much higher than in March.  However, this being the “new normal” and all, some pandemic precautions will remain in place. Costco is the only place where you can buy seven-pound tubs of Nutella and learn about the state of the post-pandemic economy. And probably come back in two minutes and hope you forget our face. But hey, we’ll take it. Costco was one of the first US retailers to mandate masks in early May 2020.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/costco-sees-inflationary-pressures-will-restart-free-samples</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/costco-sees-inflationary-pressures-will-restart-free-samples</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 14:42:00 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Police Raid a Bitcoin Mining Operation On Accident</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5293%2Forvault_north-western_fr.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;That’s why British police accidentally busted a cryptocurrency mining operation earlier this month, thinking it was an illegal cannabis farm. Zoom out: While stealing electricity is illegal in the UK, mining bitcoin is a-okay.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/police-raid-bitcoin-mining-operation-accident</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>cryptocurrency</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/police-raid-bitcoin-mining-operation-accident</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 14:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Vaccine Tracker: May 29</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F4204%2Fvaccine_tracker.JPG&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Also this week, Ohio announced the first winner of its $1 million vaccine lottery: 22-year-old Abbigail Bugenske.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/vaccine-tracker-may-29</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>covid</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/vaccine-tracker-may-29</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 14:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: May 29</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5294%2Fpresident_trump_holds_mak.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(Emerging Tech Brew) Read: Your guide to the cloud. In 2017, Neymar joined the French club Paris Saint-Germain for an unheard-of transfer fee of ~$260 million.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/key-performance-indicators-may-29</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/key-performance-indicators-may-29</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 14:31:59 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Memorial Day Weekend Will be Huge Test for Travel</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F955%2F747.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; A majority of the 37 million people expected to travel at least 50 miles from home will be driving, per AAA. They’ll get one this weekend:US airlines are planning for a daily average of at least two million passengers through the weekend. and possible jail time.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/memorial-day-weekend-travel-will-huge-test-travel</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>travel</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/memorial-day-weekend-travel-will-huge-test-travel</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 14:26:58 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Icebreakers with… John Green</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5292%2Fjohn_green.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I would love for there to be a Major League Soccer team in Indianapolis, but I would not want to own it. What's something that podcasting offers that books don't and vice versa? Tell us about something you love doing that you're terrible at. And tell us about something you really do not like doing that you're great at. What star rating would you give the five-star rating scale?  Name three books on your nightstand right now:Clint Smith's How the Word Is Passed, Ashley C.  If you could own any sports franchise other than the English soccer team AFC Wimbledon, of which you are a huge fan, what would it be? In 175 words, one can say much more about a book (or a movie, or a hotel, or a barbershop) than a single data point ever could.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/icebreakers-john-green</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>qanda</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/icebreakers-john-green</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 13:26:58 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Did the Coronavirus Get Leaked From a Lab?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F206%2Fcoronavirus_image.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Right-wing pundits and conservative lawmakers, particularly Sen. Tom Cotton, were pushing the US government to investigate claims that the virus came from the Wuhan Institute of Virology.  As researchers studied Covid-19's origins last year, the natural origin theory dominated and the lab leak theory was considered preposterous. this lab leak theory may not be as crazy as it sounds." But as 2020 went on, scientists found no evidence to support the natural origin theory, China was stonewalling any credible independent investigation, and people started saying, "You know what... Lab leak: A scientist at the Wuhan Institute of Virology, which studies bat viruses, was infected with a contagious strain through a sloppy mistake or an accident, and brought it out to the wider world.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/coronavirus-get-leaked-lab</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>analysis</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/coronavirus-get-leaked-lab</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 13:21:55 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Make It Work: New Jobs Edition</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F4689%2Fmake_it_work_logo.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Let's think about how we can reimagine your question so that you can get the answer you need without looking crazy to your boss (because you did lowkey wait eight months to ask your manager how to do the job lol).  Q: "I started a new role at my company (virtually) about eight months ago with no formal training.  Q: "I have a job offer from one company, but the company I really want to work for has scheduled my interview for the end of the week. How can I buy some time with the company that gave me the offer?"</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/make-work-new-jobs-edition</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>work life</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/make-work-new-jobs-edition</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 13:06:56 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Important Summer Dates</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5042%2Folympics.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Lollapalooza is back in Chicago from July 29 to August 1. June Lana Del Rey releases her new album, Rock Candy Sweet, June 1, followed by Blue Banisters on July 4. Soccer's Euro tournament begins June 11 and runs a full month. JulyMarvel's Black Widow is taking over theaters on July 9. Your boy Luca is coming to Disney+ on June 18. No spectators were allowed at the 2020 US Open, but tennis fans can fill the stands this year from August 30–September 12.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/important-summer-dates</link>
  <author>Yiran Yu</author>
  <categories>calendar</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/important-summer-dates</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 12:12:00 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Where Morning Brew Readers Are Going for Memorial Day </title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/l2YWnw4TcCv5Vkgb6/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;—Matt L." I have to settle with heading to my friends at the Jersey shore for MDW, if that counts as traveling."  "I'm going to a lake house in Tennessee with Hinge boy and his pals 💃💃💃 for Memorial Day. What a time." A staycation with my family is all I want and to take a day to remember all those we have lost. Going to the promised land of Moses Lake, WA! —Matthew A."</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/morning-brew-readers-going-memorial-day?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>community</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/morning-brew-readers-going-memorial-day?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 03:01:58 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: May 28</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F2788%2Fadam_neumann.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Javier Tebas, the president of Spanish soccer's La Liga, is not giving up on the concept of a European "Super League," which fizzled embarrassingly in less than 48 hours last month. Read: A deep dive into the Citizen app, which critics say is promoting vigilantism.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/key-performance-indicators-may-28?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/key-performance-indicators-may-28?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 03:01:58 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Disney's 'Cruella' Signals a Pivot to PG-13</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/9ayXNVkco6fM6YUNPU/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In the same time span, PG movies earned $24.3 billion; R movies, $26.5 billion; and G movies, $2.7 billion, according to Comscore. Cruella is Disney's third PG-13 release in a year, according to the WSJ. Today, Disney's live-action Cruella arrives in theaters and on Disney+.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/disneys-cruella-signals-pivot-pg13?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/disneys-cruella-signals-pivot-pg13?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 03:01:58 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Acorns Plans SPAC IPO Amidst Talks of Regulation</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5267%2Facorns.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SEC Chairman Gary Gensler said yesterday that the agency is beefing up resources to look into the SPAC boom, which many fintechs like Acorns have taken advantage of.  He might not have to wait long. But even the biggest name in SPACs, Chamath Palihapitiya, wants more oversight of the process.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/acorns-plans-spac-ipo-amidst-talks-regulation?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>fintech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/acorns-plans-spac-ipo-amidst-talks-regulation?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 03:01:58 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Biden to Propose $6T Budget</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5265%2Fwhite_house_budget.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This morning, President Biden will send Congress a jumbo-sized $6 trillion budget for FY2022, the NYT reported yesterday. Not the only new bill on Capitol HillYesterday, GOP senators released a $928 billion counteroffer to Biden's infrastructure package, more than half of which would go to roads and bridges. , is technically hammered out through 12 appropriations bills passed by Congress and signed by the president.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/biden-propose-6t-budget?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>government</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/biden-propose-6t-budget?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 03:01:58 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Acorns Plans SPAC IPO Amidst Talks of Regulation</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Foslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5267%2Facorns.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;SEC Chairman Gary Gensler said yesterday that the agency is beefing up resources to investigate the SPAC boom, which many fintechs like Acorns have taken advantage of.  He might not have to wait long. But even the biggest name in SPACs, Chamath Palihapitiya, wants more oversight of the process.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/acorns-plans-spac-ipo-amidst-talks-regulation</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/acorns-plans-spac-ipo-amidst-talks-regulation</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 14:51:59 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Where Morning Brew Readers Are Going for Memorial Day </title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/l2YWnw4TcCv5Vkgb6/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;—Matt L." I have to settle with heading to my friends at the Jersey shore for MDW, if that counts as traveling."  "I'm going to a lake house in Tennessee with Hinge boy and his pals 💃💃💃 for Memorial Day. What a time." A staycation with my family is all I want and to take a day to remember all those we have lost. Going to the promised land of Moses Lake, WA! —Matthew A."</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/morning-brew-readers-going-memorial-day</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>community</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/morning-brew-readers-going-memorial-day</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 14:46:59 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Brew’s Weekly News Quiz: May 28</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhAQABAIAAAAAAAP///yH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAABAAEAAAIBRAA7'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/brews-weekly-news-quiz-may-27</link>
  <author>Mary Tobler</author>
  <categories>quiz</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/brews-weekly-news-quiz-may-27</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 14:46:59 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>

</channel>
</rss>
