<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <atom:link href="https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2020/12/13/users/1/web_requests/22/MorningBrew.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
 <atom:icon>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2020/12/13/favicon.ico</atom:icon>
 

 <title>MorningBrew as a feed</title>
 <description>This is a feed of recent MorningBrew articles published by Huginn</description>
 <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2020/12/13</link>
 <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 16:43:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
 <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 16:43:16 -0800</pubDate>
 <ttl>60</ttl>
 <item>
  <title>George Senate Races Attracting Attention from Corporate America</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3405/georgia_gop_senate_candid.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;the vote is scheduled for Jan. 5, but in-person early voting starts today. Looking ahead... Its online fundraising platform processed nearly $112 million in donations from Nov. 4 and Nov. 23 (the GOP equivalent processed $55.6 million).</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/13/george-senate-races-attracting-attention-corporate-america</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>election</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/13/george-senate-races-attracting-attention-corporate-america</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 16:41:15 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Roblox, Affirm Delay IPOs to Early 2021</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/2750/roblox.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;And even companies that make no money are soaring: At least three electric vehicle companies worth more than $2 billion have no revenue. Recent IPO trends may lead them to sell more shares or price them differently. Affirm and Roblox were hoping for valuations as high as $10 billion and $8 billion, respectively.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/13/roblox-affirm-delay-ipos-early-2021</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>market</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/13/roblox-affirm-delay-ipos-early-2021</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 16:41:15 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The First Covid-19 Vaccines Are Being Delivered</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3404/pfizer_vaccine.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Altogether, around 3 million doses will snake their way to 636 distribution centers across the country in the coming days.   The vaccine requires two shots a month apart, so officials are saving the second half of the ~6.4 million doses planned for the first wave to send out in a few weeks.   Supply chain: In 2009, delivery timetables for the swine flu vaccine shifted regularly. It's expected to get approval. The remaining challenges Spoilage: Pfizer's vaccine needs to maintain -94°F, and although the company has equipped shipping containers with dry ice and GPS-enabled temperature sensors, it's expected that some doses won't survive the journey.  </description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/13/first-covid19-vaccines-delivered</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>healthcare</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/13/first-covid19-vaccines-delivered</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 16:36:11 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Week Ahead: Tesla's Grand Entrance and Another Vaccine</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/9kSH36D2DtFOU/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;   Everything else: Christopher Nolan's Tenet will be released digitally on Tuesday.    Tesla gets promoted: On Friday, Elon Musk's $578 billion electric automaker will join the S&amp;P 500 index. Friday is National Ugly Sweater Day. A major snowstorm could hit the East Coast mid-week.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/13/week-ahead-teslas-grand-entrance-another-vaccine</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>calendar</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/13/week-ahead-teslas-grand-entrance-another-vaccine</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 16:36:11 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Kevin From 'The Office' Will Bring in More Than $1 Million on Cameo This Year</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/11zU4IDJeg75Sg/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But Galanis thinks President Trump would crush Dobrik if he joined Cameo. Since he charges $195/video, we estimate Baumgartner will have averaged at least 14 videos per day in 2020.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/14/kevin-office-will-bring-1-million-cameo-year</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/14/kevin-office-will-bring-1-million-cameo-year</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 16:36:11 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Your Candy Bar Has a Dark Secret</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3391/chocolate.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  Originally filed in 2005, the case alleges the companies violated international laws against child slavery." Nestlé and Cargill say they've made efforts to eliminate child labor from supply chains. The chocolate supply chain is riddled with child labor.    That's one of the problems with the cocoa supply chain.   An October report from the Labor Department estimates ~1.6 million children are working on cocoa farms. A decision on the side of Nestlé and Cargill could affect future human rights cases brought under the ATS.    This case could have big implications for corporate liability The case centers on the Alien Tort Statute (ATS), a provision nearly as old as the U.S. that provides a path for foreign nationals to sue over violations of international law or U.S. treaties abroad in American courts.   This wasn't the Court's first dance with ATS.   They won't have to worry...   Ex.: The ATS has been invoked in conversations around corporate liability for supply chains linked to imprisoned Uighur Muslims in China."   While the justices weren't convinced that ATS was the right statute to use in pursuit of this case...</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/13/candy-bar-dark-secret</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>big-deal</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/13/candy-bar-dark-secret</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 21:06:11 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Hyundai Acquires Boston Dynamics and Its Robot Dogs for $1.1 Billion</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/47EtjlHYFREM5Rznaf/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  Some of the sectors Boston Dynamics’s tech might help with one day: self-driving vehicles, smart factories, and healthcare.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/hyundai-acquires-boston-dynamics-robot-dogs-11-billion?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/hyundai-acquires-boston-dynamics-robot-dogs-11-billion?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 03:01:11 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Popping IPO Market Could Be “Broken”</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/31q2ecYvWjcYsWthyQ/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In 2019, just three newly public companies did.   For Chesky, the gap between Airbnb’s debut share price of $68 and the $139/share it actually opened at translates to billions of dollars of missed opportunity (had the company initially sold its shares at that higher price). Plus, these first-day pops can make shares look soggy later.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/popping-ipo-market-broken?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>markets</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/popping-ipo-market-broken?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 03:01:11 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Short Sellers on Pace for Worst Year Ever</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3395/bro_meme.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Two of the most popular targets for short sellers, Moderna and Tesla, have gained 702% and 629% this year, respectively, wiping out short sellers’ March profits.   A quick refresher: Short sellers make money when a company loses value.   But it’s been nothing but pain ever since.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/short-sellers-pace-worst-year-ever?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Toby Howell</author>
  <categories>investing</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/short-sellers-pace-worst-year-ever?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 03:01:11 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Corporations Across Sectors Prepare to Make and Distribute the Vaccine</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3396/cargo_hold.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  Pfizer and Moderna are expected to generate $32 billion in Covid-19 vaccine sales in 2021, according to Wall Street forecasts. They’re confident that together they have the capacity to deliver both the life-saving shot and the Christmas sweater you sent your aunt.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/corporations-across-sectors-prepare-make-distribute-vaccine?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>public-health</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/corporations-across-sectors-prepare-make-distribute-vaccine?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 03:01:11 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Finance Bosses Look Beyond Wall Street to Florida</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/3o7TKT7gSMOT8Thtss/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  Yesterday, Ken Moelis, the chairman and CEO of New York investment bank Moelis &amp; Co., told Bloomberg he wouldn't stop his employees from moving to Florida.   It’s not just finance… And it’s not just New York bleeding business leaders. And if that talent wants to do it in Florida, that’s where we’ll support them.”   Right on cue, software giant Oracle said yesterday it was moving its HQ from Redwood City, CA, to Austin, TX.   It’s not exactly a secret that Florida is warmer than New York, boasts a cheaper cost of living, and has world-class institutions like Publix.     Why now?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/finance-bosses-look-beyond-wall-street-florida?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>finance</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/finance-bosses-look-beyond-wall-street-florida?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 03:01:11 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Short Sellers on Pace for Worst Year Ever</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3395/bro_meme.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Two of the most popular targets for short sellers, Moderna and Tesla, have gained 702% and 629% this year, respectively, wiping out short sellers’ March profits.   A quick refresher: Short sellers make money when a company loses value.   But it’s been nothing but pain ever since.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/short-sellers-pace-worst-year-ever</link>
  <author>Toby Howell</author>
  <categories>investing</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/short-sellers-pace-worst-year-ever</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 14:46:10 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Popping IPO Market Could Be “Broken”</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/31q2ecYvWjcYsWthyQ/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In 2019, just three newly public companies did.   For Chesky, the gap between Airbnb’s debut share price of $68 and the $139/share it actually opened at translates to billions of dollars of missed opportunity (had the company initially sold its shares at that higher price). Plus, these first-day pops can make shares look soggy later.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/popping-ipo-market-broken</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>markets</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/popping-ipo-market-broken</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 14:46:10 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Sony Buys Crunchyroll, Consolidates the Big Business of Bringing Japanese Anime to Western Viewers</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/qWnoVy8UlX3A44dtQk/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Netflix can appease the casual viewer by sprinkling shows and movies into its existing service, while Funimation x Crunchyroll can satisfy the straight-from-Japan needs of the truly anime-obsessed.   Crunchyroll gives Sony a Snorlax-sized foothold in anime  In 2019, Sony combined three anime streaming services under its roof—France’s Wakanim, Australia’s Madman Anime Group, and the U.S.' Funimation—into a joint venture between Sony Pictures Entertainment and Sony Music Entertainment’s subsidiary, Aniplex. On Wednesday, Sony-owned anime streaming service Funimation agreed to acquire anime streaming service Crunchyroll from AT&amp;T for $1.2 billion. But getting anime from Japan to the U.S. has historically been a slow and painful process. Medium dive: Read this Quora answer on the history of anime production, this Reddit thread on financing, and “The Dark Side of Japan’s Anime Industry” by Eric Margolis. Crunchyroll will also be folded into this streaming giant, which could mean a complete merger or just an exchange of content. Here’s how it works: Most anime is a collaboration between a studio and a production committee. That rabid love raises the question of whether anime is better suited to an all-in-one streamer like Netflix or a standalone service like Crunchyroll. Once an anime gets made, distribution is quick and painless... Deep dive: Listen to Anime in America from Crunchyroll and read The Soul of Anime: Collaborative Creativity and Japan’s Media Success Story by Ian Condry. there’s room for both Sony and Netflix to be successful anime streamers if the genre’s appeal continues to grow beyond its most hardcore fans. Enter: streaming services Pay-per-month services are getting anime to Western fans in two ways: The Crunchyroll way: In 2006, Crunchyroll started as a quasi-legal YouTube channel for fan-subtitled anime, but evolved into an above-board streaming service in 2009. When Cartoon Network started Toonami (part of Adult Swim) in 1997, the co-creators looked beyond the U.S. for more adult cartoons at the turn of the millennia. Foreign: U.S. media companies didn’t think there would be demand for content that’s not from Hollywood. Both will achieve the same end goal: exporting Japanese anime to Western audiences. Sometimes, major studios like Kyoto Animation and Shaft are part of the production committees themselves, according to this highly detailed Reddit post.   Looking ahead... Adult Swim SVP Jason DeMarco wrote on Twitter that it’s “doubtful” any of the original shows Toonami and Crunchyroll are currently co-producing will be affected.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/sony-buys-crunchyroll-consolidates-big-business-bringing-japanese-anime-western-viewers</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/sony-buys-crunchyroll-consolidates-big-business-bringing-japanese-anime-western-viewers</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 14:46:10 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Hyundai Acquires Boston Dynamics and Its Robot Dogs for $1.1 Billion</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/47EtjlHYFREM5Rznaf/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  Some of the sectors Boston Dynamics’s tech might help with one day: self-driving vehicles, smart factories, and healthcare.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/hyundai-acquires-boston-dynamics-robot-dogs-11-billion</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/hyundai-acquires-boston-dynamics-robot-dogs-11-billion</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 14:36:08 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Corporations Across Sectors Prepare to Make and Distribute the Vaccine</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3396/cargo_hold.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  Moderna did just $60 million in revenue last year. Pfizer and Moderna are expected to generate $32 billion in Covid-19 vaccine sales in 2021, according to Wall Street forecasts.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/corporations-across-sectors-prepare-make-distribute-vaccine</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>public-health</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/corporations-across-sectors-prepare-make-distribute-vaccine</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 14:21:18 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Finance Bosses Look Beyond Wall Street to Florida</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/3o7TKT7gSMOT8Thtss/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  Yesterday, Ken Moelis, the chairman and CEO of New York investment bank Moelis &amp; Co., told Bloomberg he wouldn't stop his employees from moving to Florida.   It’s not just finance… And it’s not just New York bleeding businesses. And if that talent wants to do it in Florida, that’s where we’ll support them.”   Right on cue, software giant Oracle said yesterday it was moving its HQ from Redwood City, CA, to Austin, TX.   It’s not exactly a secret that Florida is warmer than New York, boasts a cheaper cost of living, and has world-class institutions like Publix.     Why now?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/finance-bosses-look-beyond-wall-street-florida</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>finance</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/11/finance-bosses-look-beyond-wall-street-florida</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 14:21:18 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>How to Host a Company Holiday Party During Covid?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/3o7TKQO1dMAnxRXlPW/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;   But ordinary times these are not.   One benefit of an online holiday party?   You’ll find everything you need right here. What is Slack’s video function but an opportunity for embarrassment waiting to happen? We aren’t so sure. “At corporate holiday parties, you typically get a handful of folks who end up drinking too much and do something embarrassing,” Ryan Costello of Event Farm told the WSJ.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/host-company-holiday-party-covid?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Eliza Carter</author>
  <categories>employers</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/host-company-holiday-party-covid?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 03:01:23 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Jobless Claims, Food Insecurity Rise</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3180/usa.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;    Housing: A homebuying boom has added a collective $1 trillion in homeowner equity this year (an average of $17,000 per homeowner), according to CoreLogic. Applications from self-employed and gig workers for a federal program rose 48%, but that program expires Dec. 26.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/jobless-claims-food-insecurity-rise?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>economy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/jobless-claims-food-insecurity-rise?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 03:01:23 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Disney Announces Disney+ Content Slate</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/2751/lion_king_meme.png'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Zoom out: Disney’s streaming unit is growing rapidly, but still incurring big losses ($2.8 billion in fiscal year 2020) that analysts expect to peak in the next two years.   But Disney isn't planning to follow WarnerMedia down that path just yet. WarnerMedia is planning joint theater-HBO Max premieres next year.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/disney-announces-disney-content-slate?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/disney-announces-disney-content-slate?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 03:01:23 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>FDA Approves Pfizer-BioNTech Vaccine, Raising Questions Over Who Counts as Essential</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3380/covid_shot_line.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;    Now comes the hard part  Pfizer, BioNTech, and other manufacturers have generated lifesaving products at a breathtaking speed...   Bottom line: It will ultimately fall to the states to decide which workers are “essential” enough to receive the first, limited doses of the vaccine. Currently, the only clear directive is that healthcare workers and residents of long-term care facilities go first—and no industry reps dispute that.   Unblinding would hamstring the research process... but it would also get people vaccinated.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/fda-approves-pfizerbiontech-vaccine-raising-questions-counts-essential?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Eliza Carter</author>
  <categories>covid-19</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/fda-approves-pfizerbiontech-vaccine-raising-questions-counts-essential?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 03:01:23 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>FDA Approves Pfizer-BioNTech Vaccine, Raising Questions Over Who Counts as Essential</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3380/covid_shot_line.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;    Now comes the hard part  Pfizer, BioNTech, and other manufacturers have generated lifesaving products at a breathtaking speed...   Bottom line: It will ultimately fall to the states to decide which workers are “essential” enough to receive the first, limited doses of the vaccine.   Some states have drafted plans for distribution, but many of them don’t match up.   Unblinding would hamstring the research process... Currently, the only clear directive is that healthcare workers and residents of long-term care facilities go first—and no industry reps dispute that.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/fda-approves-pfizerbiontech-vaccine-raising-questions-counts-essential</link>
  <author>Eliza Carter</author>
  <categories>covid-19</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/fda-approves-pfizerbiontech-vaccine-raising-questions-counts-essential</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 15:11:18 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Disney Announces Disney+ Content Slate</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/2751/lion_king_meme.png'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Zoom out: Disney’s streaming unit is growing rapidly, but still incurring big losses ($2.8 billion in fiscal year 2020) that analysts expect to peak in the next two years.   But Disney isn't planning to follow WarnerMedia down that path just yet. WarnerMedia is planning joint theater-HBO Max premieres next year.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/disney-announces-disney-content-slate</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/disney-announces-disney-content-slate</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 15:11:18 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Jobless Claims, Food Insecurity Rise</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3180/usa.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;    Housing: A homebuying boom has added a collective $1 trillion in homeowner equity this year (an average of $17,000 per homeowner), according to CoreLogic. Applications from self-employed and gig workers for a federal program rose 48%, but that program expires Dec. 26.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/jobless-claims-food-insecurity-rise</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>economy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/jobless-claims-food-insecurity-rise</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 15:01:17 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>How to Host a Company Holiday Party During Covid?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/3o7TKQO1dMAnxRXlPW/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;   But ordinary times these are not.   One benefit of an online holiday party?   You’ll find everything you need right here. What is Slack’s video function but an opportunity for embarrassment waiting to happen? We aren’t so sure. “At corporate holiday parties, you typically get a handful of folks who end up drinking too much and do something embarrassing,” Ryan Costello of Event Farm told the WSJ.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/host-company-holiday-party-covid</link>
  <author>Eliza Carter</author>
  <categories>employers</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/host-company-holiday-party-covid</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 14:41:15 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Brew’s Weekly News Quiz: December 11</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3369/typeform_quiz_asset.png'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/brews-weekly-news-quiz-december-11</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>quiz</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/brews-weekly-news-quiz-december-11</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 11:21:15 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>ETFs: Everything You Need To Know, And Then Some</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3370/motley_fool_etf.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;One More ETF FYI As a beginner investment vehicle, ETFs can be a wonderful way to get a hang of the market and all of its fluctuations. If your brokerage charges you fees when you buy or sell ETF shares, its cost effectiveness can go out the window.   ETFs can track indexes from bonds to the NASDAQ, so find one that represents your own risk-tolerance and long-term plan.   An under-the-radar stock that could overperform. You can find out what the management team tracks their performance to, which is a good indicator to determine if you want that for your own portfolio. So good luck, and ETFs FTW. ETFs are not Always Cheaper It’s true, ETFs can be more cost-effective for the average investor than other funds.   In case you forgot, ETFs—or Exchange-Traded Funds—are funds that are traded on public exchanges just like a stock. If you read our Ultimate Guide to Investing, created with our friends at The Motley Fool, you’ll remember our comparison of ETFs to succulents.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/etfs-everything-need-know</link>
  <author>Morning Brew</author>
  <categories>investing</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/10/etfs-everything-need-know</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 07:41:21 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Google's Top Trending Searches in 2020</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/1875/google_logo_on_a_couch.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1) Cut men’s hair at home 2) plop hair 3) color your hair at home Lyrics: 1) WAP 🧐 Definitions: 1) WAP 🧐🧐🧐 1) My stimulus money 2) my refunds 3) Kansas City How to...</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/googles-top-trending-searches-2020?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>internet</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/googles-top-trending-searches-2020?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 03:01:22 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>‘Cyberpunk 2077’ Debuts to Enormous Hype and Positive Reviews</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/aTGwuEFyg6d8c/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;     The WSJ forecasts Cyberpunk 2077 will sell between 18 million and 25 million copies in its first month since a) it’s such a hyped game and b) it’s the only major title coming out during the holiday season. For real.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/cyberpunk-2077-debuts-enormous-hype-positive-reviews?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Toby Howell</author>
  <categories>videogames</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/cyberpunk-2077-debuts-enormous-hype-positive-reviews?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 03:01:22 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>International News Updates</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3365/indian_farm_protest.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;    Canada: The country’s health regulator approved Pfizer-BioNTech’s Covid-19 vaccine, becoming the second nation after the UK to do so.   Brazil: Passengers on a Gol Airlines flight from Sao Paulo to Porto Alegre were the first in nearly two years to travel on a Boeing 737 Max, which returned to commercial service yesterday.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/international-news-updates?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>around-the-world</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/international-news-updates?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 03:01:22 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Facebook Faces Two Antitrust Lawsuits at the Federal and State Levels</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3366/facebook_butterfly.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;   Bottom line: These lawsuits probably aren't the Jake Paul to Facebook’s Nate Robinson...   Yesterday, the twin investigations emerged from their chrysalises into full-fledged lawsuits.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/facebook-faces-two-antitrust-lawsuits-federal-state-levels?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Toby Howell</author>
  <categories>social-media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/facebook-faces-two-antitrust-lawsuits-federal-state-levels?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 03:01:22 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Airbnb Goes Public After Turbulent Year for Travel</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/W12WAzuqod9VS/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  The company had a roller-coaster year. If this week’s IPOs were a music festival, DoorDash would be the opener that rocked so hard everyone started moshing. As a public company, Airbnb will face a number of challenges, including angry city officials, concerns over safety, and a rising number of professional hosts who threaten Airbnb’s identity as a platform that connects people with... To swing the pendulum back toward individuals, Airbnb is creating a host endowment fund through its IPO to invest in the people who make its platform work.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/airbnb-goes-public-turbulent-year-travel?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>markets</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/airbnb-goes-public-turbulent-year-travel?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 03:01:21 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Airbnb Goes Public After Turbulent Year for Travel</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/W12WAzuqod9VS/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  The company had a roller-coaster year. If this week’s IPOs were a music festival, DoorDash would be the opener that rocked so hard everyone started moshing. As a public company, Airbnb will face a number of challenges, including angry city officials, concerns over safety, and a rising number of professional hosts who threaten Airbnb’s identity as a platform that connects people with...   Just because you survived the travel industry’s worst downturn ever doesn’t mean you can nap.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/airbnb-goes-public-turbulent-year-travel</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>markets</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/airbnb-goes-public-turbulent-year-travel</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 14:51:16 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Facebook Faces Two Antitrust Lawsuits at the Federal and State Levels</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3366/facebook_butterfly.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;   Bottom line: Facebook stock barely budged on the announcement, so these lawsuits probably aren't the Jake Paul to Facebook’s Nate Robinson.   Yesterday, the twin investigations emerged from their chrysalises into full-fledged lawsuits.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/facebook-faces-two-antitrust-lawsuits-federal-state-levels</link>
  <author>Toby Howell</author>
  <categories>social-media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/facebook-faces-two-antitrust-lawsuits-federal-state-levels</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 14:36:15 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>International News Updates</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3365/indian_farm_protest.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;    Canada: The country’s health regulator approved Pfizer-BioNTech’s Covid-19 vaccine, becoming the second nation after the UK to do so. It’s a tense issue considering more than 40% of India’s workforce is employed in agriculture. The laws loosened some rules around the pricing and storage of crops, and farmers argue the deregulation will devastate their incomes.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/international-news-updates</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>around-the-world</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/international-news-updates</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 14:36:15 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>‘Cyberpunk 2077’ Debuts to Enormous Hype and Positive Reviews</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/aTGwuEFyg6d8c/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;     The WSJ forecasts Cyberpunk 2077 will sell between 18 million and 25 million copies in its first month since a) it’s such a hyped game and b) it’s the only major title coming out during the holiday season.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/cyberpunk-2077-debuts-enormous-hype-positive-reviews</link>
  <author>Toby Howell</author>
  <categories>video-games</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/cyberpunk-2077-debuts-enormous-hype-positive-reviews</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 14:36:15 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Google's Top Trending Searches in 2020</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/1875/google_logo_on_a_couch.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1) Cut men’s hair at home 2) plop hair 3) color your hair at home Lyrics: 1) WAP 🧐 Definitions: 1) WAP 🧐🧐🧐 1) My stimulus money 2) my refunds 3) Kansas City How to...</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/googles-top-trending-searches-2020</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>internet</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/09/googles-top-trending-searches-2020</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 14:31:21 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Apple Unveils the AirPods Max, Its First Over-Ear Headphones</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://oslo-production.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/medium/asset/3355/airpods_max.jpg'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you're looking for a new way to flex on your Zoom calls, Apple unveiled its first over-ear headphones yesterday, the AirPods Max. It'd be quite the flex. the headphones arrive Dec. 15, and Apple's workout service, Fitness+ ($9.99/mo.   Looking ahead...</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/08/apple-unveils-airpods-max-first-overear-headphones?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/08/apple-unveils-airpods-max-first-overear-headphones?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 03:01:15 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>HBO Max: Strong User Growth, But Fallout From Upending Theatrical Window Continues</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/OVtqvymKkkcTu/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;According to AT&amp;T CEO John Stankey, HBO Max will notch 12.6 million activated accounts by today.   The straight-to-streaming decision has upset Hollywood creators. 30... In a fiery statement Monday night, filmmaker Christopher Nolan said, "They don't even understand what they're losing.  </description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/08/hbo-max-strong-user-growth-fallout-upending-theatrical-window-continues?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Eliza Carter</author>
  <categories>media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/08/hbo-max-strong-user-growth-fallout-upending-theatrical-window-continues?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 03:01:15 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Cybersecurity Giant FireEye Suffers Massive Attack</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/MF1kR4YmC2Z20/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  So this is like if an animal control office got infested by raccoons.   What FireEye is: the go-to security provider for governments and companies that suffer sophisticated hacks; for instance, it helped Sony and Equifax bulletproof their operations following breaches.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/08/cybersecurity-giant-fireeye-suffers-massive-attack?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Eliza Carter</author>
  <categories>cybersecurity</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2020/12/08/cybersecurity-giant-fireeye-suffers-massive-attack?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 03:01:15 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>

</channel>
</rss>
