<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <atom:link href="https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2022/06/01/users/1/web_requests/22/MorningBrew.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
 <atom:icon>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2022/06/01/favicon.ico</atom:icon>
 

 <title>MorningBrew as a feed</title>
 <description>This is a feed of recent MorningBrew articles published by Huginn</description>
 <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2022/06/01</link>
 <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 15:03:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
 <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 15:03:37 -0700</pubDate>
 <ttl>60</ttl>
 <item>
  <title>NFT industry hit with first insider trading charges</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-06-01/image-82f99d03eb0debfcdece199a48164080eb1e3079-480x262-gif/giphy(3).webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeWhether it’s an energy company’s stock or a JPEG of a _____ , you can’t make a trade based on secret information that you know will affect a security’s future price. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The former head of product at leading NFT marketplace OpenSea was charged with wire fraud and money laundering linked to the insider trading of NFTs, or non-fungible tokens. Why it matters: OpenSea is by far the largest NFT marketplace, with 65% market share. Once it was alerted of these transactions, OpenSea basically admitted that insider trading was taking place, and in September asked Chastain to leave the company after an investigation. —NF css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Therefore, a credibility hit to OpenSea is a credibility hit to the entire NFT industry. (As of March, Chastain was working on a new NFT project, Oval. It all started last September, when OpenSea users noticed something fishy was going on with crypto wallets belonging to Chastain. Nathaniel Chastain found that out yesterday.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/01/insider-trading-comes-to-nfts</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/06/01/insider-trading-comes-to-nfts</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 15:01:37 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Las Vegas chapels receive cease-and-desists for Elvis-themed weddings</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/26624f599fb00c68dbb0908a4fe8007fa8487977-5528x3664.jpg?rect=16,0,5496,3664&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Zoom out: ABG could be preparing for a resurgence of Elvis enthusiasm over the new Baz Luhrmann biopic, Elvis, which is set to release June 24. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe group that licenses Elvis Presley merch, Authentic Brands Group (ABG), sent cease-and-desist letters last month to a number of Las Vegas chapels in an attempt to quash their Elvis-themed weddings. —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! But ABG does claim the rights to the artist’s name and likeness, as well as the words “Elvis,” “Elvis Presley,” and “The King of Rock and Roll.” How many people want Elvis to marry them? Melody Willis-Williams, president of Vegas Weddings and Viva Las Vegas Weddings, told the Las Vegas Review Journal that she does thousands of sequined, “Burning Love”-esque weddings every year. The details: Nevada law says ABG can’t stop Elvis impersonators from shaking their hips any more than parents in the ’60s. The trademark battle is an existential threat to the small chapels’ post-pandemic recovery and Vegas’s $2 billion wedding industry.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/cease-and-desists-for-elvis-themed-weddings</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/cease-and-desists-for-elvis-themed-weddings</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 15:01:36 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Median worker pay at big companies is up</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-05-31/image-4fc4cdf060d47b4b1e6dc9e78f8f77dea6a1b01d-480x270-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Hiring sprees led to big shifts. ) Other interesting findings:12 out of the top 25 best compensated median employees worked at tech companies. At the majority of S&amp;P 500 companies, median worker pay is higher than 2019 levels—including 150 companies that reported an increase of 10% or more. —MK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! In 2019, 56 companies reported the median worker’s compensation to be less than $30,000, compared to 41 in 2021. Delta hired 13% of its total workforce in 2021 (11,000 people), so its median worker received 41% less compared to 2019. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeJust like they’re required to disclose top executive pay, US publicly traded companies are required to disclose the compensation of the median worker from their global staffs. (Netflix’s median employee makes around $200k. More than 140 companies reported that their median employee makes six figures, proving your parents’ advice to “write Netflix an email and ask them to let you make a movie” is pretty shrewd after all. That’s likely due to higher costs from inflation eating up wage increases, and the fact that CEO pay increased as well (up 31% from 2020, to $20 million). Retail pay has improved.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/median-worker-pay-big-companies-is-up?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Labor</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/median-worker-pay-big-companies-is-up?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 02:09:37 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The UK’s new visa program targets elite grads</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/53f0b4fb8ac896854649709ad568e4731f818fd1-1200x675.jpg?rect=94,0,1013,675&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. If you’ve graduated from one of the world’s 50 best universities within the last five years, you’re eligible for a two- or three-year visa—no job offer required. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeVery Important People, step aside: The UK just dropped a new immigration program for what it’s calling “High Potential Individuals.” —JW</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/UK-new-program-high-potential-individual-visa?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Education</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/UK-new-program-high-potential-individual-visa?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 02:09:37 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Biden to Powell: Inflation is your problem, buddy</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/4494a0677404bedb1b5b90b4df8bc5215a623b4c-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The Federal Reserve is intended to shape monetary policy independent of the US federal government, and that’s for one primary reason: Short-term political considerations shouldn’t influence the Fed chair’s decisions on what’s best for the economy in the long term. Most recent presidents have let the Fed do its thing without exerting pressure, but one exception is former President Trump.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/31/biden-tells-powell-inflation-is-his-problem-to-fix?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Economy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/31/biden-tells-powell-inflation-is-his-problem-to-fix?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 02:09:36 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Biden tells Powell inflation is his problem to fix</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/4494a0677404bedb1b5b90b4df8bc5215a623b4c-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The Federal Reserve is intended to shape monetary policy independent of the US federal government, and that’s for one primary reason: Short-term political considerations shouldn’t influence the Fed chair’s decisions on what’s best for the economy in the long term. Most recent presidents have let the Fed do its thing without exerting pressure, but one exception is former President Trump.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/31/biden-tells-powell-inflation-is-his-problem-to-fix</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Economy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/31/biden-tells-powell-inflation-is-his-problem-to-fix</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 15:16:17 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The UK’s new visa program targets elite grads</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/53f0b4fb8ac896854649709ad568e4731f818fd1-1200x675.jpg?rect=94,0,1013,675&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. If you’ve graduated from one of the world’s 50 best universities within the last five years, you’re eligible for a two- or three-year visa—no job offer required. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeVery Important People, step aside: The UK just dropped a new immigration program for what it’s calling High Potential Individuals. —JW</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/UK-new-program-high-potential-individual-visa</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Education</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/UK-new-program-high-potential-individual-visa</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 15:01:16 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Median worker pay at big companies is up</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-05-31/image-4fc4cdf060d47b4b1e6dc9e78f8f77dea6a1b01d-480x270-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Hiring sprees led to big shifts. At the majority of S&amp;P 500 companies, median worker pay has increased from 2019 levels—including 150 companies that reported an increase of 10% or more. —MK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! In 2019, 56 companies reported a median worker compensation of less than $30,000, compared to 41 in 2021. Delta hired 13% of its total workforce in 2021 (11,000 people), so its median worker received 41% less compared to 2019. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeJust like they’re required to disclose top executive pay, US publicly traded companies are required to disclose the compensation of the median worker from their global staff. More than 140 companies reported that their median employee makes six figures, proving your parents’ advice to “write Netflix an email and ask them to let you make a movie” is pretty shrewd after all (Netflix’s median employee makes around $200k). Other interesting findings:12 out of the top 25 best compensated median employees worked at tech companies.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/median-worker-pay-big-companies-is-up</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Labor</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/median-worker-pay-big-companies-is-up</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 15:01:15 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Why crypto crashed, and what happens next</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/2d15b8a7bdedc0e7961e65cd26d92a895ed1f9c5-6000x4200.jpg?rect=0,100,6000,4000&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Ignoring what happened with Terra’s luna—which is not a true stablecoin because it wasn’t actually backed by any reserves, even though it was pegged to the dollar—imagine if you’re in a Facebook-type metaverse and want to conduct a transaction with another user. Crypto began to act like a risk asset. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. That’s a true use case. To me it’s all Web3, whereas crypto really goes back only to the blockchain. The first one occurred [in early 2015] when bitcoin stood by itself as a proven cryptocurrency, and there was potentially some investor disillusionment early on about what they held. There is a valuation framework that hasn’t been created yet but could be, showing true value for these blockchain operating systems, subsequently prompting public policy leaders to change their views on these assets. But because they used new software architecture, they attached a smart contract to the cover art so when the buyer sells it at significant multiples, 10% will go back to the original owners, again split between them. Most Morning Brew readers saw the cryptocurrency market plummet in early May. There’s been a lot of anxiety since—notable for an investment community that gave rise to the battle cry “HODL,” as in “hold on for dear life.” Many of our smarter investors are using this correction to do the work to understand the space better. When you say “crypto,” you’re not just talking about currencies, are you? They’re real and people have true use cases for them: supply chain efficiency, FEMA claim reduction, things to power the metaverses of the future. First, she didn’t understand how any crypto asset had intrinsic value. The total value of the crypto market was $780 billion in January 2021. As global head of crypto and digital assets strategy at Bank of America, it’s Shah’s job to figure out what’s happening for the second largest bank in the US. It’s not that there’s any end to this sector. Paul Krugman in the New York Times comes to mind; in May he wrote: “Cryptocurrencies play almost no role in economic transactions other than speculation in crypto markets themselves.” What’s another killer application of crypto?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/31/why-crypto-crashed-and-what-happens-next</link>
  <author>Andrew Nusca</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/31/why-crypto-crashed-and-what-happens-next</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 13:02:25 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Marriage moves to the metaverse</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/b671f55accc638d5d5b6a85387c0b167400e86f5-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. ] to be decentralized and to allow a contract to continue on and on,” Rose said. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThough the Hurleys’ Decentraland wedding was a novelty, weddings in online virtual worlds aren’t particularly new—they’ve piqued the interest of gamers for years. “You think, too, ‘Okay, the virtual is automatically going to be less expensive as well,’ which is why you can see it appealing to a lot of people,” said Rachel Willis, a wedding planner who is watching the metaverse wedding industry but has yet to have a client who wants one. But the over-the-top apparel and man–animal hybrid didn’t bother Candice and Ryan, because the “anything goes” style of their guests fit perfectly with the couple’s location: Decentraland, an Ethereum-based virtual world where people can play games or buy land in the form of NFTs.“What’s great about the metaverse is you can just do whatever you want,” Candice Hurley told Morning Brew, noting the avatar she used in the 3D, virtual world wasn’t a reflection of her real-life self. ) Klaus Bandisch, wedding planner and owner of Just Maui Weddings, began offering meta “marriages” in Hawaiian destinations this year, though for now he’s focused on vow renewals because of state laws regulating remote weddings. ) “What we’ve developed is a blockchain marriage that’s recognized on the blockchain.” Those who hold virtual celebrations also need to wed in person with an officiant. Candice and Ryan aren’t the first couple to exchange vows in the metaverse. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. Then, they ran out of wedding favors. Blockchain technology, or an online public ledger, is largely associated with the transfer of cryptocurrencies, but it can potentially store important documents, like property deeds or marriage licenses, in a transparent and secure way. It can be just as expensive, but the realm of why people would decide to go with a virtual wedding…the sky’s the limit, really.” It wasn’t long after people started interacting online with avatars in virtual gaming worlds like Second Life and Runescape that people began to meet and wed in symbolic ceremonies, sometimes to advance in the game, and sometimes because they had caught feelings for the other player. Rose said her law firm has quoted people between $2,500 and $15,000 for meta weddings so far, depending on the customizations they choose. Candice and Ryan Hurley's avatars seen during their Decentraland wedding. Others were wearing crowns or brightly colored wigs, and one wore a bikini top with plaid pants. But as the lines between the virtual and tangible worlds fade, it may become more common to take vows in the metaverse. “People trust the new dating technology more and more, and the stigma of meeting online seems to have worn off,” Michael Rosenfeld, the study’s author, said of the findings.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/20/marriage-moves-to-the-metaverse</link>
  <author>Amanda Hoover</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/20/marriage-moves-to-the-metaverse</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 07:56:24 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The week ahead: May 31</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/2e1e920d45b22866afcdddef89438404fe1d593d-1967x1356.jpg?rect=0,22,1967,1311&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe UK throws Elizabeth II a party. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Ukraine war milestone: Saturday will mark 100 days since Russia first invaded Ukraine. The Boston Celtics and the Golden State Warriors will face off in the NBA Finals beginning on Thursday.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/30/the-week-ahead-may-31?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/30/the-week-ahead-may-31?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:01:19 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Mona Lisa smeared with cake in apparent climate protest</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/949d306a1df105b6dfd73b1d96095f07c49649e3-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Good news is that Leonardo da Vinci’s masterpiece, probably the most recognizable painting in the world, was not damaged by the caking. A man who disguised himself as an elderly woman in a wheelchair smeared cake on the iconic painting’s glass case at the Louvre yesterday in what appeared to be a climate protest. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe “Mona Lisa” is protected by bulletproof glass, and yesterday we found out that it’s properly shielded against cake, too. Big picture: Something about the “Mona Lisa” gets people riled up, and yesterday’s attack was not the first time the portrait’s been messed with…It was stolen by three Italian handymen in 1911, which actually helped boost its status.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/30/mona-lisa-smeared-with-cake-in-apparent-climate-protest?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Culture</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/30/mona-lisa-smeared-with-cake-in-apparent-climate-protest?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:01:19 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Pools, restaurants brace for another summer of worker shortages</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-05-30/image-3a32b937df77169a4471bf3ac1379989fc3a8470-480x276-gif/giphy(2).webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. On the one hand, Americans are basically done with home-cooked meals. Given the shortage of workers in other age cohorts, more teens are working now than they have since the 2008–09 financial crisis. Even after dangling a $2,500 incentive, the city can’t find enough staff. And a lack of lifeguards could prevent one-third of the 300,000+ public pools in the US from opening this summer, the American Lifeguard Association warned. How to explain it?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/30/pools-restaurants-brace-for-another-summer-of-worker-shortages?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Labor</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/30/pools-restaurants-brace-for-another-summer-of-worker-shortages?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:01:18 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The week ahead: May 31</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/2e1e920d45b22866afcdddef89438404fe1d593d-1967x1356.jpg?rect=0,22,1967,1311&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe UK throws Elizabeth II a party. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Ukraine war milestone: Saturday will mark 100 days since Russia first invaded Ukraine. The Boston Celtics and the Golden State Warriors will face off in the NBA Finals beginning on Thursday.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/30/the-week-ahead-may-31</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/30/the-week-ahead-may-31</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 16:16:19 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Pools, restaurants brace for another summer of worker shortages</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-05-30/image-3a32b937df77169a4471bf3ac1379989fc3a8470-480x276-gif/giphy(2).webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. On the one hand, Americans are basically done with home-cooked meals. Given the shortage of workers in other age cohorts, more teens are working now than they have since the 2008–09 financial crisis. Even after dangling a $2,500 cash incentive, the city can’t find enough staff. How to explain it? css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/30/pools-restaurants-brace-for-another-summer-of-worker-shortages</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Labor</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/30/pools-restaurants-brace-for-another-summer-of-worker-shortages</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 16:16:19 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Mona Lisa smeared with cake in apparent climate protest</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/949d306a1df105b6dfd73b1d96095f07c49649e3-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Good news is that Leonardo da Vinci’s masterpiece, probably the most recognizable painting in the world, was not damaged by the caking. A man who disguised himself as an elderly woman in a wheelchair smeared cake on the iconic painting’s glass case at the Louvre yesterday in what appeared to be a climate protest. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe “Mona Lisa” is protected by bulletproof glass, and yesterday we found out that it’s properly shielded against cake, too. Big picture: Something about the “Mona Lisa” gets people riled up, and yesterday’s attack was not the first time the portrait’s been messed with…It was stolen by three Italian handymen in 1911, which actually helped boost its status.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/30/mona-lisa-smeared-with-cake-in-apparent-climate-protest</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Culture</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/30/mona-lisa-smeared-with-cake-in-apparent-climate-protest</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 16:16:18 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Crypto money is shaking up US politics</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/0da6e939ff9437c1a33651530f91381663982af2-7794x5196.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. So how is SBF spending his money? On a podcast this week, Bankman-Fried (nicknamed SBF) said that he expects to give at least $100 million in political donations for the upcoming 2024 election, and could spend up to $1 billion if Donald Trump were a factor. )Some think that SBF has other motives with his political giving. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/27/crypto-money-is-shaking-up-us-politics?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/27/crypto-money-is-shaking-up-us-politics?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 15:01:27 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Make it work: How should I utilize a mentor?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7b6de1bb891bb0dd9e289abb0a591582a5da30e6-1503x603.png?rect=299,0,905,603&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. In fact, one of the ways I would look to utilize this mentor is to gain access to the people that they know. The key to figuring out how to utilize a mentor starts with understanding a mentor’s purpose. In order to best utilize your mentor, you’ll want to 1) make sure they know what problems you’re running into 2) have some level of visibility into your work and 3) have insight into your short- and long-term goals. Most were not officially assigned and, sadly, none were actually named Mentor.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/27/make-it-work-how-should-i-utilize-a-mentor?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Shane Loughnane</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/27/make-it-work-how-should-i-utilize-a-mentor?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 15:01:26 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Icebreakers with…Tyler Cowen and Daniel Gross, authors of Talent</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/1eda1828318fa99102449d54d21519c7eeffe374-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Then they hired Allen Klein, which led to great discord within the group and damaged their financial affairs. There are also biases when men interview women, at least on average. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. More generally, many interviewers are trying too hard to look for people who are a lot like them. To help us become better talent spotters in a world where spotting talent is increasingly important, economist Tyler Cowen and venture capitalist and entrepreneur Daniel Gross wrote a book on the art and science of finding talent at the highest level. Many highly successful individuals are terrible at talent assessment. This interview has been condensed.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/26/icebreakers-with-tyler-cowen-and-daniel-gross-authors-of-talent?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/26/icebreakers-with-tyler-cowen-and-daniel-gross-authors-of-talent?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 15:01:24 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Stock watch: May 29</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/2430107219a980161be4c38e063f5534ba59226a-1500x2000.png?rect=0,500,1500,1000&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/stock-watch-may-29?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/stock-watch-may-29?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 15:01:22 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Here’s what the ‘Planes, Trains and Automobiles’ trip would cost today</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/a61090f8155cb1c4818e6ea82f35ed995240bc6e-1024x664.jpg?rect=14,0,996,664&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Here’s our pricing breakdown, in case you’re thinking of reliving the worst weekend of all time:A 6:00pm first-class flight from LGA to O’Hare before a holiday weekend: ~$400Midtown Manhattan car (let’s say Uber) to LGA: ~$85 (x2 since Del steals the first)Uber to a hotel after being diverted to Wichita: ~$25Last-minute hotel in Wichita: ~$100 a nightAmtrak from Kansas City (closest available location) to Chicago: ~$200 (x2)Bus from Jefferson City to St. Louis (once the train breaks down): ~$30 (x2)Rental car in St. Louis: likely unavailable, but ~$210 (x2 since movie Neal’s car is missing)Illinois hotel: ~$150Chicago L train: $2.50 (x2)Not included: gas, a speeding ticket, a robbery, or the cost of their destroyed rental car. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. —MK</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/travel-movies-trip-cost-planes-trains-automobiles?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Travel</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/travel-movies-trip-cost-planes-trains-automobiles?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 08:02:15 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Camping is holding on to its pandemic popularity in 2022</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-05-27/image-737222a627307e1ee7d02fc3a980865ae823efdc-500x296-gif/giphy-1.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. 33% more people are shopping on Amazon for camping tents this year compared to 2019, and demand for other outdoor gear (lanterns, backpacks, camp stoves) has also risen by double digits, per data analytics company Pattern. —JW Zoom out: Getaway’s Chief Experience Officer Carlos Becil told the Brew via a spokesperson, “Between inflation, the stock market, and recession fears, people have a strong desire to find ways to disconnect from the stress and spend time in nature to help them reconnect with themselves, and their loved ones.” css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/camping-is-holding-on-to-its-pandemic-popularity-in-2022?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Travel</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/camping-is-holding-on-to-its-pandemic-popularity-in-2022?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 08:02:14 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Brew readers share their travel hot takes</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/1eb29114460253a08d5fcb7b0f1f40f54d722ce2-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. ? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Curated playlist: 54%Podcast: 20%Audiobook: 12%No aux needed—road trips are for the local radio stations: 10%Nothing, I prefer silence: 4%Do you use cruise control on the highway?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/27/brew-readers-share-their-travel-hot-takes?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/27/brew-readers-share-their-travel-hot-takes?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 08:02:14 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Hospitality industry evolves to accommodate a surge in pet travel</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-137f015d55ad89423ff6ec2fe524581c764aabe4-480x249-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. But this is pet owners we’re talking about here—so a bustling luxury pet travel market has also sprung up. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeWhen we first announced we were publishing a travel newsletter, requests flooded in around one topic specifically: traveling with pets. While road tripping with your pet has likely never been easier, flying with one has gotten a lot more complicated and restrictive during Covid. The surge in pet-related travel amenities appears to be yet another one of those simmering trends that the pandemic sent boiling. Lists of the best pet carriers for travel (CNN, HuffPost)Two websites that help you find pet-friendly accommodation. Big picture: The best pet-friendly vacation might be one that’s not too far away. Pet-friendly travel is one of the hottest trends in the industry. Nearly one in five households (~23 million Americans) acquired a cat or dog since the beginning of the Covid outbreak, the ASPCA reported last year. A Santa Barbara hotel, El Encanto, offers a gourmet dog menu with seasonal fish for $15/plate, followed by an herbal tea blend at $5/bowl.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/27/hospitality-industry-evolves-to-accommodate-a-surge-in-pet-travel?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/27/hospitality-industry-evolves-to-accommodate-a-surge-in-pet-travel?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 08:02:13 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The best weekend getaways in the US, as recommended by Morning Brew readers</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/6ac1ce03502199bf59b9af84638fa85290df12da-6144x4096.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Newport, RI for the mansions, of course. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. ) Inniswood Metro Gardens just 20 minutes north of downtown Columbus. Mackinac Island in Lake HuronHolland, MI, for breweries and lake views. Lake Winnipesaukee, the largest lake in New Hampshire. Onfokus/Getty ImagesBig Bear Lake in San Bernardino National Forest. Point Reyes National SeashoreCalistoga, a tiny town in Napa Valley with the Old Faithful Geyser of California. Ojai, a small city in a valley in the Topatopa Mountains. Just southwest of LA, the resort town on Catalina Island. Montauk on the east end of Long Island. Reno, NV, known as “The Biggest Little City in the World.” Michel Arnaud/Getty ImagesFredericksburg, TX, is known for its wineries and is located about two hours west of AustinDinosaur Valley State Park, an hour southwest of Fort Worth. Asbury Park, a bustling seaside town on the Jersey Shore. Gaul/Getty ImagesHighlands, NC, a town in the Nantahala National Forest at an elevation of 4,118 feet. The weird West Texas town of Marfa.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/26/the-best-weekend-getaways-in-the-us-as-recommended-by-morning-brew-readers</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Travel</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/26/the-best-weekend-getaways-in-the-us-as-recommended-by-morning-brew-readers</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 11:21:23 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Hospitality industry evolves to accommodate a surge in pet travel</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-137f015d55ad89423ff6ec2fe524581c764aabe4-480x249-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. But this is pet owners we’re talking about here—so a bustling luxury pet travel market has also sprung up. While road tripping with your pet has likely never been easier, flying with one has gotten a lot more complicated and restrictive during Covid. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeWhen we first announced we were publishing a travel newsletter, requests flooded in around one topic specifically: traveling with pets. Big picture: The best pet-friendly vacation might be one that’s not too far away. Pet-friendly travel is one of the hottest trends in the industry. Lists of the best pet carriers for travel (CNN, HuffPost)Two websites that help you find pet-friendly accommodation. Nearly one in five households (~23 million Americans) acquired a cat or dog since the beginning of the Covid outbreak, the ASPCA reported last year. The surge in pet-related travel amenities appears to be yet another one of those simmering trends that the pandemic sent boiling. Metropolitan at the 9 in Cleveland has an indoor dog park. And finally, here are some resources to help you plan the perfect pet vacation. You can get a facial and nail care done alongside your dog at the Lygon Arms in England’s Cotswolds for about $218. This presents a new group of customers to be won, and many hotels are racing to offer the friendliest pet accommodations around.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/27/hospitality-industry-evolves-to-accommodate-a-surge-in-pet-travel</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/27/hospitality-industry-evolves-to-accommodate-a-surge-in-pet-travel</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 10:52:10 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Here’s what the “Planes, Trains and Automobiles” trip would cost today</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/a61090f8155cb1c4818e6ea82f35ed995240bc6e-1024x664.jpg?rect=14,0,996,664&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Here’s our pricing breakdown, in case you’re thinking of reliving the worst weekend of all time:A 6:00pm first-class flight from LGA to O’Hare before a holiday weekend: ~$400Midtown Manhattan car (let’s say Uber) to LGA: ~$85 (x2 since Del steals the first)Uber to a hotel after being diverted to Wichita: ~$25Last-minute hotel in Wichita: ~$100 a nightAmtrak from Kansas City (closest available location) to Chicago: ~$200 (x2)Bus from Jefferson City to St. Louis (once the train breaks down): ~$30 (x2)Rental car in St. Louis: likely unavailable, but ~$210 (x2 since movie Neal’s car is missing)Illinois hotel: ~$150Chicago L train: $2.50 (x2)Not included: gas, a speeding ticket, a robbery, or the cost of their destroyed rental car. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. —MK</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/travel-movies-trip-cost-planes-trains-automobiles</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Travel</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/travel-movies-trip-cost-planes-trains-automobiles</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 10:31:08 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Camping is holding on to its pandemic popularity in 2022</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-05-27/image-c1c6af1677754f4907ebc1ae5d0bfc8a0629d54c-500x296-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. 33% more people are shopping on Amazon for camping tents this year compared to 2019, and demand for other outdoor gear (lanterns, backpacks, camp stoves) has also risen by double digits, per data analytics company Pattern. —JW Zoom out: Chief Experience Officer Carlos Becil told the Brew via a spokesperson, “Between inflation, the stock market, and recession fears, people have a strong desire to find ways to disconnect from the stress and spend time in nature to help them reconnect with themselves, and their loved ones.” css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/camping-is-holding-on-to-its-pandemic-popularity-in-2022</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Travel</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/camping-is-holding-on-to-its-pandemic-popularity-in-2022</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 10:02:10 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Stock watch: May 29</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/2430107219a980161be4c38e063f5534ba59226a-1500x2000.png?rect=0,500,1500,1000&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/stock-watch-may-29</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/stock-watch-may-29</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 07:31:08 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Crypto money is shaking up US politics</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/0da6e939ff9437c1a33651530f91381663982af2-7794x5196.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. So how is SBF spending his money? On a podcast this week, Bankman-Fried (nicknamed SBF) said that he expects to give at least $100 million in political donations for the upcoming 2024 election, and could spend up to $1 billion if Donald Trump were a factor. )Some think that SBF has other motives with his political giving. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/27/crypto-money-is-shaking-up-us-politics</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/27/crypto-money-is-shaking-up-us-politics</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 06:16:08 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Make it work: How should I utilize a mentor?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7b6de1bb891bb0dd9e289abb0a591582a5da30e6-1503x603.png?rect=299,0,905,603&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. In fact, one of the ways I would look to utilize this mentor is to gain access to the people that they know. The key to figuring out how to utilize a mentor starts with understanding a mentor’s purpose. In order to best utilize your mentor, you’ll want to 1) make sure they know what problems you’re running into 2) have some level of visibility into your work and 3) have insight into your short- and long-term goals. Most were not officially assigned and, sadly, none were actually named Mentor.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/27/make-it-work-how-should-i-utilize-a-mentor</link>
  <author>Shane Loughnane</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/27/make-it-work-how-should-i-utilize-a-mentor</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 05:56:16 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Icebreakers with…Tyler Cowen and Daniel Gross, authors of Talent</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/1eda1828318fa99102449d54d21519c7eeffe374-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Then they hired Allen Klein, which led to great discord within the group and damaged their financial affairs. There are also biases when men interview women, at least on average. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. More generally, many interviewers are trying too hard to look for people who are a lot like them. To help us become better talent spotters in a world where spotting talent is increasingly important, economist Tyler Cowen and venture capitalist and entrepreneur Daniel Gross wrote a book on the art and science of finding talent at the highest level. Many highly successful individuals are terrible at talent assessment. This interview has been condensed.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/26/icebreakers-with-tyler-cowen-and-daniel-gross-authors-of-talent</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/26/icebreakers-with-tyler-cowen-and-daniel-gross-authors-of-talent</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 05:42:12 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Analysts think ‘Top Gun: Maverick’ will be Tom Cruise’s biggest opening ever</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/171eaf8c4864f084b15d7932a436128e68659896-2560x1072.jpg?rect=476,0,1608,1072&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. For Hollywood, Top Gun: Maverick is a throwback to a film industry built on star power, practical effects, and spectacle (as opposed to the raw sex appeal of Paddington that dominates today’s box office). Like audiences, movie studios aren’t exactly rushing back into theaters.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/top-gun-maverick-tom-cruise-biggest-opening-analysts</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/top-gun-maverick-tom-cruise-biggest-opening-analysts</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 15:06:16 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The global helium shortage is getting serious</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/8804051591dbb1efb3a4cb6d0cca4df62dafa8c7-4787x3186.jpg?rect=4,0,4779,3186&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The university said it isn’t providing balloons to fans due to a helium shortage. Zoom out: In FY 2013, helium cost about $65 per thousand cubic feet. Because of the global helium shortage, the National Weather Service warned that it would need to reduce the frequency of weather balloon launches, according to Axios.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/global-helium-shortage</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/global-helium-shortage</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 15:06:15 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Sequoia Capital warns of a “Crucible Moment” for startups</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-05-26/image-e6059d9d1f672818786a14a62049faa4d8e31439-500x213-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Silicon Valley startup incubator Y Combinator sent an email to its founders with a Game of Thrones season one vibe. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. It’s one of at least 16 tech companies that let more than 7,200 employees go this week. These days, it’s not the only one sounding the alarm for startups. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. The tech rout isn’t just cyclical—it’s well-earned, and overdue. (Bloomberg)</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/26/sequoia-capital-warns-of-a-crucible-moment-for-startups</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/26/sequoia-capital-warns-of-a-crucible-moment-for-startups</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 14:51:13 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Brew's summer '22 reading list</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-05-26/image-425946a319ba8e8fbe5cbb7078b48844cbf358d2-480x273-gif/simpsonedit.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Freezing Order reads like a thriller, but it’s the true story of how Russia ended up interfering in the 2016 US presidential election. Order these books so your summer reading is sitting on your porch when you get back on Monday. Read the novel so you can be that person who says the book was better. How many more times can you go through Harry Styles’s new album? css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. Bestsellers worth the airport price-gouging:Why not explore every possible thing that could go wrong this summer?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/the-brews-summer-2022-reading-list</link>
  <author>Rohan Anthony</author>
  <categories>Books</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/the-brews-summer-2022-reading-list</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 08:47:12 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Apple’s self-repair program disappoints right-to-repair advocates</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/9323a9f38e000cc0a5b96829b14e84cb0e2a203f-755x439.png?rect=48,0,659,439&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The backstory: Last month, Apple launched its Self Service Repair Store, which allows customers to buy parts for select Apple devices they can repair at home. Apple said in a white paper last month, “For the vast majority of customers, the safest and most reliable repair is achieved through an Apple Store. —JW css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Bottom line: Critics say Apple doesn’t want customers to repair their phones at home, and, when this program proves to be unpopular, will use it as evidence against right-to-repair initiatives.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/apple-s-self-repair-program-disappoints-right-to-repair-advocates?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/apple-s-self-repair-program-disappoints-right-to-repair-advocates?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:01:17 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Chelsea FC is latest English soccer club to be gobbled up by American investors</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/8e7315d4a0b823cc4def411879fce52da56c3ff8-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIt’s one of our favorite conversation starters: If you’re a rich American investor looking to buy a sports franchise, which league would you choose? Chelsea joins a growing list of Premier League clubs backed by American money. For real moguls and not just wannabes like us, that answer is increasingly the English Premier League.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/25/chelsea-fc-is-latest-english-soccer-club?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/25/chelsea-fc-is-latest-english-soccer-club?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:01:16 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>After the Texas elementary school shooting, what comes next?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/cab415468bcf8c27921cbcb69c18199f99c15a83-4000x2668.jpg?rect=0,0,4000,2667&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. The gunman in Tuesday’s massacre legally purchased two AR platform rifles in the days following his 18th birthday last week. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. One potential road to compromise: “Red flag” legislation, or laws that would allow authorities to temporarily take guns away from individuals who are deemed a threat to themselves or others. Texas has among the least restrictive gun laws in the US, and lawmakers have actually relaxed them in the state over the past few years, according to the Texas Tribune. And at the federal level, gun reform is effectively frozenSenate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer added votes on two background check bills to the chamber’s calendar, both of which would expand checks for sales at gun shows and online. Democratic lawmakers renewed their calls for gun legislation, but were once again confronted with the fact that the numbers for enacting policy are stacked against them due to Republican opposition. Even with a slight majority in the House, Democrats are evenly split in the Senate and would need 10 Republicans to vote alongside them there. —MM They don’t think access to guns contributes to mass shootings. Other links to stay up to date about the shootingMeta said the gunman discussed his planned attack in private messages on Facebook about 30 minutes before the shooting. “The time to stop the next shooting is now, and you are doing nothing,” O’Rourke said. Alabama Sen. Tommy Tuberville said yesterday that “Guns are not the problem. For instance, In 2013, the bipartisan duo of Democratic Sen. Joe Manchin and Republican Sen. Pat Toomey introduced a compromise bill that would require background checks for commercial sales of guns.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/after-texas-elementary-school-shooting-what-comes-next?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Education</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/after-texas-elementary-school-shooting-what-comes-next?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:01:16 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>After the Texas elementary school shooting, what comes next?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/cab415468bcf8c27921cbcb69c18199f99c15a83-4000x2668.jpg?rect=0,0,4000,2667&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. The gunman in Tuesday’s massacre legally purchased two AR platform rifles in the days following his 18th birthday last week. Historically, mass shootings haven’t led to much action from American lawmakers. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. One potential road to compromise: “Red flag” legislation, or laws that would allow authorities to temporarily take guns away from individuals who are deemed a threat to themselves or others. But gun laws have been loosened in the state in the past few years, reports the Texas Tribune. That includes a permitless carry bill passed, the Second Amendment Sanctuary Act (which means local agencies can’t enforce new federal gun laws), and a law that allows individuals as young as 18 to buy a handgun all passed last year. —MM Democrats could also try to change filibuster rules and allow a simple majority to pass gun reform, but Democratic Senators Joe Manchin and Kyrsten Sinema have vocally opposed messing with the rules. And currently, even with a slight majority in the House, Democrats are evenly split in the Senate and would need 10 Republicans to vote alongside them there. And don’t expect immediate action at the federal levelSenate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer added votes on two background check bills to the chamber’s calendar, both of which would expand checks for sales at gun shows and online. “The time to stop the next shooting is now, and you are doing nothing,” O’Rourke said. Other links to stay up to date about the shootingMeta said the gunman discussed his planned attack in private messages on Facebook about 30 minutes before the shooting.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/after-texas-elementary-school-shooting-what-comes-next</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Education</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/after-texas-elementary-school-shooting-what-comes-next</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 15:26:16 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>

</channel>
</rss>
