<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <atom:link href="https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2021/08/20/users/1/web_requests/22/MorningBrew.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
 <atom:icon>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2021/08/20/favicon.ico</atom:icon>
 

 <title>MorningBrew as a feed</title>
 <description>This is a feed of recent MorningBrew articles published by Huginn</description>
 <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2021/08/20</link>
 <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 14:39:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
 <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 14:39:09 -0700</pubDate>
 <ttl>60</ttl>
 <item>
  <title>The Great Havana Syndrome Mystery</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6335%2Fu_s_embassy_at_focus_of.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This summer, at least two US officials at the US Embassy in Germany felt so sick they couldn’t work. In the years since, reported Havana syndrome cases among US foreign officers have popped up in Moscow, China, London, Virginia, and, most recently, Vienna and Germany.  One recent victim, who was working at a US embassy in Europe, told the WSJ it was “striking” that some people hit with the attacks were working on Russia-related issues.  Turns out, they were suffering from an illness experienced by dozens of US diplomats and intelligence officers around the globe in recent years: Havana Syndrome.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/20/great-havana-syndrome-mystery</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>analysis</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/20/great-havana-syndrome-mystery</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 14:36:08 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Icebreakers With...E-Commerce Mogul Marc Lore</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6328%2Fmarc_lore.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; What is a fact that most people don’t know about you? When you have an idea for a business there always seems to be concern about telling too many people out of fear that someone will steal it. It doesn’t work like that.  What will be the most disruptive force in e-commerce in the next 10 years? Land appreciation is caused by primarily two things: First is when people build communities, other people want to join those communities and live in those locations. Share your idea with as many people as possible.  In the future buying something will be like having your own personal Jarvis. Sharing ideas with as many people as possible will help you shape your vision, plus it will help you recruit people. Having a really strong Chief People Officer can help set the culture and values and bring in the very best, most diverse talent. And now in the startups that I’m creating today, the Chief People Officer is typically the first hire, because people are the most important asset within a company. People will tell you it doesn’t make sense and why it won’t work. And it’s about being more equitable and giving citizens an ownership stake and, as the city does better, the residents do better. That was fun and interesting, but more interesting was that they were going to take the fastest time of the week and send the person to the US national team training camp.   It seems to me that the fair way to do it would be for all this land appreciation—appreciation caused by the people within the city—to benefit those citizens and come back to them. At the end of the month there were tryouts and the top 13 would make the US national team.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/20/icebreakers-withecommerce-mogul-marc-lore</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>qanda</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/20/icebreakers-withecommerce-mogul-marc-lore</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 13:51:10 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Brave New Crypto World</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5670%2Fcrypto_future.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Businesses &lt;3 bitcoin (and crypto in general)Thanks to BTC-bullish owner Mark Cuban, you can buy Dallas Mavericks tickets and merchandise in bitcoin. Crypto is getting hotter and hotterThe current market capitalization of all cryptocurrencies has soared to about $2 trillion¹; bitcoin alone is at around $850 billion.  Bottom line: Crypto is no longer niche. These trends help show that investors think crypto is a good place to park their money, even if governments are just making moves to regulate it now. is basically just the world these days. ²In April, crypto exchange Coinbase went public at a valuation of about $85 billion, showing there’s quite a bit of appetite for access to cryptos. You can also pay with bitcoin when you order the latest paperback plus some dish soap on Amazon. The water’s warm, and with Bakkt, you can swan-dive in, free of transaction fees and with as little as $10. But because of fractional coins and investment tools like futures and ETFs, you can invest as little as $5 in cryptocurrency.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/07/24/next-disruption-finance-yep-involves-crypto</link>
  <author>Morning Brew</author>
  <categories>finance</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/07/24/next-disruption-finance-yep-involves-crypto</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 12:26:13 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Is Your Newsletter...Newsworthy?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6331%2Freferral.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This allowed us to automate the referral process and spend that time thinking strategically about how to use that data to inform other, more important decisions. Here’s the happy ending—they were able to convert newsletter readers to paid subscribers. Time to get your newsletter act togetherNewsletters can be a powerful tool for media companies to establish robust connections with their audience, expand their reach, and grow revenue. More specifically, our referral program. Moral of this news story: Newsletters can be a tool to drive subscriber growth across your entire organization. While we’d like to think we’re pretty dang smart, it doesn't take a newsletter genius to know that people are more willing to try... By driving newsletter subscribers to its website, New York Magazine uncovered a strong conversion rate to becoming a paid subscriber within 90 days after signing up. This helped New York Magazine take action and drive One Great Story readers to more of the content that suited their taste, while simultaneously introducing them to New York Magazine’s full plate of offerings. Today, reader referrals significantly supplement our growth, accounting for 30% of our 3 million subscribers. New York Magazine used their newsletter, One Great Story, to drive subscription growth across the entire publication. New York Magazine partnered with Sailthru to figure out which topics One Great Story readers enjoyed most, the largest group (30%) ranked longform features as their top choice, followed by news analysis and profiles (20%).</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/20/newsletternewsworthy</link>
  <author>Morning Brew</author>
  <categories>marketing</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/20/newsletternewsworthy</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 11:11:09 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Amazon Is Reportedly Planning to Open Its Own Department Stores</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6318%2Famazon_shopping_cart.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The backstory: After opening its first brick-and-mortar bookstore in Seattle in 2015, Amazon has expanded its physical footprint to grocery and cashierless convenience stores. The company is planning to open several large brick-and-mortar retail locations in the US that resemble department stores, the WSJ reports. – SQ</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/amazon-reportedly-planning-open-department-stores?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Sherry Qin</author>
  <categories>retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/amazon-reportedly-planning-open-department-stores?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 03:02:12 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: August 20</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/d89EspFlEceJYM7LXV/giphy.gif?cid=ecf05e472xfxn6qwtx8fh3ysoddocss6qen1bwkbs4hxfnod&amp;rid=giphy.gif&amp;ct=g'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;That’s how one Mexican agave producer described the tequila boom to the LA Times. The number of applications to start new businesses in the US grew 24% last year to 4.3 million, the highest on record by far. (Year Zero) </description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/key-performance-indicators-august-20?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/key-performance-indicators-august-20?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 03:02:12 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Chip Shortages Continues to Hit Global Automakers</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/Q4MKucytzKYJ4elFhG/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Recent Covid-19 outbreaks in Southeast Asian manufacturing hubs mean the chip shortage could hamstring auto production into 2022.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/chip-shortages-continues-hit-global-automakers?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>auto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/chip-shortages-continues-hit-global-automakers?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 03:02:12 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Facebook Launches VR Meeting Space Called Workrooms</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6317%2Ffacebook_horizon_workrooms.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Zoom out: Workrooms is one part of a larger VR experience called Horizon that Facebook originally planned to launch last year. – JW Facebook’s announcement came right before the FTC refiled a lawsuit yesterday alleging the company has a “monopoly” on social networking. Or maybe clever timing? Bad timing?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/facebook-launches-vr-meeting-space-called-workrooms?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/facebook-launches-vr-meeting-space-called-workrooms?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 03:02:12 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>OnlyFans Will Ban Sexually Explicit Content in Surprising Pivot</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/yyp58Yx3Qk0TK/giphy.gif?cid=ecf05e47v9kg19wd5np8o8ej1ee2phx3fgo51eds3uwg6gnq&amp;rid=giphy.gif&amp;ct=g'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Those creators have earned more than $5 billion since the company started in 2016, per OnlyFans. expect other adult entertainment platforms to crop up and try to dethrone a wounded OnlyFans. The falloutOnlyFans will need to find itself a new content strategy, considering it just blew up the one that it relies on currently.  The BBC said it approached OnlyFans with the leaked documents, implying that these allegations were linked to yesterday’s ban.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/onlyfans-will-ban-sexually-explicit-content-surprising-pivot?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/onlyfans-will-ban-sexually-explicit-content-surprising-pivot?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 03:02:12 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: August 20</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/d89EspFlEceJYM7LXV/giphy.gif?cid=ecf05e472xfxn6qwtx8fh3ysoddocss6qen1bwkbs4hxfnod&amp;rid=giphy.gif&amp;ct=g'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;That’s how one Mexican agave producer described the tequila boom to the LA Times. The number of applications to start new businesses in the US grew 24% last year to 4.3 million, the highest on record by far. (Year Zero) – NF</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/key-performance-indicators-august-20</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/key-performance-indicators-august-20</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 14:51:12 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Facebook Launches VR Meeting Space Called Workrooms</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6317%2Ffacebook_horizon_workrooms.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Zoom out: Workrooms is one part of a larger VR experience called Horizon that Facebook originally planned to launch last year. And if not everyone on your team has an Oculus headset, they can still join via video, appearing as part of a tiled, Zoom-like display at the end of the table.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/facebook-launches-vr-meeting-space-called-workrooms</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>metaverse</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/facebook-launches-vr-meeting-space-called-workrooms</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 14:41:11 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Amazon Is Reportedly Planning to Open Its Own Department Stores</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6318%2Famazon_shopping_cart.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The backstory: After opening its first brick-and-mortar bookstore in Seattle in 2015, Amazon expanded its physical footprint to grocery and cashierless convenience stores.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/amazon-reportedly-planning-open-department-stores</link>
  <author>Sherry Qin</author>
  <categories>retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/amazon-reportedly-planning-open-department-stores</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 14:37:11 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Chip Shortages Continues to Hit Global Automakers</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/Q4MKucytzKYJ4elFhG/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; And because every bad episode has a few bad subplots, other automakers like GM, Ford, Stellantis, and VW said this week they’re likely cutting production soon due to the lack of chips.  </description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/chip-shortages-continues-hit-global-automakers</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>auto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/chip-shortages-continues-hit-global-automakers</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 14:26:09 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>OnlyFans Will Ban Sexually Explicit Content in Surprising Pivot</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/yyp58Yx3Qk0TK/giphy.gif?cid=ecf05e47v9kg19wd5np8o8ej1ee2phx3fgo51eds3uwg6gnq&amp;rid=giphy.gif&amp;ct=g'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Those creators have earned more than $5 billion since the company started in 2016, per OnlyFans. OnlyFans, the adult entertainment platform we wrote about earlier this week for launching a parent-approved app, made a bigger, more shocking move away from porn yesterday. The falloutOnlyFans will need to find itself a new content strategy, considering it just blew up the one that it relies on currently. — NF Looking ahead...</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/onlyfans-will-ban-sexually-explicit-content-surprising-pivot</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/19/onlyfans-will-ban-sexually-explicit-content-surprising-pivot</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 14:22:10 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Old Navy Will No Longer Keep Women’s Plus-size Clothing in Separate Sections</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6302%2Fold_navy_plus-sized_models.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Zoom out: Old Navy joins other apparel brands that have recently broadened their size options and featured plus-size models in marketing materials, including Victoria’s Secret, Target, Nike, and Nordstrom.  Quick history lesson: Back in 2014, Old Navy was criticized for charging higher prices for women’s plus-size jeans, but not men’s.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/old-navy-will-no-longer-keep-womens-plussize-clothing-separate-sections?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Sherry Qin</author>
  <categories>retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/old-navy-will-no-longer-keep-womens-plussize-clothing-separate-sections?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 03:02:14 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: August 19</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5340%2Faustin_texas_skyline.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(Harper's) The number of people who died from opioid overdoses from 1999 to 2019 is nearly half a million, per the CDC.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/key-performance-indicators-august-19?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/key-performance-indicators-august-19?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 03:02:13 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>T-Mobile Data Breach Compromises The Data of Nearly 50 Million</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6299%2Fin_this_photo_illustratio.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In response, T-Mobile said it was “working around the clock to investigate claims being made that T-Mobile data may have been illegally accessed.” Looks like hackers couldn’t resist T-Mobile’s hot pink branding: The mobile carrier said yesterday that the data of 40 million former and prospective customers + 8 million current users had been breached. — JW</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/tmobile-data-breach-compromises-data-nearly-50-million?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>cybersecurity</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/tmobile-data-breach-compromises-data-nearly-50-million?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 03:02:13 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>What's Next for Afghanistan's Economy? </title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6298%2Ftaliban_closes_in_on_afgh.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;— NF Big picture: Gaining economic leverage against the Taliban might be difficult for the US, since the group operates outside formal banking channels that the US has traditionally used to apply sanctions.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/whats-next-afghanistans-economy?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>international</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/whats-next-afghanistans-economy?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 03:02:13 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Robinhood Extends Its Relationship With Individual Traders Using Say's Platform</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F2127%2Frobinhood_illustration.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The forum for investors’ questions was made possible by Say Technologies, a firm Robinhood acquired for $140 million earlier this month. It earned $233 million in revenue from crypto trading last quarter, which is astonishing because…It earned just $5 million from crypto trading in Q2 2020Crypto now accounts for 51% of all transaction-based revenueDogecoin trading made up 62% of total crypto revenueLooking ahead... As initial investors, can we get a Robinhood coat and hoodie jacket?  Forget the hoodies—for Robinhood it’s all about crypto. Is Robinhood getting a crypto wallet?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/robinhood-extends-relationship-individual-traders-using-says-platform?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>stocks</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/robinhood-extends-relationship-individual-traders-using-says-platform?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 03:02:13 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: August 19</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F5340%2Faustin_texas_skyline.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(Knowable Magazine) You could, too. Read: Dozens of traditional cultures use a whistled form of their native language for long-distance communication.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/key-performance-indicators-august-19</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/key-performance-indicators-august-19</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 14:51:21 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Old Navy Will No Longer Keep Women’s Plus-size Clothing in Separate Sections</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6301%2Fold_navy.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Old Navy will no longer keep women’s plus-size clothing in separate sections in its stores and plans to offer all its designs from sizes 0 to 30. - SQ Back in 2014, Old Navy was criticized for charging higher prices for women’s plus-size jeans, but not men’s.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/old-navy-will-no-longer-keep-womens-plussize-clothing-separate-sections</link>
  <author>Sherry Qin</author>
  <categories>retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/old-navy-will-no-longer-keep-womens-plussize-clothing-separate-sections</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 14:51:21 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Robinhood Extends Its Relationship With Individual Traders Using Say's Platform</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F2127%2Frobinhood_illustration.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The forum for investors’ questions was made possible by Say Technologies, a firm Robinhood agreed to acquire for $140 million earlier this month.  Forget the hoodies—for Robinhood it’s all about crypto. Is Robinhood getting a crypto wallet? As initial investors, can we get a Robinhood coat and hoodie jacket? Robinhood needs to find its next meme stock. It earned $233 million in revenue from crypto trading last quarter, which is astonishing because…It earned just $5 million from crypto trading in Q2 2020.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/robinhood-extends-relationship-individual-traders-using-says-platform</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>stocks</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/robinhood-extends-relationship-individual-traders-using-says-platform</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 14:46:21 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>T-Mobile Data Breach Compromises The Data of Nearly 50 Million</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6299%2Fin_this_photo_illustratio.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In response, T-Mobile said it was “working around the clock to investigate claims being made that T-Mobile data may have been illegally accessed.” Looks like hackers couldn’t resist T-Mobile’s hot pink branding: The mobile carrier said yesterday that the data of 40 million former and prospective customers + 8 million current users had been breached.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/tmobile-data-breach-compromises-data-nearly-50-million</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>cybersecurity</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/tmobile-data-breach-compromises-data-nearly-50-million</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 14:46:21 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>What's Next for Afghanistan's Economy? </title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6298%2Ftaliban_closes_in_on_afgh.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  Now, the Taliban can access just 0.1% of the reserves,  Afghanistan’s former central bank governor, Ajmal Ahmady, said Tuesday.  International aid accounted for ~43% of Afghanistan’s economy in 2020, per the World Bank. the IMF is set to send more than $450 million to Afghanistan’s bank account on Monday as part of the fund’s coronavirus relief program.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/whats-next-afghanistans-economy</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>international</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/whats-next-afghanistans-economy</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 14:36:19 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>How to Buy Bitcoin...Without Buying Bitcoin</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F3997%2Fbitcoin_tesla.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Plus, the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) is a publicly traded, SEC-reporting company that you can invest in through your normal brokerages, making it more accessible to traders who are less comfortable navigating other avenues for acquiring bitcoin. Invest in companies that hold bitcoin on their balance sheetsOn August 11, 2020, business intelligence firm MicroStrategy became the first publicly traded company to allocate a portion of its cash holdings into bitcoin.  Now, many of them are publicly traded companies that you can also invest in. Invest in crypto trading platforms As cryptocurrencies have risen to prominence over the last decade, so too have companies that offer a safe and secure way to buy and sell the digital assets. The cards listed below each give you a small amount of bitcoin every time you swipe. Invest in blockchain ETFsA relatively recent development in the crypto space is the rise of Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs) that offer exposure to bitcoin and other blockchain-based companies. One is made up of bitcoin and the other ethereum, which are the two largest cryptocurrencies. Since then, higher profile companies have added bitcoin to their balance sheets, most notably Tesla, leading to more opportunities for investors to get their toes wet without diving all the way into the crypto deep end.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/buy-bitcoinwithout-buying-bitcoin</link>
  <author>Toby Howell</author>
  <categories>cryptocurrency</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/buy-bitcoinwithout-buying-bitcoin</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 10:36:15 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Let the Pandemic Take Office Dress Codes</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/geXJ0CoZr9PyM/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“ Most straight-sized folks can go out to a store and just buy clothing or can go thrift a lot of their professional attire,” they said. Melinda, a new teacher who asked to be identified by only their first name, spent $600+ when they switched schools after their first year of teaching and had to match a new school’s muddy “business professional” dress code. Business casual is a dress code so ill-defined that the best way to describe it is to say what it isn’t. Dress codes create financial barriers for young people, support bias in the workplace, and cause more problems that bleed over into our everyday lives, even after the end of the work day. At one point, I even got a comment from my office manager asking if I had already worn one of those three shirts earlier that week,” he said. Her job is asking employees to come back into the office, and when she tried to bring up her financial concerns about purchasing new office clothes, she was met with congratulations on her weight loss. For the last year-and-a-half, most office workers have been working from home in, at their fanciest, a stain-free shirt for meetings. Dress codes create a barrierThis confusion can be frustrating and expensive for young people entering the workforce.  And for many young professionals, there’s a serious disconnect between dress codes and pay. brands might be seeing the error of their ways. Emily Milligan, a recent grad, told Morning Brew that after getting a competitive unpaid internship with their state’s attorney general, they had to buy an entire suit. The good news: Business casual and its precious lil $50 flowy-sleeved blouses are already on their way out. Before we do, let’s officially retire office dress codes.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/let-pandemic-take-office-dress-codes</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>work</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/18/let-pandemic-take-office-dress-codes</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 05:51:25 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Palantir Buys $50.7 Million Worth of Gold Bars</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6280%2Flots_of_gold_bars.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As for putting bitcoin on its balance sheet, “The short answer is yes, we’re thinking about it,” finance chief Dave Glazer said in May. — NF But Palantir is putting its own spin on the genre, investing in gold bars and pouring $250 million into startups that use Palantir software.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/palantir-buys-507-million-worth-gold-bars?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>strategy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/palantir-buys-507-million-worth-gold-bars?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 03:01:18 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: August 18</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F4619%2Fheisman_trophy.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(GQ)  Read: The 21 most exciting young musicians on planet Earth. Fed Chair Jerome Powell talked about the pandemic’s effect on students at a town hall meeting yesterday.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/key-performance-indicators-august-18?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/key-performance-indicators-august-18?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 03:01:18 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>OnlyFans Launches a SFW App</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6281%2Fscreenshot_from_oftv_app.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;And while OFTV won’t ditch the creators who helped drive OnlyFans revenue 553% higher last year, the app will also feature chefs, pilates instructors, and podcasters. We still don’t recommend scrolling through OnlyFans at work, but the company’s latest product—a new app for Android and iOS—is much closer to PG.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/onlyfans-launches-sfw-app?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>creator economy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/onlyfans-launches-sfw-app?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 03:01:17 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Biden Administration is Expected to Advise Boosters for Most Americans</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F4371%2Fvaccine_tracker.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Nearly 1 million Israelis have already received booster shots.  Why booster shots? Hope you have enough storage in your phone for one more vaccine selfie: The White House is expected to announce this week that most Americans will need a Covid booster shot eight months after their second doses. – SQ</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/biden-administration-expected-advise-boosters-americans?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Sherry Qin</author>
  <categories>covid</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/biden-administration-expected-advise-boosters-americans?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 03:01:17 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Can Kids Revive Retail?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/l1J9rURykdgphbkLS/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Even worse, a Cincinnati-area Walmart ran out of all Disney backpacks. The retailer said its stores were busy with parents buying backpacks, lunch boxes, and other school supplies for their kids, and even raised its revenue outlook for the year. With inflation on the rise, consumers should expect to pay 10%–15% more compared to last year for apparel, according to USA Today. Families with children in elementary through high school plan to spend an average of $848.90 on school supplies, a $59 increase over last year. — NF</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/can-kids-revive-retail?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/can-kids-revive-retail?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 03:01:17 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Biden Administration is Expected to Advise Boosters for Most Americans</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F4371%2Fvaccine_tracker.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Why booster shots?  Nearly 1 million Israelis have already received booster shots. Growing case numbers in highly vaccinated countries show that vaccine effectiveness may wear off over time, particularly against the Delta variant.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/biden-administration-expected-advise-boosters-americans</link>
  <author>Sherry Qin</author>
  <categories>covid</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/biden-administration-expected-advise-boosters-americans</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 15:01:22 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Can Kids Revive Retail?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://media.giphy.com/media/l1J9rURykdgphbkLS/giphy.gif'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Even worse, a Cincinnati-area Walmart ran out of all Disney backpacks. Retail could use the sparkRetail sales fell more than expected (-1.1%) in July, the Commerce Department said yesterday. Thanks to inflation, consumers should expect to pay 10%–15% more compared to last year for apparel, according to USA Today. Families with children in elementary- through high school plan to spend an average of $848.90 on school supplies, a $59 increase over last year.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/can-kids-revive-retail</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/can-kids-revive-retail</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 14:51:19 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>OnlyFans Launches a SFW App</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6281%2Fscreenshot_from_oftv_app.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;And while OFTV won’t ditch the adult creators who drove OnlyFans’s revenue to pop by 553% last year, the app will also feature chefs, pilates instructors, and podcasters. The workaround: a new product called OFTV that contains a library of over 800 videos featuring the same creators from its site...</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/onlyfans-launches-sfw-app</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>creator economy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/onlyfans-launches-sfw-app</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 14:46:18 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Palantir Buys $50.7 Million Worth of Gold Bars</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6280%2Flots_of_gold_bars.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As for putting bitcoin on its balance sheet, “The short answer is yes, we’re thinking about it,” finance chief Dave Glazer said in May. But Palantir is pushing the genre to new limits, investing in gold bars and pouring $250 million into startups that use Palantir software.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/palantir-buys-507-million-worth-gold-bars</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>investing</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/palantir-buys-507-million-worth-gold-bars</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 14:41:18 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: August 18</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F4619%2Fheisman_trophy.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(GQ)  Read: The 21 most exciting young musicians on planet Earth. Fed Chair Jerome Powell talked about the pandemic’s effect on students at a town hall meeting yesterday.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/key-performance-indicators-august-18</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/17/key-performance-indicators-august-18</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 14:41:18 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Anonymous Chat App Yik Yak Is Back Four Years After Shutting Down</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6270%2Fyik_yak_promo_image.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Yik Yak is the id unleashed. The revived Yik Yak said it’s trying to clean up the toxicity by instituting a one-strike no bullying policy and providing links to mental health resources—though most of the functionality appears similar to V1.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/16/anonymous-chat-app-yik-yak-back-four-years-shutting?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>social media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/16/anonymous-chat-app-yik-yak-back-four-years-shutting?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 03:01:18 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: August 17</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6273%2Fwhite_lotus_image.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Quote: “Are you passionate about Digital Currencies and driven by opportunities to scale new products and businesses?”  Read: The dirty secret of what happens to many of the clothes we donate to charity.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/16/key-performance-indicators-august-17?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/16/key-performance-indicators-august-17?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 03:01:18 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>US Launches Investigation Into Tesla's Autopilot System</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6268%2Fan_illustration_of_a_parked_tesla.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The investigation stems from 11 incidents in which drivers using Tesla’s Autopilot feature struck stationary first-responder vehicles. US auto regulators have launched an investigation into Tesla’s advanced driver-assistance system, Autopilot, ramping up scrutiny of Elon Musk’s self-driving efforts.  What isn’t Autopilot?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/16/us-launches-investigation-teslas-autopilot-system?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>auto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/16/us-launches-investigation-teslas-autopilot-system?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 03:01:18 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Dark Future Looms Over Women Living In Afghanistan</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.morningbrew.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedium%2Fasset%2F6272%2Fa_poster_of_women_in_afghanistan.jpg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75'&gt;&lt;br/&gt; When the Taliban last ruled Afghanistan, from 1996–2001, Afghan women were not allowed to... Work outside of the homeAttend schoolLeave home without a male escort and their faces and bodies coveredSince the US ousted the Taliban from power in 2001, Afghan women made gains in education and the workforce. An estimated 1.6 million more Afghan women are employed now over 20 years ago. Five Mediterranean nations have requested EU-level talks about how to respond.  Washington Post publisher Fred Ryan pleaded with the White House to protect more than 200 journalists, staffers, and family members from the WaPo, New York Times, and Wall Street Journal who were in danger at the airport.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/16/dark-future-looms-women-living-afghanistan?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>geopolitics</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/08/16/dark-future-looms-women-living-afghanistan?email=%7B%7Bprofile.email%7D%7D</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 03:01:18 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>

</channel>
</rss>
