<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <atom:link href="https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2023/03/02/users/1/web_requests/22/MorningBrew.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
 <atom:icon>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2023/03/02/favicon.ico</atom:icon>
 

 <title>MorningBrew as a feed</title>
 <description>This is a feed of recent MorningBrew articles published by Huginn</description>
 <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2023/03/02</link>
 <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:46 -0800</lastBuildDate>
 <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:46 -0800</pubDate>
 <ttl>60</ttl>
 <item>
  <title>G-7 Ministers Agree to Corporate Minimum Tax</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/35816b06c5940fbe97a92f309e0b36987d059b3e-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. It represents one of the biggest attempts to bring an outdated global tax system from black-and-white into Technicolor. The Biden administration estimates a global minimum tax system would lead to $500 billion in additional tax revenue for the US over the next decade. Ireland has managed to attract lots of tech jobs due to its low corporate tax rate of 12.5%, and it won’t want to give up that competitive advantage. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeOn Saturday, the finance ministers from G7 nations announced their support for a global corporate minimum tax of 15%, which would require companies to pay at least a 15% rate in each country they operate in. The provision is meant to address European leaders’ concerns that they can’t sufficiently tax tech giants like Facebook and Google, because while those companies make tons of money in Europe, they are based in the US and pay taxes there. The backstory: Multinational companies have been taking advantage of existing tax rules by shuffling money between jurisdictions with super-low rates. But wait, there’s moreIn addition to the 15% minimum tax, the agreement by the G7 (which, by the way, is composed of Canada, France, Germany, the US, Italy, Japan, and the UK) calls for an extra tax on profits from the “largest and most profitable multinational enterprises.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/06/g7-ministers-agree-corporate-minimum-tax</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>taxes</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/06/g7-ministers-agree-corporate-minimum-tax</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:56 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>El Salvador Moves to Adopt Bitcoin as Legal Tender</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/ff9b575748a839803d8cdae0d5389fb5992c6c56-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Why El Salvador? On Saturday, El Salvador’s president, Nayib Bukele, said he’s going to send a bill to the legislature to make bitcoin a legal tender in the country. Here’s a fun read describing the ridiculousness of the event. 20% of the country’s GDP comes from remittances, which are payments sent by Salvadorans living abroad back to the country. + While we’re here: Bukele’s announcement came in a taped message delivered to the Bitcoin 2021 conference in Miami. Bukele said that bitcoin could help streamline those cumbersome cross-border payments, while promoting “financial inclusion” for those left out of the system. It’d be the first country to formally adopt the cryptocurrency as part of its economy. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/06/el-salvador-move-adopt-bitcoin-legal-tender</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/06/el-salvador-move-adopt-bitcoin-legal-tender</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:56 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Calm App, Sweetgreen, Others Rush to Back Naomi Osaka’s Decision to Leave French Open</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/e565147ec2446ac29959fb76ab93319fe022a997-3840x2560.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The backstory: Last Sunday, Osaka dropped out of the tournament to focus on her mental health after initially declaring she’d skip mandatory press conferences. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeSweetgreen, Nike, Calm, and other brands moved quickly this week to back tennis star Naomi Osaka after she dropped out of this year’s French Open. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Calm, an app that produces guided meditations, offered to pay the $15,000 fine for any player opting out of 2021 Grand Slam media appearances for mental health reasons.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/04/calm-app-sweetgreen-others-rush-back-naomi-osakas-decision-leave-french-open</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/04/calm-app-sweetgreen-others-rush-back-naomi-osakas-decision-leave-french-open</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:56 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>May Jobs Report Offers Wins, Losses, And Some Hope</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-d6999f80f75382c2a465757cfc01c4e5b9e0609d-480x270-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The biggest job gains were in the leisure and hospitality sector, which added 292,000 new jobs, more than the 278,000 jobs the economy added in total in April.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/04/may-jobs-report-offers-wins-losses-hope</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>economy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/04/may-jobs-report-offers-wins-losses-hope</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:55 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: June 5</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/e069eb90b74ec6a3f06ea620b1a685c7234ccb31-2031x1476.jpg?rect=0,61,2031,1354&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeStat: Every single corporate board in the S&amp;P 500 now has at least one woman on it after Monolithic Power Systems added a female director last month, according to Bloomberg. (YouTube) “We need more rain, and we need it now." Quote: “We need some divine intervention.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/04/key-performance-indicators-june-5</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/04/key-performance-indicators-june-5</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:54 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Bill Ackman's Proposed SPAC Deal Confuses Just About Everyone</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/93d91cb4cd9da8f127600ae41dcbbb1625383701-620x413.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. There’s even more 4D financial chess going on behind the scenes, but the bottom line is that shares in Ackman’s SPAC plummeted yesterday following the announcement, meaning investors doubt Ackman can pull off these business theatrics. Assuming you’ve got a cold brew close by, here’s what’s going on:Last year Ackman created a SPAC, aka a “blank-check company,” called Pershing Square Tontine Holdings, which raised about $4 billion. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/04/bill-ackmans-proposed-spac-deal-confuses-just-everyone</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>m&amp;a</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/04/bill-ackmans-proposed-spac-deal-confuses-just-everyone</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:54 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Icebreakers with… Uma Valeti</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/f8a4f2be3c8194d4d5a4d44fbffd031d2dda3fc5-1200x628.png?rect=129,0,942,628&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. The company raised $161 million in Series B funding, including investments from SoftBank, Bill Gates, Richard Branson, and Tyson Foods. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The second one is working with regulators on food safety, making sure that we work with them properly and that there is a healthy dialogue back and forth. You have to look upwards and keep the focus on your North Star and who you're trying to impact. I read that the Upside Foods office has albums based on meat? Now for the last five years, I've been eating it again. Now, his company, Upside Foods (previously Memphis Meats), is doing just that: growing real meat in a lab. But I made a promise to myself that I will only eat the meat that we produce. But a third of the people stopped within a month because they wanted to go back to their old habits, whether it was eating what they liked or not taking meds. What's your favorite meal made out of Upside Foods's cell-grown meat? No. I grew up in a meat-eating family, but during medical school, I stopped eating meat because I thought, "I don't like how meat is coming to the table." Absolutely don't look back because it looks scary if you start looking back. Are you a vegan or vegetarian? And I'm like, "Okay, we need to bring meat to the table, not a meat alternative." You can go fast on a lot of things, but you have to deliberately slow down for some really important moments. What made you interested in creating cell-based meat instead of a meat substitute like a veggie patty? css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe other thing to know is when to go fast and when to go slow. Another really important thing was we decided not to go into stealth mode. You can't go fast when you introduce a product to market.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/04/icebreakers-uma-valeti</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>q&amp;a</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/04/icebreakers-uma-valeti</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:53 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Floyd Mayweather vs. Logan Paul: But...Why?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-eb55355c34ecbcff2e6b2239a052a49447258129-480x240-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeSocial media star Logan Paul will fight Floyd Mayweather Jr., who is considered one of the best boxers ever, in an exhibition match tonight at Miami's Hard Rock Stadium. If you are one of the many people who decide to pay $49.99 on Showtime pay-per-view to watch (it'll likely be one of the most-viewed events of the year), you probably won't see a competitive fight. He's posted a number of controversial videos, including one where he visits a "suicide forest" in Japan and another where he tasered two dead rats.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/04/paul-vs-mayweather-butwhy</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>analysis</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/04/paul-vs-mayweather-butwhy</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:51 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Make It Work: Returning to the Office and Bad Management</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7b6de1bb891bb0dd9e289abb0a591582a5da30e6-1503x603.png?rect=299,0,905,603&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. I'm not sure what type of treatment you received from management, but if it was not aligned with general ethics or company policy then it should be reported. With the collective, you can reach out to HR through email and make a request to have a group session to discuss the new rule. If this is something you are still thinking about then you can reach out to your former employer and let them know how you feel. Your HR rep can be the mediator between your group and the leadership team, and they can also provide insight into how the company arrived at the decision of a hybrid work structure post-pandemic." How do we have a conversation with leadership about this?" css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Something bothering you at work? Did I do a disservice to fellow employees and management when I didn't disclose that the reason I left my company was due to my treatment by management?" Ask Kate here. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeEach week, Morning Brew's Head of People Ops Kate Noel answers reader-submitted questions about work in 2021."</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/04/make-work-returning-office-bad-management</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>work life</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/04/make-work-returning-office-bad-management</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:49 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>United Airlines Cuts Deal for Supersonic Commercial Jets</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/9896e0e6660cbe1071713de9c2d97b8beeb39807-1678x1000.png?rect=89,0,1500,1000&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Supersonic = faster than the speed of sound. Just last month, one of the leading supersonic jet makers, Aerion, shut down because of financial troubles and concerns about fuel-efficiency and noise regulations. The promise of supersonic commercial flight reemerged yesterday when United Airlines announced it's buying 15 jets from Boom Supersonic. Now, Boom and other supersonic startups are working on net-zero emissions and noise-muffling tech.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/03/united-airlines-cuts-deal-supersonic-commercial-jets</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>travel</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/03/united-airlines-cuts-deal-supersonic-commercial-jets</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:49 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Twitter Launches First Paid Subscription Service, Blue</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/665dcb7e800fc0b19638a0076dc893664c980d18-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. For now, only Australian and Canadian users can pay around $3/month to access Blue features like a 30-second grace period to undo or edit a tweet before it's posted, prioritized customer support, Reader Mode for easier viewing of threads, and color scheme customization for the app. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeAt long last, Twitter has released its first subscription product, Twitter Blue. A virtual tip jar"Super Follows" for individual users to charge subscriptionsVoice-based DMs and tweetsFeatures that limit the spread of misinformation and prevent harassmentStories (aka "Fleets")Spaces, a Clubhouse competitor why are we writing about it? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/03/twitter-launches-first-paid-subscription-service-blue</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/03/twitter-launches-first-paid-subscription-service-blue</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:48 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>California Drought Could Cause Wide-Ranging Industry Problems</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/1fe71b469cb5247d0b99e0d0cd11d1933fcbc111-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Officials are predicting the water level of Lake Oroville, the Beyoncé of California lakes, to hit a record low in August. The state of play: California Gov. Gavin Newsom has put 41 counties under a state of emergency in an attempt to drastically limit water use. The water levels of 1,500+ reservoirs in California are 50% lower than normal at this time of year, per Jay Lund, co-director of the Center for Watershed Sciences at UC-Davis.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/03/california-drought-cause-wideranging-industry-problems</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>environment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/03/california-drought-cause-wideranging-industry-problems</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:47 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Amazon Gets Rid of Marijuana in Drug Screenings, Says ‘Legalize It’</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7ae08c91607ae806ed42cc31fdc9dc18a6523e3a-1600x900.png?rect=125,0,1350,900&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/02/amazon-gets-rid-marijuana-drug-screenings-says-legalize</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>e-commerce</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/02/amazon-gets-rid-marijuana-drug-screenings-says-legalize</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:45 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Etsy Announces Plans To Acquire Depop</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/a28287e27b7dc7bbd584ccf1c1ab25bdc7f63f08-562x386.png?rect=0,5,562,375&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. For Etsy, whose median seller is about 39, it’s a strategic move meant to court Depop’s overwhelmingly Gen Z user base: More than 90% of its users are under 26. thrifting is expected to get more popular as Gen Z ages into greater spending power and more shoppers favor sustainable products over fast-fashion.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/02/etsy-announces-plans-acquire-depop</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/02/etsy-announces-plans-acquire-depop</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:44 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>AMC, Gaining Nearly 100% in a Day, Embraces Its Life as a Meme Stock</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/e1e6f317d004ef9f6427663f3c61d8f626b18e38-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. Over the weekend, it sold $230 million worth of stock to a hedge fund in order to “go on the offense again." css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/02/amc-gaining-nearly-100-day-embraces-life-meme-stock</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>investing</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/02/amc-gaining-nearly-100-day-embraces-life-meme-stock</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:44 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>London's See-Through Sky Pool Opens</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/719f3fb23295b8d0e37c9cabb1f8e8741925cb42-4000x2661.jpg?rect=4,0,3992,2661&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. above the ground in London, the infamous Sky Pool opened for business this week. Windy out? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/02/londons-seethrough-sky-pool-opens</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>architecture</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/02/londons-seethrough-sky-pool-opens</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:42 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Krispy Kreme Files To Go Public</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-c7d50fd40d73214f539f283d299254709302d1c0-720x404-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. But after being battered and fried, Krispy Kreme was picked up by European investment firm JAB Holdings and glazed back to glory. Consider this a comeback tour, because when the 83-year-old chain first went public in 2000, it filed for bankruptcy just five years later—when carbs became public enemy No. 1. Did you know: Krispy Kreme owns Insomnia Cookies, which conducts over half of its sales via e-commerce. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! The chain expanded its footprint from 6,040 Krispy Kreme-selling locations in 2019 to 8,275 last year. 64% of all Krispy Kreme donuts sold are the glazed kind, because that's the best flavor. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeKrispy Kreme filed to go public yesterday under the ticker symbol DNUT, a much better choice than KRPY but less creative than GLZD. Some notable stats from Krispy Kreme's SEC filing…US sales grew 17% in its last fiscal year, and net revenue jumped 23% in Q1 2021 year over year.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/01/krispy-kreme-files-go-public</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>ipo</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/01/krispy-kreme-files-go-public</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:42 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>AMC Raises Millions To Acquire Other Theaters</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/05f3fc979495abc1f9d7b30be2994904bcf785eb-5200x3466.jpg?rect=1,0,5199,3466&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. AMC issued 8.5 million shares to investment firm Mudrick Capital to raise the sum.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/01/amc-raises-millions-acquire-theaters</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/01/amc-raises-millions-acquire-theaters</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:42 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Oil Prices Surge to Highest Levels Since Covid Began</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-e09ea59b9f01e50d9faf494756625f569f4f478f-281x200-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. At one point the price of oil plunged into negative territory—meaning someone would pay you to take possession of their oil barrel. What happened: The powerful oil cartel OPEC and its allies agreed to gradually increase oil production. But the big wild card is Iran: If the country rejoins the nuclear deal with the US, which is under consideration, it will play a significant role in global oil production. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeYesterday, oil prices hit their highest levels since the pandemic began. That announcement, signaling more demand for fuel in the coming months, only added to the positive vibes around the price of oil, which has shot up more than 30% this year.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/01/oil-prices-surge-highest-levels-since-covid-began</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>energy</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/01/oil-prices-surge-highest-levels-since-covid-began</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:41 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>What Is Stock Analysis? Financial Experts Explain Their Go-to Strategies</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d592128b481ab6764d2cb1c1fba523c02d848715-2120x1414.jpg?rect=0,0,2120,1413&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. If a company has $1 million in earnings and 1 million shares outstanding, its EPS is $1. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. If the same company is trading at $20 per share, the PE ratio is 20. It’s more about finding patterns in the stock price that investors can exploit. You can find company financials through the SEC EDGAR portal. One last reminder: You’re probably not going to get stupid rich by investing in individual stocks. Here are some signs of a company with a blossoming future:Lasting edge in the market: You want to invest in a company that has some competitive advantage in its sector. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. You won’t find any analysis there, so head over to a site like Yahoo Finance to see what investors are thinking. It’s OK if you’re feeling this way, because there’s more to a stock price than the numbers. It’s the same thing with picking stocks: You want to invest in companies that are part of a growing industry. Do your own researchAt first, financial statements can look like they’re written in Klingon. Then, move onto valuation ratios, which compare a company’s financial results to its price in the market. See what analysts—and even your friends—are saying about the company’s future in qualitative terms. Review the numbersNo matter your approach, it’s a good idea to take a look at the company’s financials before investing. Financial market experts agree that identifying stocks that’ll beat the overall market is hard. They care less about the company’s intrinsic value and more about how the stock price will shift in the future. Chat with a financial advisor about the most responsible way to fit stock trading into your portfolio. Fundamental analysis involves determining the company’s intrinsic value from the bottom up, from examining historical financial statements to imagining the company’s future. If someone says a company’s share price is “20 times earnings,” they’re talking about the PE ratio. Price to sales ratio (PSR): Market capitalization divided by annual sales. In general, you want a quick ratio higher than 1. An important metric in mature companies, net profit margin shows you how much money a company actually earns for every dollar in sales. That’s why you often see higher trading volume around earnings reports. Put it all togetherThis is where investment analysts take their research, create a financial model, and forecast the company’s future financials before making a trading decision. Analysts often associate industries with specific ratios that best depict a company’s financials.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/01/stock-analysis-101</link>
  <author>Ryan Lasker</author>
  <categories>markets</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/01/stock-analysis-101</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:40 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Naomi Osaka, Highest-Earning Female Athlete in the World, Drops Out of French Open</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/53a01e66de4d247f471723db2f29c5e51b9c4251-5472x3648.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Other athletes said they respected Osaka’s initial decision to avoid the press, but pointed out that answering questions in front of a hot mic is just part of the job.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/naomi-osaka-highestearning-female-athlete-world-drops-french-open</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/naomi-osaka-highestearning-female-athlete-world-drops-french-open</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:28 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: June 1</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/3798e63bba9f6347c0295061676b357177523780-730x410.jpg?rect=58,0,615,410&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Marqueece Harris-Dawson of the LA City Council described the uptick in gun purchases to the NYT in a way we can all relate to.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/key-performance-indicators-june-1</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/key-performance-indicators-june-1</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:27 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>China Adopts Three-Child Policy Rule to Boost Population</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-314fa06e5ce5fd8f76aab62368dcb0d09faa01aa-309x208-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeOn Monday, China's government said that couples will be able to have a third child, a decision meant to spark more babies in a country where population growth has hit a wall. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Fewer babies = fewer future workers. South Korea's rate of births per woman fell to 0.84 last year, the lowest in the world. Africa’s population is set to double by 2050, helping the world grow from 7.8 billion people today to 11 billion by 2100. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Why it matters: Declining population growth has profound implications for a country's economic success.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/china-adopts-threechild-policy-rule-boost-population</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>demographics</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/china-adopts-threechild-policy-rule-boost-population</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:27 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Nestlé Rethinks Health Strategy Following Leaked Report</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/9622b93d5d097283c22316a1a41238ea9202ff88-800x405.jpg?rect=96,0,608,405&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. One pepperoni pizza Hot Pocket contains almost 30% of recommended daily sodium intake. Unfortunately for Nestlé's PR team... Baby Ruths aren’t going anywhere, though: "Confectionary and chocolate address a deep human need and are going to be here to stay," CEO Mark Schneider said last year.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/nestl-rethinks-health-strategy-following-leaked-report</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>food &amp; bev</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/nestl-rethinks-health-strategy-following-leaked-report</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:25 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Exclusive: Post-Pandemic, Summer Travel Trends to Watch</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d4cdb139b1768a6b4783eb4b6dc6d48ea1e1c46f-2119x1414.jpg?rect=0,0,2119,1413&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. To the 3% who said they're taking 5 or more... Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. YouGov is an international research and data analytics group that surveys a panel of 15+ million people across 40 major markets. More demand = higher pricesGenerally. Of the 30% of respondents who work remotely at least one day a week, 42% said it's positively impacted their ability to travel. While more travelers are looking to get their delayed Eurotrip on, domestic travel is still the name of the game this summer, Keyes said. 39% of travelers said they're concerned about travel costs. 69% expect to be fully vaccinated by the time they travel, but plenty still have pandemic worries, including…Contracting Covid (22%)Confusion over local pandemic laws (25%)Overcrowding (32%)Other travelers not following Covid rules (37%)But the No. 1 concern?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/exclusive-postpandemic-summer-travel-trends-watch</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>travel</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/31/exclusive-postpandemic-summer-travel-trends-watch</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:24 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Business Trends to Watch This Summer</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/2f9cf53cdc6c8f8ffc57d0a7de7354f8c4040e89-3000x1196.jpg?rect=603,0,1794,1196&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Inflation data over the summer will reveal whether this quirkiness is more permanent than officials had thought. Slower vaccinations = slower recoveries, which threaten a global economic rebound. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. —Neal FreymanCryptoMaybe I'm on Twitter too much, but cryptocurrency, and more specifically cryptocurrency regulation, is the top business topic I'll be watching this summer. I think the big thing to watch is whether supply chains getting back to normal will cause the inflation scaries to subside. But there are other consumer trends I'm excited to watch this summer. When you read the news this summer, we want you to think to yourself, "Ah yes... Here's what we do know: The home makeover revolution probably won't let up. —Yiran Yu Btw, have you experienced the awkwardness of a post-Covid hug/handshake?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/business-trends-watch-summer</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey,</author>
  <categories>trends</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/business-trends-watch-summer</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:22 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>So You Survived a Year of Virtual School…Now What?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d30685b2b208c75d6a99a8f8f2a96eb2c09def8d-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. —Fatima Ali, Brew U Campus Ambassador, University of Wisconsin, Class of 2021)Here are some resources to get you to be your most productive self:How to Track Your Networking with Notion (Medium)2020's Most Popular Coursera Courses(Coursera)How to Find a Hobby (The New York Times)Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. College students have endured one of the most exhaustive school years ever due to the pandemic, and finally now have the chance to relax, breathe, and celebrate. We asked them to share one piece of advice they would have given themselves a year ago while still in school during the pandemic. Coming into college I didn’t know what I wanted to use my major for. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. I wish I would’ve taken more time prior to this to explore alternative careers and network with people in different industries, and I highly encourage other college students to do so before deciding what exactly they want to do.” If you’re one of those hard-working, highly accomplished students actually posting those pictures, kudos to you. —Colleen McFall, Morning Brew Intern, Temple University, Class of 2022“Explore people, projects, and career paths that interest you...</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/29/survived-year-virtual-schoolnow</link>
  <author>Aishwarya Ramaswamy</author>
  <categories>career</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/29/survived-year-virtual-schoolnow</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:19 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Costco Sees Inflationary Pressures, but Will Restart Free Samples</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/575a4334415024e8fbf0f1fb2fe6f4eef261d53d-1462x780.png?rect=146,0,1170,780&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Costco was one of the first US retailers to mandate masks in early May 2020. Overall, the company said that price inflation at the selling level, excluding gasoline, was 2.5%–3.5%, much higher than in March. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/costco-sees-inflationary-pressures-will-restart-free-samples</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/costco-sees-inflationary-pressures-will-restart-free-samples</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:12 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Police Raid a Bitcoin Mining Operation On Accident</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/40186ecfdd313e8fff0cfda4c5ddcad4b2aa43a7-4928x3280.jpg?rect=4,0,4920,3280&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Instead, about 100 computers were leeching thousands of pounds worth of electricity off surrounding circuits in order to mine bitcoin. That’s why British police accidentally busted a cryptocurrency mining operation earlier this month, thinking it was an illegal cannabis farm. Leading up to the raid, the West Midlands Police had noticed telltale signs that a Birmingham warehouse was probably being used to grow marijuana—lots of wiring and ventilation on the outside, high levels of heat emanating from the inside, and people going in and out like it was a salad bar. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! However, as the giant energy toll of crypto mining puts a greater burden on electric grids, more governments may install curbs. Zoom out: While stealing electricity is illegal in the UK, mining bitcoin is a-okay.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/police-raid-bitcoin-mining-operation-accident</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/police-raid-bitcoin-mining-operation-accident</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:10 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Vaccine Tracker: May 29</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/8f84fd336fe3a0dfaf213c52c81a2a3f92177bad-3000x1196.jpg?rect=603,0,1794,1196&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIn the US…about half of the population has now received at least one dose of a Covid-19 vaccine. Latest headlinesMore incentives: On Thursday, California announced a program called “Vax for the Win,” and in this case win = $116.5 million in total prizes for people who’ve been vaccinated or will get a dose. Also this week, Ohio announced the first winner of its $1 million vaccine lottery: 22-year-old Abbigail Bugenske.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/vaccine-tracker-may-29</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>covid</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/vaccine-tracker-may-29</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:10 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: May 29</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7d3f1d48657260b1bf96f1df5b92d39436ff016f-5174x3449.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. (Emerging Tech Brew) css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/key-performance-indicators-may-29</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/key-performance-indicators-may-29</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:09 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Memorial Day Weekend Will be Huge Test for Travel</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/c5508ea2ffdcc2a840eeac58b3aee1afca95a5ea-1200x800.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. They’ll get one this weekend:US airlines are planning for a daily average of at least 2 million passengers through the weekend. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. A majority of the 37 million people expected to travel at least 50 miles from home will be driving, per AAA. Memorial Day weekend, typically one of the busiest travel weekends of the year, presents a big opportunity for airlines, hotels, and other hospitality companies desperate for a travel surge.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/memorial-day-weekend-travel-will-huge-test-travel</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>travel</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/memorial-day-weekend-travel-will-huge-test-travel</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:09 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Did the Coronavirus Get Leaked From a Lab?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/b9640b3697e1ac59a490fff6eff8a035c690b7ad-1000x667.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. On Wednesday, President Biden asked his intelligence agencies to "redouble" their efforts to examine the origins of Covid-19, with a specific focus on the so-called "lab-leak theory." Experts warn that with clues like blood samples drying up, time may be running out to ever learn the virus's true origins. Lab leak: A scientist at the Wuhan Institute of Virology, which studies bat viruses, was infected with a contagious strain through a sloppy mistake or an accident and brought it out to the wider world. But as 2020 went on, scientists found no evidence to support the natural origin theory, China was stonewalling any credible independent investigation, and people started saying, "You know what... As researchers began studying Covid-19's origins last year, the natural origin theory dominated and the lab leak theory was considered preposterous. this lab leak theory may not be as crazy as it sounds." css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! The two prevailing theories are:Natural origin: A bat carrying the coronavirus spread it to another animal such as a pangolin, and the pangolin spread an even more contagious version of the virus to humans.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/coronavirus-get-leaked-lab</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>analysis</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/coronavirus-get-leaked-lab</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:08 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Make It Work: New Jobs Edition</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7b6de1bb891bb0dd9e289abb0a591582a5da30e6-1503x603.png?rect=299,0,905,603&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Q: "I have a job offer from one company, but the company I really want to work for has scheduled my interview for the end of the week. I would ask your manager something like this: "How can I do my job better to support you?" css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/make-work-new-jobs-edition</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>work life</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/make-work-new-jobs-edition</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:06 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Brew's Bookshelf</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-a72bd4ae4737c32552e0667c1c41f2cec88ae39c-500x281-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. In Walkable City Rules: 101 Steps to Making Better Places, he gives community members the data and tools to make it happen. forming a cult? css-1dlcpt7[data-disabled]{opacity:0.4;background-color:rgba(0,0,0,. City Planner Jeff Speck makes the case for why your city should be more walkable. If you need something to start at the gate and finish when you land, My Sister, the Serial Killer by Oyinkan Braithwaite is a quick, funny thriller. Plane reads: air travel is back and so is the guy sitting next to you who won't stop showing you videos of him playing harmonica. css-1dlcpt7{width:100%;min-width:0px;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;position:relative;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);border:1px solid;color:var(--colors-jet);border-color:var(--colors-geyser);background:inherit;background-color:var(--chakra-colors-white);}.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/brews-bookshelf</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>from the crew</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/28/brews-bookshelf</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:05 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Acorns Plans SPAC IPO Amidst Talks of Regulation</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/2e3f74567114b5623a6a6344411cb78399557dec-2924x1949.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Acorns doesn't allow its 6.8+ million users to buy or sell individual stocks. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/acorns-plans-spac-ipo-amidst-talks-regulation</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>fintech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/acorns-plans-spac-ipo-amidst-talks-regulation</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:04 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Where Morning Brew Readers Are Going for Memorial Day </title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-fa7084f72203da5f058100b77ecca3de3ae030f3-480x264-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. —Matt L." Maybe make an oven pizza?" I will be taking an extravagant trip to my WFH setup so I can study for the bar!" css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! I'm going to a lake house in Tennessee with Hinge boy and his pals 💃💃💃 for Memorial Day. What a time." I'm traveling to visit my aunt and uncle at their lake house for Memorial Day. It will be their first time meeting our baby girl!" css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeA few weeks ago, we asked you about your Memorial Day weekend plans, because it seemed like a fun thing to do. Going to the promised land of Moses Lake, WA! I have to settle with heading to my friends at the Jersey shore for MDW, if that counts as traveling." Still searching for a friend in the Hamptons since I've moved to NYC... A staycation with my family is all I want and to take a day to remember all those we have lost. —Matthew A." First time on a plane since Covid!" Some of them my friends." I'm going to wake up at 11am, watch TikToks for two hours, and then write about the stock market for the media company I work for. —Dare accepted, Jonathan." I dare you to feature it.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/morning-brew-readers-going-memorial-day</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>community</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/morning-brew-readers-going-memorial-day</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:03 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: May 28</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/257d609c058163df38555f1dff6b1991cbc96b8a-1024x677.jpg?rect=4,0,1016,677&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Quote: "It's not true that the Super League is dead because the concept is still alive." Javier Tebas, the president of Spanish soccer's La Liga, is not giving up on the concept of a European "Super League," which fizzled embarrassingly in less than 48 hours last month. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! During Neumann’s tenure, WeWork paid $759 million across 10 investments.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/key-performance-indicators-may-28</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/key-performance-indicators-may-28</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:02 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Disney's 'Cruella' Signals a Pivot to PG-13</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-cf5c3f29dfa8a4838a611421668f35ee44a3e2c6-480x270-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. In the same time span, PG movies earned $24.3 billion; R movies, $26.5 billion; and G movies, $2.7 billion, according to Comscore. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. By the 2000s, PG-13 movies were raking in most of the box office revenue. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeToday, Disney's live-action Cruella arrives in theaters and on Disney+. Cruella is Disney's third PG-13 release in a year, according to the WSJ.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/disneys-cruella-signals-pivot-pg13</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/disneys-cruella-signals-pivot-pg13</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:01 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Biden to Propose $6T Budget</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/22d917ef15c7f38d3c6d8ef2dfccf7250d4764f3-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. , is technically hammered out through 12 appropriations bills passed by Congress and signed by the president. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThis morning, President Biden will send Congress a jumbo-sized $6 trillion budget for FY2022, the NYT reported yesterday. What's inside? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! The budget is also expected to outline additional policy proposals like... If it passes, federal spending will eclipse records set during WWII. While the bill falls short of funding goals for several of Biden’s priorities—particularly investments in rail, public transit, and clean energy—the White House said it's big enough to continue negotiations into next week, which means blowing past Biden's original Memorial Day deadline to pass an infrastructure deal.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/biden-propose-6t-budget</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>government</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/05/27/biden-propose-6t-budget</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:24:01 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>

</channel>
</rss>
