<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <atom:link href="https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2022/05/05/users/1/web_requests/22/MorningBrew.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
 <atom:icon>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2022/05/05/favicon.ico</atom:icon>
 

 <title>MorningBrew as a feed</title>
 <description>This is a feed of recent MorningBrew articles published by Huginn</description>
 <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2022/05/05</link>
 <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:13:23 -0700</lastBuildDate>
 <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:13:23 -0700</pubDate>
 <ttl>60</ttl>
 <item>
  <title>If Roe v. Wade is overturned, abortion pills could be the next target</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/3f6d143d150eab22bf1dc7216e1897c0c8d1d702-3019x2263.jpg?rect=0,125,3019,2013&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Abortion pills (aka medication abortions) already account for over half of all abortions in the US, according to the Guttmacher Institute. Big picture: Most of the states waiting to pass restrictions on abortion have already attempted to make it harder to access abortion pills. How medication abortions work: Two drugs, when taken within the first 10 weeks of pregnancy, are 95% effective. —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Texas passed a bill in December that would slap health care workers with jail time and a $10,000 fine if they prescribed abortion pills through telehealth services. With federal protection out of the way, abortion pills would likely become the next target of conservative legislators and the anti-abortion movement. But there are other methods for abortions that are harder to restrict.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/roe-v-wade-abortion-pills</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Health</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/roe-v-wade-abortion-pills</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:11:22 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>E-commerce is flatlining in the first quarter</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/4810ff2efd8faab4b8e119616eed20cd25b05fa8-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Amazon set the stage last week, reporting a 3% drop in online sales in the first three months of the year, and forecasting a meager 3% sales growth for the current quarter. Etsy and eBay shares both dropped by double digits yesterday after giving weak guidance for the current quarter. —MK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! As shoppers abandon the tab for the fitting room, online retailers will have to pivot to stay competitive.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/e-commerce-flatline-first-quarter-online-sales</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>E-Commerce</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/e-commerce-flatline-first-quarter-online-sales</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 14:56:23 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Elon lines up $7.1 billion in additional financing for his Twitter takeover</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-05-05/image-1b0a3356288c194e44a71d92c2e09278b92cf83f-480x360-gif/giphy(3).webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The Saudi royal, who is one of Twitter’s largest backers already, said he’d roll over his current investment into the “new” Twitter. They include…Prince Alwaleed bin Talal: $1.9 billion. Seems like Elon will be pretty hands-on.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/05/elon-lines-up-usd7-1-billion-in-additional-financing-for-his-twitter-takeover</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Social Media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/05/elon-lines-up-usd7-1-billion-in-additional-financing-for-his-twitter-takeover</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 14:41:20 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Ransomware attacks are part of the cost of doing business</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-05-05/image-ec0236d107c049ff19518d77756b78d58d3a34ea-1500x1000-gif/ransomware-0422.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. A 2022 report surveyed over 1,200 security leaders and found that 79% of those had been the target of a ransomware attack, and 35% admitted at least one of those attacks led to the loss of access to data and systems. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Coalition is one of the largest companies insuring against cyberattacks. In an exercise called a penetration test, or pentest for short, a company will attempt to hack its own infrastructure with a designated red team of hackers (i.e. bad guys) versus a defending blue team (the good guys). Though the FBI advises companies against paying ransom, many do because the alternative can mean a massive data leak, loss of profits, or worse. Ransomware as a Service offers technical support for hackers who require guidance on their ransomware attack, as well as services to transfer encrypted files once the ransom has been paid. Insurance companies are sometimes on the hook for ransomware payments. While many large organizations conduct threat assessments of their systems, the limitations of a test can prevent a realistic hack simulation. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. These macros allow a background program to run and execute code so that a hacker could pilfer data or upgrade their security privileges and wade further into the company. The hacker says they’ve already downloaded 250 gigabytes of user data and are threatening to release it if the company doesn’t comply within 24 hours. The JBS hack is exceptional, not simply because of its impact on America’s beef supply chain, but because it illustrates that hacks are now part of the cost of doing business. In one exercise, Rawlins’s team gained access to the message center of a stock exchange. The average company has more resources to protect against hackers than it did a decade ago, Sentonas said, but ransomware has become more frequent and far more sophisticated, including the rise of Ransomware as a Service. André Nogueira was woken up early one Sunday morning by a phone call telling him that his company, JBS Foods, the world’s largest meat supplier, had been hacked. Then he has to figure out if a ransom payment is legal or if it will violate any sanctions, which can be an issue with hackers outside the US. In some cases, Chainalysis can unmask the identity of a hacker involved with a ransomware attack, he said. Carter said he spends most of his time dealing with ransomware. He was given the distressing details: A group of hackers called REvil had gained access to the company’s critical infrastructure and was holding it hostage, demanding a ransom of $11 million in bitcoin. Realistic pentests and red-team exercises are important, Sentonas said, because “you play it like you practice.” Because getting hacked and paying a ransom is now a mundane business expense, a new industry has also popped up: cyber liability insurance. “The extortion piece is one part.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/ransomware-attacks-cost-of-business</link>
  <author>Ashwin Rodrigues</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/ransomware-attacks-cost-of-business</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 11:06:37 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Guinness World Record set for longest career at one company</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/e38bbcc83bded8b53eb6174ce6e93634563501ea-678x452.png?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The Brazilian recently set a Guinness World Record for spending his 84-year career at a single company. —JW All I care about is that tomorrow will be another day in which I will wake up, get up, exercise, and go to work; you need to get busy with the present, not the past or the future. Why? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/Guinness-World-Record-longest-career-one-company?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/Guinness-World-Record-longest-career-one-company?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:01:30 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Online mental health care startup Cerebral will stop new Adderall prescriptions</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d2a02941c824615453cb3fa17da4f9f8ff5bd3a1-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Following a funding round led by SoftBank last December, Cerebral was valued at $4.8 billion. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Cerebral, the mental health telehealth startup, said yesterday it would pause Adderall and other ADHD medication prescriptions for new patients.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/cerebral-mental-health-startup-stop-new-adderall-perscriptions?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Health Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/cerebral-mental-health-startup-stop-new-adderall-perscriptions?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:01:30 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Fed enacts largest interest rate hike since 2000</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/3ca67bf91701f08ad3ffb444609649404e71982a-5101x3400.jpg?rect=1,0,5100,3400&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. But hiking interest rates is just one tool the Fed plans to use to bring inflation back down. “Inflation is much too high, and we understand the hardship it is causing,” Powell said at a press conference yesterday—the first one he’s held in-person since the pandemic began. Given that keeping prices stable is one of the Fed’s main responsibilities, critics say it’s been a total slacker over the past year and needs to get hiking to bring down inflation from its stratospheric heights. The Fed has heard that message. Fed Chair Jerome Powell jacked up interest rates by a half-percentage point yesterday. —NF Even Janet Yellen, the current Treasury Secretary and former Fed Chair, said Powell would need to be “skillful and lucky” to get this plane on the ground without hurting anyone.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/04/fed-hikes-interest-rates-the-most-since-2000?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/04/fed-hikes-interest-rates-the-most-since-2000?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Fed hikes interest rates the most since 2000</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/3ca67bf91701f08ad3ffb444609649404e71982a-5101x3400.jpg?rect=1,0,5100,3400&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. But hiking interest rates is just one tool the Fed plans to use to bring inflation back down. “Inflation is much too high, and we understand the hardship it is causing,” Powell said at a press conference yesterday—the first one he’s held in-person since the pandemic began. Given that keeping prices stable is one of the Fed’s main responsibilities, critics say it’s been a total slacker over the past year and needs to get hiking to bring down inflation from its stratospheric heights. The Fed has heard that message. Fed Chair Jerome Powell jacked up interest rates by a half-percentage point yesterday. —NF Even Janet Yellen, the current Treasury Secretary and former Fed Chair, said Powell would need to be “skillful and lucky” to get this plane on the ground without hurting anyone.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/04/fed-hikes-interest-rates-the-most-since-2000</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/04/fed-hikes-interest-rates-the-most-since-2000</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 15:16:26 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Online mental health care startup Cerebral will stop new Adderall prescriptions</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d2a02941c824615453cb3fa17da4f9f8ff5bd3a1-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Following a funding round led by SoftBank last December, Cerebral was valued at $4.8 billion. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Cerebral, the mental health telehealth startup, said yesterday it would pause Adderall and other ADHD medicine prescriptions for new patients.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/cerebral-mental-health-startup-stop-new-adderall-perscriptions</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Health Tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/cerebral-mental-health-startup-stop-new-adderall-perscriptions</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 15:16:25 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Guinness World Record set for longest career at one company</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/e38bbcc83bded8b53eb6174ce6e93634563501ea-678x452.png?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The Brazilian recently set a Guinness World Record for spending his 84-year career at a single company. —JW All I care about is that tomorrow will be another day in which I will wake up, get up, exercise, and go to work; you need to get busy with the present, not the past or the future. Why? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/Guinness-World-Record-longest-career-one-company</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/Guinness-World-Record-longest-career-one-company</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 15:01:33 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Imperial Banking System: Too Far Away to Fail</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-2ae1354e3b21fada0ea1bdb61ed556c323cba213-480x270-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Feinstein estimates the Death Star 2 would’ve cost $419 quintillion to build ($226 quintillion in steel alone). Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The Rebel Alliance would need to prep a rescue package of at least 15% of GGP in order to prevent “catastrophic economic collapse.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/03/the-imperial-banking-system-too-far-away-to-fail?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/03/the-imperial-banking-system-too-far-away-to-fail?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 02:00:35 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Western megadrought uncovered a 40-year-old homicide on Lake Mead</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7575cb44e71631b3ad3d6dae0b0dd0d1ba288f06-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. But, record temperatures and declining snowmelt runoff have led to the lake’s lowest level on record. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Well, this isn’t the work of a clumsy murderer—just one who didn’t predict Lake Mead’s drastic water level plunge. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeA 40-year-old, potentially Mafia-related homicide has been uncovered on the shores of Lake Mead, thanks in large part to climate change. On Sunday, visitors walking along Lake Mead’s shoreline discovered a partially corroded barrel containing a body. 25 million people and millions of acres of farmland use Lake Mead’s water. —MK Lake Mead is currently around 1,054 feet above sea level, its lowest level since it was first filled in the 1930s.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/lake-mead-homicide-megadrought?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Environment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/lake-mead-homicide-megadrought?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 02:00:35 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Politicians and protesters react to Roe v. Wade being threatened</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/56f7889c273095b5677a77911bbf32ac55dcae0a-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Wade in legislation to affirm abortion access in all states. To recap: Politico published a leaked draft opinion from the Supreme Court that suggested it would strike down Roe v. Wade, which would leave abortion legislation up to individual states and strip away abortion rights for millions of Americans. The reaction in DCPresident Biden—who promised to protect the federal right to an abortion during his campaign—criticized the draft opinion and warned that overturning Roe v. Speaking of the midterms, primary season kicked off yesterday with a big win by venture capitalist JD Vance in the closely watched GOP Senate primary. —JW css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! As for Democratic leaders…California Gov. Gavin Newsom and other governors promised to protect the right to abortion in their states.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/politicians-and-protesters-react-to-roe-v-wade-being-threatened?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/politicians-and-protesters-react-to-roe-v-wade-being-threatened?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 02:00:35 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Politicians and protesters react to Roe v. Wade being threatened</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/e4e8fdcbf25ef918cc7cf700d2a680df1848e100-1200x800.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Yesterday morning, one rock climber with the pseudonym “Pro-Life Spider-Man” free-soloed San Francisco’s 1,070-foot Salesforce tower. The reaction in DCPresident Biden—who promised to protect the federal right to an abortion during his campaign—criticized the draft opinion and warned that overturning Roe v. To recap: Politico published a leaked draft opinion from the Supreme Court that suggested it would strike down Roe v. Wade in legislation to affirm abortion access in all states. Wade “would set us back 50 years and disproportionately impact the most vulnerable women in society.” Democrats could be motivated to show up en masse at the polls to elect pro-choice leaders. Wade, which would leave abortion legislation up to individual states and strip away abortion rights for millions of Americans. —JW</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/politicians-and-protesters-react-to-roe-v-wade-being-threatened</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/politicians-and-protesters-react-to-roe-v-wade-being-threatened</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 15:16:30 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Imperial Banking System: Too Far Away to Fail</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-2ae1354e3b21fada0ea1bdb61ed556c323cba213-480x270-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Feinstein estimates the Death Star 2 would’ve cost $419 quintillion to build ($226 quintillion in steel alone). Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The Rebel Alliance would need to prep a rescue package of at least 15% of GGP in order to prevent “catastrophic economic collapse.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/03/the-imperial-banking-system-too-far-away-to-fail</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/03/the-imperial-banking-system-too-far-away-to-fail</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 14:31:26 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Western megadrought uncovered a 40-year-old homicide on Lake Mead</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7575cb44e71631b3ad3d6dae0b0dd0d1ba288f06-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. But, record temperatures and declining snowmelt runoff have led to the lake’s lowest level on record. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Well, this isn’t the work of a clumsy murderer—just one who didn’t predict Lake Mead’s drastic water level plunge. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeA 40-year-old, potentially Mafia-related homicide has been uncovered on the shores of Lake Mead, thanks in large part to climate change. On Sunday, visitors walking along Lake Mead’s shoreline discovered a partially corroded barrel containing a body. 25 million people and millions of acres of farmland use Lake Mead’s water. —MK Lake Mead is currently around 1,054 feet above sea level, its lowest level since it was first filled in the 1930s.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/lake-mead-homicide-megadrought</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Environment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/lake-mead-homicide-megadrought</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 14:16:27 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>John Cena, Vanessa Hudgens and more team up for a new cocktail brand</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-05-02/image-f7c7bfafe0cebdcf846bc76c2b35eb376e6f9ffc-480x270-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. : Premixed cocktails were the fastest-growing segment of the spirits market in 2021. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Cena’s drink is four parts muscle milk, one part absinthe and it’s called “Muscle Absinthe”—JK, it’s actually just an old-fashioned. —MK</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/celebrity-cocktail-john-cena-thomas-ashbourne?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Food &amp; Bev</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/celebrity-cocktail-john-cena-thomas-ashbourne?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:01:30 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>10% of Russia’s tech sector is expected to leave the country</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/767cc0953314f51d71381a22d384aaffdb4280ca-4516x3387.jpg?rect=0,188,4516,3011&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. A group representing IT companies in Russia said in April that 50k–70k tech workers had already left Russia since the country’s invasion of Ukraine, and it’s expecting 100k more to leave by the end of this month. Big picture: Russia has scrambled to keep its disgruntled tech workers happy. In a $33 billion funding request for Ukraine that Biden unveiled last week, he included a proposal to make it easier for Russian STEM workers to come code in the US. —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/russia-tech-sector-mass-exodus?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>International</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/russia-tech-sector-mass-exodus?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Supreme Court votes to strike down Roe, according to Politico report</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/264283b100cca09e2290ded630db4ee45b490fd6-7165x4733.jpg?rect=33,0,7100,4733&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Stephen Breyer, Sonia Sotomayor, and Elena Kagan are working on at least one dissent. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe Supreme Court has voted to overturn Roe v. Wade, according to a draft opinion that was leaked to Politico. Wade, abortion laws would be left to individual states. Just yesterday, Amazon joined several other corporate giants that have pledged to reimburse US employees who have to travel for abortions as states have moved to pass restrictive abortion laws. Should SCOTUS overturn Roe v. Why was Roe even being considered? It’s a shocking development that would end the constitutional right to an abortion that has been enshrined since 1973. In fact, states passed 106 laws restricting abortion access in 2021, the most in any year since the Roe decision. —NF What happens next? How they voted:Justice Samuel Alito, who wrote the decision to overturn Roe, was joined by Clarence Thomas, Neil M. Chief Justice John Roberts’s vote was unknown, but sources told CNN that he reportedly does not want to completely overturn Roe.Alito, in the majority opinion, blasted Roe, calling it “egregiously wrong from the start.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/02/supreme-court-votes-to-strike-down-roe-according-to-politico-report?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/02/supreme-court-votes-to-strike-down-roe-according-to-politico-report?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Supreme Court votes to strike down Roe, according to Politico report</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/264283b100cca09e2290ded630db4ee45b490fd6-7165x4733.jpg?rect=33,0,7100,4733&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Stephen Breyer, Sonia Sotomayor, and Elena Kagan are working on at least one dissent. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe Supreme Court has voted to overturn Roe v. Wade, according to a draft opinion that was leaked to Politico. Wade, abortion laws would be left to individual states. Just yesterday, Amazon joined several other corporate giants that have pledged to reimburse US employees who have to travel for abortions as states have moved to pass restrictive abortion laws. Should SCOTUS overturn Roe v. Why was Roe even being considered? It’s a shocking development that would end the constitutional right to an abortion that has been enshrined since 1973. In fact, states passed 106 laws restricting abortion access in 2021, the most in any year since the Roe decision. —NF What happens next? How they voted:Justice Samuel Alito, who wrote the decision to overturn Roe, was joined by Clarence Thomas, Neil M. Chief Justice John Roberts’s vote was unknown, but sources told CNN that he reportedly does not want to completely overturn Roe.Alito, in the majority opinion, blasted Roe, calling it “egregiously wrong from the start.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/02/supreme-court-votes-to-strike-down-roe-according-to-politico-report</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/02/supreme-court-votes-to-strike-down-roe-according-to-politico-report</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 20:31:33 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>10% of Russia’s tech sector is expected to leave the country</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/767cc0953314f51d71381a22d384aaffdb4280ca-4516x3387.jpg?rect=0,188,4516,3011&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. A group representing IT companies in Russia said in April that 50k–70k tech workers have already left Russia since the country’s invasion of Ukraine, and it’s expecting 100k more to leave by the end of this month. Big picture: Russia has scrambled to keep its disgruntled tech workers happy within its borders. In a $33 billion funding request for Ukraine that Biden unveiled last week, he included a proposal to make it easier for Russian STEM workers to come code in the US. —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/russia-tech-sector-mass-exodus</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>International</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/russia-tech-sector-mass-exodus</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 14:56:27 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>John Cena, Vanessa Hudgens and more team up for a new cocktail brand</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-05-02/image-f7c7bfafe0cebdcf846bc76c2b35eb376e6f9ffc-480x270-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Cena’s drink is four parts muscle milk, one part absinthe and it’s called “Muscle Absinthe”—JK, it’s actually just an old-fashioned. —MK</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/celebrity-cocktail-john-cena-thomas-ashbourne</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Food &amp; Bev</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/celebrity-cocktail-john-cena-thomas-ashbourne</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 14:56:27 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>May’s GOP primaries are big-money affairs</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/b28535805554d34e351973248c12bd04cae0c9af-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Advertising spends in the PA primary hit $45 million as of late April, with weeks left until voters head to the polls. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeNow that May is upon us, midterm election season has begun in earnest: 13 states head to the polls to vote in primaries this month, including elections in Ohio and Indiana today. His super PAC recently received a $3.5 million donation from billionaire Peter Thiel. Citadel CEO Ken Griffin has donated $7.5 million to a pro-McCormick super PAC so far.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/may-gop-primaries-elections</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Government</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/may-gop-primaries-elections</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 14:56:26 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The week ahead: May 2</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/3789510ef37549dcb36370c5217f6c93d9a9d250-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. In the holiday world: Cinco de Mayo is on Thursday and Mother’s Day is on Sunday.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/01/the-week-ahead-may-2?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/01/the-week-ahead-may-2?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:01:31 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>How the Fed actually hikes interest rates</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/fd383d4e9b83a663e666607382e3ff03ea534125-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. When a bank has excess cash on hand, it can loan it out to another one that needs it. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeOn Wednesday, the Fed is expected to hike interest rates even higher to bring inflation back from levels we haven’t seen in decades. Instead, the central bank adjusts what’s known as the “federal funds rate,” which is the average interest rate that banks pay each other for overnight loans. This week, we’re going to carve out some space to explore interest rate hikes from a variety of angles. The banks lending to each other typically settle on an interest rate near the midpoint of the Fed’s range. Because Fed Chair Jerome Powell doesn’t just show up at your bank and tell them to raise their interest rates. Like, what are the mechanics? What that is: Commercial banks borrow and lend money to each other so that they can meet liquidity requirements set by regulators before the business day begins. You should also know that the Fed picks a range for the federal funds rate—not a specific number. In March, when the Fed hiked interest rates for the first time following the onset of the pandemic, it raised its target range from 0–25 basis points to 25–50.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/01/how-the-fed-actually-hikes-interest-rates?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/01/how-the-fed-actually-hikes-interest-rates?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:01:31 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Warren Buffett holds court at the Berkshire Hathaway annual shareholders meeting</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d8b97dc8ffafb5868690d805d935c084f286f1a3-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. It’s unlikely that Buffett has ever touched an Xbox controller, but Berkshire Hathaway is now the largest shareholder of Activision Blizzard after amassing a 9.5% stake. Buffett said that inflation “swindles almost everybody” and was a result of the Fed’s gargantuan stimulus measures to prop up the economy during the pandemic. And…video games? So what did he buy? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIn an investing world of air fryers, Warren Buffett is a slow cooker.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/01/buffett-berkshire-hathaway-annual-shareholders-meeting?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Investing</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/01/buffett-berkshire-hathaway-annual-shareholders-meeting?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:01:30 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Warren Buffett holds court at the Berkshire Hathaway annual shareholders meeting</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d8b97dc8ffafb5868690d805d935c084f286f1a3-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. It’s unlikely that Buffett has ever touched an Xbox controller, but Berkshire Hathaway is now the largest shareholder of Activision Blizzard after amassing a 9.5% stake. Around the topic of the stock market, Buffett said the influx of new traders buying and selling stocks during the pandemic has turned the market into “almost totally a casino” in which large American companies have become “poker chips.” Buffett said that inflation “swindles almost everybody” and was a result of the Fed’s gargantuan stimulus measures to prop up the economy during the pandemic. Of course, Buffett would never call it “buying the dip” because he doesn’t believe in timing the market. And…video games? So what did he buy? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/01/buffett-berkshire-hathaway-annual-shareholders-meeting</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Investing</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/01/buffett-berkshire-hathaway-annual-shareholders-meeting</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 17:41:29 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>How the Fed actually hikes interest rates</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/fd383d4e9b83a663e666607382e3ff03ea534125-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. When a bank has excess cash on hand, it can loan it out to another one that needs it. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThis week, the Fed is expected to hike interest rates even higher to bring inflation back from levels we haven’t seen in decades. Instead, the central bank adjusts what’s known as the “federal funds rate,” which is the average interest rate that banks pay each other for overnight loans. This week, we’re going to carve out some space to explore interest rate hikes from a variety of angles. Because Fed Chair Jerome Powell doesn’t just show up at your bank and tell them to raise their interest rates. The banks lending to each other typically settle on an interest rate near the midpoint of the Fed’s range. Like, what are the mechanics? What that is: Commercial banks borrow and lend money to each other so that they can meet liquidity requirements set by regulators before the business day begins. You should also know that the Fed picks a range for the federal funds rate—not a specific number. In March, when the Fed hiked interest rates for the first time following the onset of the pandemic, it raised its target range from 0–25 basis points to 25–50.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/01/how-the-fed-actually-hikes-interest-rates</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/01/how-the-fed-actually-hikes-interest-rates</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 17:41:28 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The week ahead: May 2</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/3789510ef37549dcb36370c5217f6c93d9a9d250-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. In the holiday world: Cinco de Mayo is on Thursday and Mother’s Day is on Sunday</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/01/the-week-ahead-may-2</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/05/01/the-week-ahead-may-2</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 17:26:27 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Turntable: May 2</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d6d5ff67f65ccfc42ccab384cde8bbc6f76d8507-1920x1080.png?rect=150,0,1620,1080&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/turntable-may-2</link>
  <author>Mary Tobler</author>
  <categories>games</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/turntable-may-2</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 16:41:27 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Timed Turntable: May 2</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d6d5ff67f65ccfc42ccab384cde8bbc6f76d8507-1920x1080.png?rect=150,0,1620,1080&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/timed-turntable-may-2</link>
  <author>Mary Tobler</author>
  <categories>games</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/timed-turntable-may-2</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 16:41:27 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Why are dolphins guarding a Russian naval base?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/247d66442b7080245b0ac3da8fb36de678621182-1024x681.jpg?rect=1,0,1022,681&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The US jump-started its marine mammal military program in 1960, primarily employing bottlenose dolphins and sea lions to accomplish a variety of underwater tasks humans just don’t have the fins for. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeWe know a decent amount about the US’ use of marine mammals for military purposes after information was leaked about the program in 1992. Their most likely porpoise—sorry, purpose—is to defend Russian warships against enemy divers, serving as a crucial line of defense for what is Russia’s most important naval base on the Black Sea.While we can see you there looking shocked at the existence of a Russian dolphin infantry division…Marine mammals have a long history of military serviceAnd not just for the Russians. Dolphins’ skills were on display during the Iraq War in 2003. Big picture: Over time, humans have become a lot more skilled at leveraging marine mammals to win wars.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/29/why-are-dolphins-guarding-a-russian-naval-base?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/29/why-are-dolphins-guarding-a-russian-naval-base?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>When a dog-sitting gig turns into an awkward conversation with your boss</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7b6de1bb891bb0dd9e289abb0a591582a5da30e6-1503x603.png?rect=299,0,905,603&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. A key question I have is whether your boss is aware of your side hustle. I dog-sit as a side hustle, so I happily obliged when he asked if I was free. The first of the month is traditionally a big day for bones: Some of us owe them, others collect them, and a hip-hop group that bears the name gave us an iconic 90s track to help mark the calendar. What should I do? Anything nagging at you? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! My boss has a new puppy and needed someone to watch her for the weekend. Is it possible your boss was simply biding his time so that he could wake up and settle his debts with the rest of us today? Share your workplace conundrum with Make It Work here. Probably not, so let’s work out your best move here. I feel awkward asking, especially since he’s my boss, but I deserve to be paid for the work I did. Ask Shane here. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeEach week, our workplace whisperer Shane Loughnane answers a reader-submitted question about problems at work.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/29/when-a-dog-sitting-gig-turns-into-an-awkward-conversation-with-your-boss?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Shane Loughnane</author>
  <categories>Work life</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/29/when-a-dog-sitting-gig-turns-into-an-awkward-conversation-with-your-boss?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:01:27 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Icebreakers with...the indistractable author Nir Eyal</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/20a60b9610e2c0ee9e0c5a0ce50827ddcde75a3d-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. I wouldn’t advocate saying, “Oh, if I work for 30 minutes, then I'll be able to putz around on a video game.” Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. So that’s when it’s a problem: when we say we’re going to do one thing and yet we’re doing something else. What I want to cater to is the person who’s like me: I would be the kind of person who said I’d do one thing and I do something else. I would say I’m going to be fully present with people I love, and yet I used my phone as opposed to being really there for my daughter and my wife. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/29/icebreakers-with-the-indistractable-author-nir-eyal?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/29/icebreakers-with-the-indistractable-author-nir-eyal?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:01:26 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Stock watch: May 1</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/de2962601c0dcd9d28980412d8f3ac1f66d20012-1500x2000.png?rect=0,500,1500,1000&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/29/stock-watch-may-1?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Culture</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/29/stock-watch-may-1?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:01:24 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Saturday sketch: How to improve Twitter</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/c1382f089dce6166a24879b9f605b6d625a0909e-1500x1613.png?rect=0,306,1500,1000&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/29/saturday-sketch-how-to-improve-twitter?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories></categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/29/saturday-sketch-how-to-improve-twitter?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 00:01:30 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Johnny Depp, Amber Heard’s defamation trial is a social media circus</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/b1ed26c029ef65b15b2fec2b4c0d8c06975acdca-995x572.png?rect=69,0,858,572&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. TikToks tagged with the hashtag #justiceforjohnnydepp are nearing 6 billion views, and one viral video shows an LA Starbucks with a full tip jar that reads “Johnny Depp” and an empty one with “Amber Heard” on it. Even brands are chiming in: Milani Cosmetics made a TikTok contradicting Heard’s attorney’s claim that Heard used a specific makeup kit to cover up bruises from domestic violence, saying the kit referenced wasn’t available yet. —MM css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIt never takes too long for a celebrity trial to go completely off the rails, but in just two-and-a-half weeks, the Johnny Depp–Amber Heard libel trial has overrun TikTok. Depp supporters have flocked to social media and YouTube livestreams of the trial to share their extremely anti-Amber Heard views.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/Johnny-depp-amber-heard-trial-social-media-circus?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Social Media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/Johnny-depp-amber-heard-trial-social-media-circus?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 00:01:30 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Bored Ape Yacht Club is getting a metaverse</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/fe8f43f0dc262427c42c2552bcd3b7a409981538-1920x1080.png?rect=150,0,1620,1080&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Zoom out: Bored Apes swung onto the NFT scene almost one year ago exactly—when volume for searches like “non-fungible thingamabob” was at its peak. Yesterday, Bored Ape NFTs hit a record-high floor price of 152 ETH (about $430,000), per The Block Research. —JW At 9pm ET, preapproved buyers with no Saturday night plans can buy “Otherdeeds” for a flat 305 ApeCoins (a digital currency created last month), which was equivalent to more than $8,300 at Thursday’s high. In other words, to many people a Bored Ape is more than just a JPEG.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/nfts-bored-ape-yacht-club-metaverse?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>Crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/nfts-bored-ape-yacht-club-metaverse?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 00:01:30 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Nasdaq suffers its worst monthly drop since 2008</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2022-04-29/image-92db9d07dfdf39c640b7cb83c896b4a33e2b4b45-480x360-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. With China locking down cities at the first trace of Covid, American companies whose products are made in Chinese factories aren’t able to fulfill orders. In April, the S&amp;P dropped 8.8%, the Dow 4.9%, and the Nasdaq, 13.3%—which marks that index’s worst month since 2008.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/29/the-nasdaq-suffers-its-worst-monthly-drop-since-2008?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Markets</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/29/the-nasdaq-suffers-its-worst-monthly-drop-since-2008?utm_campaign=mb&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_source=morning_brew&amp;mid={{md5(profile.email)}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 00:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Stock watch: May 1</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/de2962601c0dcd9d28980412d8f3ac1f66d20012-1500x2000.png?rect=0,500,1500,1000&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/29/stock-watch-may-1</link>
  <author>Max Knoblauch</author>
  <categories>Culture</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2022/04/29/stock-watch-may-1</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 15:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>

</channel>
</rss>
