<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <atom:link href="https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2023/03/02/users/1/web_requests/22/MorningBrew.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
 <atom:icon>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2023/03/02/favicon.ico</atom:icon>
 

 <title>MorningBrew as a feed</title>
 <description>This is a feed of recent MorningBrew articles published by Huginn</description>
 <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2023/03/02</link>
 <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:31:55 -0800</lastBuildDate>
 <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:31:55 -0800</pubDate>
 <ttl>60</ttl>
 <item>
  <title>Name, Image, and Likeness Relaxations Creates New Industry Overnight</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-6196f1d1296ae0707ad37cdf0529e68f5235f9a0-480x268-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. She’s the only one with more than 1 million followers on both TikTok and Instagram. + Further NIL reading: The top 20 athletes who could capitalize on NIL and the earning potential of athletes across sports and endorsement deals. 25 states passed NIL bills that challenged the NCAA’s rules banning student athletes from monetizing their popularity.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/07/01/name-image-likeness-relaxations-creates-new-industry-overnight</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/07/01/name-image-likeness-relaxations-creates-new-industry-overnight</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:45 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: July 2</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/dabd8d09139883c0f53a9422510ac991d074d4e0-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. (New York Times) css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeStat: Wally Funk, 82, will become the oldest person to go to space after being asked by Jeff Bezos to accompany him on the Blue Origin mission July 20.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/07/01/key-performance-indicators-july-2</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/07/01/key-performance-indicators-july-2</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:43 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Robinhood Announces IPO After $70 Million Finra Fine</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/aee338d1047d71515e9606ca653782797e1ab42f-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. For instance, Robinhood wants you to buy into Robinhood’s IPO on Robinhood. The trading app will list its shares under the symbol HOOD in an IPO that reflects the growing influence of the individual trader on Wall Street. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! In an unusual move, it’s setting aside 20%–35% of its Class A stock for its customers, as opposed to bankers. Robinhood’s revenue surged to $959 million in 2020, a 245% jump from 2019. Bottom line: Robinhood’s highly anticipated IPO is the belle of the ball on a packed dance floor.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/07/01/robinhood-announces-ipo-70-million-finra-fine</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>ipo</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/07/01/robinhood-announces-ipo-70-million-finra-fine</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:43 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>New York Has The Worst Traffic In The US</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d55ea6a02fd7d5f1e9a1345286cae7469ce2160d-5723x3808.jpg?rect=6,0,5712,3808&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeNew Yorkers have one less excuse to complain about Los Angeles, because the country’s worst stop-and-go conditions moved to the East Coast last year.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/30/new-york-worst-traffic-us</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>traffic</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/30/new-york-worst-traffic-us</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:43 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>China's Communist Party Turns 100</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/8afd03af351ec1d1c108563f543c5013c73eed60-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Bottom line: At 100 years old, the Communist Party remains a potent global force led by a president who could be the first since Mao to rule until he dies. After the Communists gained power in the 1949 revolution, Mao initiated a series of disastrous economic reforms that led to the deaths of tens of millions of people. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. China will eclipse the US as the world’s largest economy by 2028, per one estimate. Since the liberalization of China’s economy, the country has developed a close business relationship with the West—just last week Nike’s CEO said, “Nike is a brand that is of China and for China.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/30/chinas-communist-party-turns-100</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>geopolitics</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/30/chinas-communist-party-turns-100</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:42 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Finra Levies Robinhood Its Biggest Fine Ever</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/ecfd8bf194468bbb0384893ceef6d40c2ef01bec-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Two major outages resulted in tens of thousands of losses for users who weren’t able to conduct trades and couldn’t reach customer service agents. One 20-year-old died by suicide in June 2020 after seeing -$720,000 in his account, when his balance was actually about half that.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/30/finra-levies-robinhood-biggest-fine-ever</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>finance</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/30/finra-levies-robinhood-biggest-fine-ever</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:41 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Top Five Business Stories of Q2</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/5176a6853752ec0cb4da799d6c8bfb414a715619-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Inflation scariesWith prices increasing at their highest rate in more than a decade, the No. 1 business story of the quarter could only be inflation. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Let's count down the top 5 business stories of last quarter, as chosen (correctly) by Morning Brew's editorial staff. Fed Chair Jerome Powell has argued higher inflation is mostly transitory, while legendary investor Paul Tudor Jones responded, “That one just doesn’t work the way I see the world.” css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. Covid who? Meme stocks capitalizeIn the winter, executives at meme stock companies were flummoxed by their newfound popularity; last quarter they decided to do something about it.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/30/top-five-business-stories-q2</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde,</author>
  <categories>business</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/30/top-five-business-stories-q2</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:40 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Time Capsule: Q2 2021</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/06f7221f5532d6edd6aea892827618c2c62f46f8-1280x720.png?rect=100,0,1080,720&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. 26% of podcasts in the Apple Podcasts app have produced just one episode. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeFacts on factsWe read a lot of news stories over the past three months.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/30/time-capsule-q2-2021</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>culture</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/30/time-capsule-q2-2021</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:36 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>SpaceX’s Starlink Internet Service Has 69,420 Users</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-aabe1de647dce383a01af96ace2fb3bc218611c4-480x267-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Musk said Starlink could make up to $30 billion in revenue per year—about 10 times the revenue of the rocket-launching side of SpaceX. Starlink provides internet via a network of over 1,500 satellites orbiting low enough for stargazers to spot them overhead. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! 69,420, SpaceX CEO Elon Musk said yesterday.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/29/spacexs-starlink-internet-service-69420-users</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/29/spacexs-starlink-internet-service-69420-users</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:35 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Facebook Launches Bulletin, Its Subscription Newsletter Service</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-19c0ae2eaac258b761dccc481fb12a4f12fa9aba-480x270-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The other major competitor in the space is Twitter, after it purchased newsletter platform Revue in January. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Zoom out: Bulletin is Facebook’s latest product that chases individual creators; its previous launch was a Clubhouse competitor for live audio content, which Zuck used to announce Bulletin.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/29/facebook-launches-bulletin-subscription-newsletter-service</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/29/facebook-launches-bulletin-subscription-newsletter-service</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:34 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>United Makes Big Bet on the Future of Air Travel</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/b52c4bc9bf93bb3cf77e7124926a0e4a71971c7d-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. One does not simply order 270 state-of-the-art planes worth more than $30 billion and then leave them unused in the hangar. Big picture: With the worst of the crisis behind them, United and other US airlines are barreling ahead with plans to target a specific traveler—the one who pays extra for “priority boarding.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/29/united-makes-big-bet-future-air-travel</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>aviation</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/29/united-makes-big-bet-future-air-travel</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:33 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>US Home Price Growth Hits a Record High in April</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/034bcbf7731eaa80bd50fb12a549c3b325aa3905-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Another buyer in Austin, TX, bought two houses from the same seller so he could get the one he really wanted. Actually, experts predict the housing market won’t implode like it did 10 years ago. Sounds pretty bubbly, right? And now? A key national home price index skyrocketed 14.6% nationwide in April, the largest annual gain in more than 30 years. What’s happening: Low mortgage rates and a move-to-the-suburb frenzy have fueled demand for bigger houses, but builders face shortages of materials and workers can’t keep up the pace.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/29/us-home-price-growth-hits-record-high-april</link>
  <author>Sherry Qin</author>
  <categories>real estate</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/29/us-home-price-growth-hits-record-high-april</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:32 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Two Big Banks Announce Hybrid Work Schedules Amid ‘Get Back to the Office’ Attitude on Wall Street</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-0f5f284d2ab0547f0591f06549268d301e7128f7-400x225-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Synchrony will offer three different office options: permanently remote for those who love their noon showers, satellite locations for employees to reserve desks ad hoc, or hybrid schedules with an assigned desk. In May, JPMorgan and Goldman Sachs announced they would start bringing staff back this summer. Bottom line: Both UBS and Synchrony hope that offering flexible work schedules will help them retain and attract workers, which is necessary since 41% of employees globally are considering leaving their current employer this year. UBS, the Swiss lending giant, as well as Synchrony Financial, provider of Amazon and PayPal credit cards, both recently announced hybrid work plans that won’t require employees to stand on a sticky train five days a week. UBS plans to let two-thirds of its staff work remotely several days a week.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/28/two-big-banks-announce-hybrid-work-schedules-amid-get-back-office-attitude-wall-street</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>finance</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/28/two-big-banks-announce-hybrid-work-schedules-amid-get-back-office-attitude-wall-street</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:31 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: June 29</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/4177530f7dab26d367f68427a7e2fddd5c78f01a-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. (Vox) css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/28/key-performance-indicators-june-29</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/28/key-performance-indicators-june-29</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:31 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>MWC Returns to Barcelona After One-Year Hiatus</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/939fc84f48ef72d0118746d011e7177b888ce2cf-1024x682.jpg?rect=1,0,1023,682&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The line for coffee will be much shorter than usual. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Zoom out: Barcelona hopes enough of those virtual attendees get FOMO and buy plane tickets for next year's show. The people are attendees at the Mobile World Congress (MWC), the largest mobile industry trade show, which kicked off in Barcelona yesterday after a one-year hiatus due to the pandemic.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/28/mwc-returns-barcelona-oneyear-hiatus</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/28/mwc-returns-barcelona-oneyear-hiatus</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:30 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The Week Ahead: June 28</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/d09e17d02ad8a00c99e013b5893d49ca0ef5b19a-3000x1964.jpg?rect=27,0,2946,1964&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Got any fun plans? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! The biggest economic event of the week is the release of the June jobs report, which will tell us more about the improving labor market and whether inflation will show up in the form of higher wages.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/27/week-ahead-june-28</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>calendar</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/27/week-ahead-june-28</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:29 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Intellia Therapeutics Announces Big Gene Editing Breakthrough in Early-Phase Trials</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-e27db47f451e67336e4860e85792a19e8eee394a-500x280-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. It stands for “clustered regularly interspaced short palindromic repeats,” and it’s one of those things humans found in nature and then copied. Bacteria use CRISPR to repel viruses, but humans have harnessed it to ctrl+c, ctrl+v DNA sequences, potentially leading to a revolution in treating disease.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/27/intellia-therapeutics-announces-big-gene-editing-breakthrough-earlyphase-trials</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>health</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/27/intellia-therapeutics-announces-big-gene-editing-breakthrough-earlyphase-trials</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:29 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Extra Unemployment Benefits Are Drying Up </title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/9f3dc7efb2702bc27c32076d7630c8ac404221e7-5568x3712.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. 25 out of the 26 states that axed the benefits early are led by GOP governors. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Perhaps by then we’ll have more data to understand how the extra $300/week has played a role in the labor market’s sluggish recovery. Other data paints a cloudier picture, though. four more states end enhanced benefits on July 10. Businesses are desperate to hire workers, and many states think scrapping the extra $300/week in unemployment benefits, which the Biden administration incorporated into its pandemic relief bill, will spur more job-seeking. In the states that cut off the extra payments the earliest, the number of workers who were paid benefits decreased 13.8% from mid-May to mid-June. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeTen more states including Florida, Ohio, and Texas ended extra unemployment benefits on Saturday. On Capitol Hill last week, Fed Chair Jerome Powell said that extra benefits could be playing a role in the worker shortage problem, but focused his attention on other challenges holding back the job market. Earlier this month, the job site Indeed found that job search activity fell below the national trend in states that cut off extra benefits in June. Industry groups and Republican lawmakers say that the extra payments disincentivize work and are the leading cause of the worker shortage.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/27/extra-unemployment-benefits-drying</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>work</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/27/extra-unemployment-benefits-drying</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:28 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Rescue Workers Continue to Search for Survivors of the Florida Condo Tower Collapse</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/6d69b3e77ebe2864a13604e915ea197ee4b150db-4900x3267.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Officials are now considering whether or not to temporarily evacuate the sister building, Champlain Towers North, which is located right next door and was built around the same time. It is not clear whether the pool deck was related to the collapse; another 2018 report from the same company gave the building mostly a clean bill of health. The latest:An engineering firm’s report from 2018 said that faulty waterproofing on the pool deck presented a “systemic issue for this building structure.” css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe desperate search for survivors continued over the weekend following the partial collapse of the Champlain Towers South condo building in Surfside, FL.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/27/rescue-workers-continue-search-survivors-florida-condo-tower-collapse</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>real estate</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/27/rescue-workers-continue-search-survivors-florida-condo-tower-collapse</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:27 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Make it Work: First Job out of College</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/7b6de1bb891bb0dd9e289abb0a591582a5da30e6-1503x603.png?rect=299,0,905,603&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Oh, and one more thing: Find a mentor and never let them go. I just graduated from college and am about to start my first-ever job. My advice to you and all recent college grads is to act like a sponge. You are going to learn many things for the first time, like navigating workplace culture, managing relationships, and figuring out whether you enjoy the work you're doing (studying things and actually doing them for your job is not the same thing! —KimoHow exciting! Ask Kate here. Something bothering you at work? Going through this process, however overwhelming, will teach you more about yourself and can help set you on a successful career path.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/27/make-work-first-job-college</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>work life</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/27/make-work-first-job-college</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:27 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Icebreakers with… Chef José Andrés</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/6fa12adad4c48c530231165390e8c0ffc221c0c4-2048x1536.jpg?rect=0,85,2048,1365&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. You only get to eat one condiment for the rest of your life. What's one of the best kitchen tricks you've learned? css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. Back home, do you see #ChefsforAmerica winding down as we move out of the pandemic, or continuing in some other form?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/27/icebreakers-chef-jos-andrs</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>q&amp;a</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/27/icebreakers-chef-jos-andrs</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:27 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: June 26</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/4df41ff4622a06f6df386e1bdf91bc3dca7a1455-3664x2061.jpg?rect=286,0,3092,2061&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Next up, he’s planning to launch a weekly variety show on HBO Max.Read: In honor of the Tour de France beginning today, check out the epic saga of Primož Roglič. (Bicycling) Why the exodus? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Experts cite antagonism during the protests following George Floyd’s death last summer, low pay, and overwork.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/25/key-performance-indicators-june-26</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/25/key-performance-indicators-june-26</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:23 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Money Matters: Is a Financial Advisor Worth It? </title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-56898bc2138c01031dc96409f2423cfa665bc625-500x374-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Is it worth getting a financial advisor, and if so, how do I choose one? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! For example, consider a one-time financial review. Financial advisors look at your financial situation, get a feel for your goals, and make and manage a personalized investing plan. I do believe that financial advisors offer tremendous value by helping people build sound investment portfolios and navigate complicated financial matters. You want a fiduciary, a credentialed financial advisor who’s legally bound to act in your best interest. It’s a fallacy that you need a milli to get a callback from a financial advisor. —Tony from ColoradoIt doesn’t bruise my ego to say you can’t rely solely on writers like me to chart your financial path.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/25/money-matters-financial-advisor-worth</link>
  <author>Ryan Lasker</author>
  <categories>money matters</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/25/money-matters-financial-advisor-worth</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:23 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Virgin Galactic Receives FAA Clearance to Take Passengers to Space</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/236697667c8d4163660fd07759668b7dad53e767-1200x812.jpg?rect=0,6,1200,800&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Billionaire Sir Richard Branson’s space travel company Virgin Galactic received FAA clearance yesterday to fly paying customers to space—great news for the 600 people on its waitlist eager to glimpse the curvature of Earth from 56 miles up.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/25/virgin-galactic-receives-faa-clearance-take-passengers-space</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>space</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/25/virgin-galactic-receives-faa-clearance-take-passengers-space</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:22 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>BuzzFeed's Got a SPAC That Values the Media Company at $1.5 Billion</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/2291a33da3e49982d7f08df04f4bb095f64a7158-1350x900.png?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. BuzzFeed hopes to scoop up more media companies and use that muscle to grab market share from the most powerful throuple in digital ads: Google, Facebook, and Amazon, which accounted for almost 90% of the US digital ad market in 2020, per ad agency GroupM. But by 2020, BuzzFeed was able to diversify its revenue streams (i.e., those addictive Tasty videos) and turned its first profit since 2014. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeYou'll finally be able to own a piece of the media company that owns a serious chunk of your screen time (we're reusing that line when we IPO). Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. With the Complex acquisition, BuzzFeed wants to grow revenue to $654 million next year and draw in an even younger, cooler, more intimidating audience. Now, BuzzFeed is in growth mode. The backstory: BuzzFeed was founded by CEO Jonah Peretti in 2006 and listicled its way to hundreds of millions in funding from the likes of NBCUniversal.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/24/buzzfeeds-got-spac-values-media-company-15-billion</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/24/buzzfeeds-got-spac-values-media-company-15-billion</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:22 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: June 25</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-8a854c81769a069a7e7d00a75d6bde3a2e9c91f2-480x270-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. (Rolling Stone) css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! He told the AP he expects the pet business to keep booming as people move into larger, suburban houses and workplaces become more pet-friendly.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/24/key-performance-indicators-june-25</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/24/key-performance-indicators-june-25</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:21 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Microsoft Hits $2T Market Cap, Shows off Major Windows Update</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/ec930229b154ee659f49c6a058a5874c52c0b2f9-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. And during debate on one pertaining to data portability, the committee specifically discussed whether the bill had been altered so Microsoft wouldn't fall under its purview. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Because of its focus on business software, the company has generally escaped the antitrust scrutiny that lawmakers have leveled on its more consumer-facing peers Facebook, Amazon, Apple, and Google in recent years... until now? An upgraded interfaceFeatures for multitasking and working across multiple screensA direct integration with its messaging/collaboration platform, TeamsNew gaming features, including an Xbox Game Pass integrationNot your grandma's operating systemWell, actually it is. Windows 11 is adding support for Android apps on its laptops and PCs for the first time and incentivizing developers to put their apps in the Microsoft Store by giving them 100% of revenues from app sales—a swipe at Apple's and Google's 30% fees. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeMicrosoft was incorporated 40 years ago today, but instead of installing a barn door in its master bathroom, the company closed above a $2 trillion market cap for the first time this week and unveiled its first major Windows update in years.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/24/microsoft-hits-2t-market-cap-shows-off-major-windows-update</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>tech</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/24/microsoft-hits-2t-market-cap-shows-off-major-windows-update</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:20 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Britney Spears Asks Judge to End Her Conservatorship in Public Testimony</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/223c6077ce1b49c5d445d8c5ab54b80f00d7b779-5472x3648.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIn her most public statement to date about her personal affairs, Britney Spears told an LA probate judge that she wants to end the conservatorship she's been under for 13 years." Released four albumsGrew her net worth to $60 millionHeld a four-year contract with Planet Hollywood that brought in ~$138 million and was the fourth highest-grossing Las Vegas residency, per Billboard. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/23/britney-spears-asks-judge-end-conservatorship-public-testimony</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/23/britney-spears-asks-judge-end-conservatorship-public-testimony</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:19 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Hong Kong’s Largest Pro-Democracy Paper Shuts Down</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/32e65af6f4fb08f1bcc6bad5094981bf313fcd68-4000x2667.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Free speech is getting more costly in Hong KongThe region has historically been a media hub because of its press freedoms, but the government’s crackdown on pro-democracy activism has spread to journalism. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeToday, Hong Kong’s largest pro-democracy tabloid, Apple Daily, printed its last issue. the former chair of the Hong Kong Journalists Association said, “Police did not rule out the possibility of more arrests, and the next [target] could be other media.” Radio Television Hong Kong (RTHK) was forced to swap its station head with a career politician with no journalism experience. Following difficulties obtaining necessary work permits, the New York Times moved part of its Hong Kong office to Seoul.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/23/hong-kongs-largest-prodemocracy-paper-shuts</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>international</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/23/hong-kongs-largest-prodemocracy-paper-shuts</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:19 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Resorts World Opens in Las Vegas</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/f9b5742c684df7954a3063c41184f2d47d2e72cf-1024x810.jpg?rect=0,63,1024,683&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/23/resorts-world-opens-las-vegas</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>hospitality</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/23/resorts-world-opens-las-vegas</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:18 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Supreme Court Hands Down Major Rulings on Farms, Free Speech, and Fannie and Freddie</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/e083011d075395526e2e4144e8886345ce8c3855-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Yesterday, the Supreme Court struck down a regulation that allowed union organizers to meet with agricultural workers during some periods of the day. The Supreme Court didn’t buy that, but did concede that the structure of the agency that oversees Fannie and Freddie is unconstitutional. Mortgage maniaShares in Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac, which back about half of the country’s $11 trillion in mortgages, tanked yesterday after the Supreme Court foreclosed on investors’ dreams of recouping some of their investments. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! The school banned Levy from cheer for a full year and her (clearly cool) dad got the ACLU involved, claiming that the school violated her First Amendment rights. What it means: President Biden gets to replace the agency’s head with someone of his choosing, and Fannie and Freddie will likely stay under the government’s watch for a while longer. Cheerleaders can cussWhen Brandi Levy, a Pennsylvania public high school student, didn’t make the varsity cheer team in 2017, she posted the uncensored version of, “f– school f– softball f– cheer f– everything” to Snapchat. Fast forward to 2021, and some argue union organizers could just slide into farmers’ DMs instead of meeting IRL.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/23/supreme-court-hands-major-rulings-farms-free-speech-fannie-freddie</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde,</author>
  <categories>legal</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/23/supreme-court-hands-major-rulings-farms-free-speech-fannie-freddie</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:17 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Tinder Rolls Out Biggest Update in Years</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/259fd55fdb3f2399961ba2334f7681f3e515fa37-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Gen Z accounts for over 50% of Tinder’s user base, and adding videos and opportunities to display an “authentic” self is intended to attract more young adults to the app. Some dating apps are taking a different approachBumble, an app known for requiring women to make the first move, is doubling down on its “Bumble BFF” feature to help nurture IRL friendships. Users coming out of Covid “just want to slow things down and get to know people first a lot more before they decide to match, let alone before they decide to go meet someone offline,” Lanzone told the BBC. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/22/tinder-rolls-biggest-update-years</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>dating</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/22/tinder-rolls-biggest-update-years</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:16 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>US Likely Won’t Hit Vaccination Goal by Fourth of July, Says White House</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/233164daf15109e4271cda850e9221552b27aecc-1000x667.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Bottom line: Health officials are painting a portrait of “two Americas,” one in regions with high immunization rates and the other where they lag. If the current pace of vaccinations continues, 67% of adults will have at least one shot of a Covid vaccine by the time the fireworks start, according to the NYT.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/22/us-likely-wont-hit-vaccination-goal-fourth-july-says-white-house</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>covid</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/22/us-likely-wont-hit-vaccination-goal-fourth-july-says-white-house</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:15 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Blackstone to Buy Rental Firm Home Partners of America for $6B</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/6a1d69f381bb5dae79a2b84a7800bdd45d01d644-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Now, the firm (and others) want back in on the soaring housing market, where last month median home prices rose almost 24% annually to break $350k. Blackstone bought tens of thousands of units and rented them out through Invitation Homes, now the US’ largest single-family home renter. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! After the 2008 crash, Wall Street firms like Blackstone scooped up foreclosed homes on the cheap. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeBlackstone is getting back into the rough-and-tumble business of arguing about where to hang the photos. Getting back into?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/22/blackstone-buy-rental-firm-home-partners-america-6b</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>real estate</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/22/blackstone-buy-rental-firm-home-partners-america-6b</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:15 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Supreme Court Ruling Over Athlete Compensation Deals Blow to NCAA</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/5b24eb8aeb47199ce0e842e9f79f8915e9bb47ad-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeCollege athletes scored another big W in their looooong quest to get paid for their work on the field. At least seven states have passed bills allowing college athletes to make money from their names, images, and likenesses that go into effect next week. “But the student athletes who generate the revenues, many of whom are African American and from lower-income backgrounds, end up with little or nothing.” “The bottom line is that the NCAA and its member colleges are suppressing the pay of student athletes who collectively generate billions of dollars in revenues for colleges every year.” For its part, the NCAA claims that compensating student athletes would undermine the “amateur” flavor of college sports, damaging fans' enjoyment of the product.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/21/supreme-court-ruling-athlete-compensation-deals-blow-ncaa</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/21/supreme-court-ruling-athlete-compensation-deals-blow-ncaa</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:14 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Spielberg's Amblin Partners Agrees to Make Movies for Netflix</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://images.morningbrew.com/gif/2021-10-26/image-722e6d344d3e0740d499ff810d5df4ce456db636-500x275-gif/giphy.webp'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/21/spielbergs-amblin-partners-agrees-make-movies-netflix</link>
  <author>Jamie Wilde</author>
  <categories>entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/21/spielbergs-amblin-partners-agrees-make-movies-netflix</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:13 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>WeWork Posts Best 2-Month Sales Streak Since 2019</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/e8ae10a464b6816de85487f80c97cc6a42a40a35-1120x630.jpg?rect=88,0,945,630&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! More offices are looking for hybrid or remote-friendly setups, and WeWork is once again poised to scratch the labor market's newest itch.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/21/wework-posts-best-2month-sales-streak-since-2019</link>
  <author>Alex Hickey</author>
  <categories>work</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/21/wework-posts-best-2month-sales-streak-since-2019</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:12 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Key Performance Indicators: June 21</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/2390f62155537d633be85db78e7dabb296676363-5004x3384.jpg?rect=0,24,5004,3336&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. And one of them, the Soberana 2 vaccine, has shown 62% efficacy with just two of its three doses in late-phase trials. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. (Washington Post) The NASA astronaut and a colleague faced a number of unexpected challenges (like a loose helmet) while installing new solar panels on the International Space Station, but they finally got the job done in a spacewalk yesterday.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/20/key-performance-indicators-june-21</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>grab bag</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/20/key-performance-indicators-june-21</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:11 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>China Ramps up Crackdown on Bitcoin Mining</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/52c8e7697b495b0de2b446909b4e27b8cc175c81-4500x3000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Why it matters: The restrictions mean bitcoin mining could shift out of China, which handled 75% of the world’s mining capacity before the increased scrutiny, and arrive in... Taken together with similar moves in other mining hubs, more than 90% of China’s bitcoin mining capacity is now at least temporarily offline, according to the state-run Global Times. America? Why crack down? css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/20/china-ramps-crackdown-bitcoin-mining</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>crypto</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/20/china-ramps-crackdown-bitcoin-mining</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:11 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Amazon Prime Day Returns to the Summer</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/4c84a498b6b0a144e797ecf4bed30c395b1d5111-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Today and tomorrow, Amazon will offer more than 2 million deals to its Prime members to juice e-commerce sales during what is typically a lull in the shopping calendar. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. He’ll step down on July 5 to make way for AWS head Andy Jassy. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! this Prime Day is Jeff Bezos’s last as CEO. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIt’s Amazon Prime Day, a holiday you can’t attack for being co-opted by consumerism because that is precisely the point.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/20/amazon-prime-day-returns-summer</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>e-commerce</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2021/06/20/amazon-prime-day-returns-summer</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:54:10 -0800</pubDate>
 </item>

</channel>
</rss>
