<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <atom:link href="https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2023/05/03/users/1/web_requests/22/MorningBrew.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
 <atom:icon>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2023/05/03/favicon.ico</atom:icon>
 

 <title>MorningBrew as a feed</title>
 <description>This is a feed of recent MorningBrew articles published by Huginn</description>
 <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/2023/05/03</link>
 <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:31:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
 <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:31:43 -0700</pubDate>
 <ttl>60</ttl>
 <item>
  <title>VC funding dropped to $18 billion last month</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/0afa316413a9f44eb6be1f3583bc9b6b0723684f-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. One sector that’s on the up-and-up: AI, partly due to increased investor interest in generative AI tools like ChatGPT and Bard. Companies in the AI space are raising at high valuations, Teare said, but despite the spike, the sector wasn’t enough to buoy the rest of the tech industry’s numbers. The technologies that will shape the future of business, all in one newsletter. “Every single funding stage is down from the peaks of 2021, but I think seed funding has stayed the most robust—it’s the least impacted by what’s happening—and then…Series A is stronger than Series B,” Teare said, adding, “It’ll be interesting to see how that market—the newer companies being formed…what those valuations and what those round sizes look like into 2023.” Looking aheadAcross the board, investors seem to be choosier about their investments, and since the “heat has gone away from the market…it’s just a much more selective funding environment overall,” Teare said. Top-up roundsBut Teare said her team has seen more companies raise extension rounds—especially if they need extra money to carry them through to their next big milestone or larger-scale funding round, in a presumably less challenging funding environment. “What we’ve seen now is that, broadly, for the tech industry, that companies are not able to raise…that next big master round, and so they’re raising extensions…funding to sort of tide over that company for the next 12 to 18 months, to get them through to a funding environment which is a little bit stronger.” “Typically, you raise rounds every 18 to 24 months, and we were seeing companies raise more often…some more at 12 to 18 months…largely because they could in this funding environment,” Teare said.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/60S?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Hayden Field</author>
  <categories>Venture capital</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/60S?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:29:44 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>WGA strike means we’re about to see some weird stuff on TV</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fstorage.morningbrew.com%2Fgif%2F2023-05-02%2Fimage-5d6f997925e16c254330d56cf178adcd42a71eb1-412x275-gif%2Fconan-coin-zoom-0423.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=70'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. What does TV look like without its writers? —CC While the boom in reality TV was underway before the previous strike, the lack of competition from scripted series helped juice the genre’s ratings: Over 31 million people tuned in to watch their crush David Archuleta lose to David Cook in the American Idol finale in 2008. css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none!</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/60C?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Cassandra Cassidy</author>
  <categories>TV</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/60C?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:29:43 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>AI fears cut Chegg in half</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/34106c75b37e888b0a188b4d24b0b6664d0c5399-720x480.png?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Zoom out: Chegg’s warning about ChatGPT stands in stark contrast to the companies mentioning AI to excite investors: On their earnings calls last week, Meta, Alphabet, Microsoft, and Amazon collectively dropped “AI” 168 times, according to Insider. It’s the first instance of a company warning that ChatGPT was eating into its business that we know of. Chegg has partnered with ChatGPT-creator OpenAI to develop its own conversational AI tool Cheggmate, which it’ll start testing this month. The AI anxiety spread to other education companies: Shares in publisher Pearson and language-learning app Duolingo dropped about 15% and 10%, respectively. —SK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Meanwhile, Duolingo released a subscription tier that lets users practice their language skills with an AI bot and has an AI-powered tool to explain mistakes. So, how to combat ChatGPT disrupting your business?</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/60T?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Sam Klebanov</author>
  <categories>Business News</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/60T?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:29:42 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Pornhub shuts down site in Utah ahead of new age verification law</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/c5eff3fca53271242e15137018ec5ab979cfcb40-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeGoogle searches for “VPN” have skyrocketed in Utah this week for one reason: You can no longer visit Pornhub from a Utah IP address. Louisiana implemented a similar law in January, but unlike Utah, it has a digital ID program that residents can use to verify their age and access adult sites. If you fire up Incognito Mode and head to Pornhub with an IP address in the state of Utah, you’ll be diverted to a page that has an adult performer (SFW) reading a statement from the site that claims “giving your ID card every time you want to visit an adult platform is not the most effective solution for protecting our users.” Counterpoint: Social media companies warn that restricting access to their sites would limit free speech and push younger users to less safe, more-fringe corners of the internet—an argument echoed by Pornhub in its opposition to the Utah bill. —MM To protest a new age restriction law that goes into effect today, MindGeek’s adult sites, including Pornhub, blocked access to its content in Utah.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/60r?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Government</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/60r?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:29:41 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Choupette and owner Karl Lagerfeld honored at Met Gala</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/1d14abaef1bad79950650c0bdad1909c4b80ff0b-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. “Everything that Karl represented is something that we all generally are very against,” one of the account organizers told the Washington Post. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIf you couldn’t guess by the parade of sunglasses and feline homages, the theme of last night’s annual Met Gala fundraiser at the Metropolitan Museum of Art, “Karl Lagerfeld: A Line of Beauty,” commemorated the late fashion playmaker and father to the world’s fanciest cat, Choupette. —CC</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/05/01/met-gala-honors-karl-lagerfeld</link>
  <author>Cassandra Cassidy</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/05/01/met-gala-honors-karl-lagerfeld</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 08:26:30 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>What’s next for banks?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fstorage.morningbrew.com%2Fgif%2F2023-05-01%2Fimage-4221df880ed9711bcbbe1fde94e5ffb22a71df67-480x360-gif%2Fslack-imgs.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=70'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. For now…no one knows if the credits are truly rolling on the banking crisis, but investors seemed to take Dimon’s assurances to heart: Stocks didn’t tank yesterday like they did after the bank failures in March. Purchasing beleaguered banks has been part of its growth strategy for some time, but the bank has experienced buyer’s remorse in the past: JPMorgan had to deal with legal issues and extra expenses when it took over Bear Stearns during the 2008 financial crisis. “This part of the crisis is over,” Dimon said, reasoning that after the three recent bank collapses, there just aren’t many more financial institutions with a large share of uninsured deposits to make them vulnerable to panics. JPMorgan took over First Republic (and its affluent client list), in return for $10.6 billion paid to regulators and other financial concessions. —SK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! The aerobic advice came after the banking heavyweight got even bulkier by gobbling up most of the assets of failed First Republic Bank. Are more banking crises coming? But Dimon thinks this time is different, as First Republic had a simpler business model.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/05/01/what-s-next-for-banks</link>
  <author>Sam Klebanov</author>
  <categories>Business News</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/05/01/what-s-next-for-banks</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 08:26:29 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The ‘Godfather of AI’ fears his own creation</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/e6311ac74b5132961c6addb3e350c9c723253240-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. He did so, he said, to be able to speak freely about the dangers of AI without worrying about impacting the company. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe chorus of tech leaders calling for a moratorium on AI development just gained one of the most commanding voices in the sector: Geoffrey Hinton, a trailblazing creator of the deep-learning techniques that underpin ChatGPT and other rapidly evolving AI systems.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/05/01/the-godfather-of-ai-fears-his-own-creation</link>
  <author>Molly Liebergall</author>
  <categories>AI</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/05/01/the-godfather-of-ai-fears-his-own-creation</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 08:26:28 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Choupette and owner Karl Lagerfeld honored at Met Gala</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/1d14abaef1bad79950650c0bdad1909c4b80ff0b-1024x683.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. “Everything that Karl represented is something that we all generally are very against,” one of the account organizers told the Washington Post. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIf you couldn’t guess by the by the parade of sunglasses and feline homages, the theme of last night’s annual Met Gala fundraiser at the Metropolitan Museum of Art, “Karl Lagerfeld: A Line of Beauty,” commemorated the late fashion playmaker and father to the world’s fanciest cat, Choupette. —CC</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5YY?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Cassandra Cassidy</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5YY?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:01:28 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The ‘Godfather of AI’ fears his own creation</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/e6311ac74b5132961c6addb3e350c9c723253240-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. He did so, he said, to be able to speak freely about the dangers of AI without worrying about impacting the company. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe chorus of tech leaders calling for a moratorium on AI development just gained one of the most commanding voices in the sector: Geoffrey Hinton, a trailblazing creator of the deep-learning techniques that underpin ChatGPT and other rapidly evolving AI systems.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5YT?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Molly Liebergall</author>
  <categories>AI</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5YT?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:01:22 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>What’s next for banks?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fstorage.morningbrew.com%2Fgif%2F2023-05-01%2Fimage-4221df880ed9711bcbbe1fde94e5ffb22a71df67-480x360-gif%2Fslack-imgs.webp&amp;w=3840&amp;q=70'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. For now…no one knows if the credits are truly rolling on the banking crisis, but investors seemed to take Dimon’s assurances to heart: Stocks didn’t tank yesterday like they did after the bank failures in March. Purchasing beleaguered banks has been part of its growth strategy for some time, but the bank has experienced buyer’s remorse in the past: JPMorgan had to deal with legal issues and extra expenses when it took over Bear Stearns during the 2008 financial crisis. “This part of the crisis is over,” Dimon said, reasoning that after the three recent bank collapses, there just aren’t many more financial institutions with a large share of uninsured deposits to make them vulnerable to panics. JPMorgan took over First Republic (and its affluent client list), in return for $10.6 billion paid to regulators and other financial concessions. —SK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! The aerobic advice came after the banking heavyweight got even bulkier by gobbling up most of the assets of failed First Republic Bank. Are more banking crises coming? But Dimon thinks this time is different, as First Republic had a simpler business model.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5YL?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Sam Klebanov</author>
  <categories>Business News</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5YL?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:01:22 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Hollywood braces for writers’ strike</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/cfa97524e6b96e4a323fa73cb2a35d6444b06966-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Studios have been stockpiling scripts ahead of the May 1 deadline, so scripted TV shows would continue for awhile. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIf production companies and unionized writers don’t reach a new contract by midnight tonight, the scribes will put down their No. 2 pencils and strike for the first time in 15 years. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Last month, 97.85% of eligible members of the Writers Guild of America, which represents most of the working writers in Hollywood, voted to authorize a strike if an agreement with major studios wasn’t reached. Here’s why…Shorter series: In the previous TV era, shows like How I Met Your Mother reliably churned out seasons with 20+ episodes. What happens if they strike?</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/30/hollywood-braces-for-writers-strike</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/30/hollywood-braces-for-writers-strike</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 06:21:21 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>No Shave November in May…but for lawns</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/3251c8eafba3c600ff139f8e728979783f6b2fc1-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. In past years, participants have watched their lawns transform from an “ecological dead zone”—as one professor calls the average American yard—into a tall-grassed ecosystem rife with bumblebees, songbirds, chipmunks, and other forest friends... But some environmentalists say No Mow May isn’t the right way to bring biodiversity back to residential areas because it “teases” insects and other pollinators. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeTo mow or not to mow? —ML That is the question homeowners are debating as more cities and towns embrace No Mow May, a movement started in 2019 to revitalize backyard wildlife by refraining from lawn care for an entire month. The Guelph Turfgrass Institute suggests channeling the benefits of No Mow May throughout the other 11 months by sectioning off a part of the yard as a permanent “wildflower zone.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/28/no-shave-november-in-may-but-for-lawns</link>
  <author>Molly Liebergall</author>
  <categories>Environment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/28/no-shave-november-in-may-but-for-lawns</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 06:21:19 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Why your super online friends are talking about Bluesky</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/143568222ba4befdaaa2bc7001d801dbed541d3a-1024x702.jpg?rect=0,9,1024,683&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. On a decentralized platform, one person does not have the power to create rules that govern the entire ecosystem. One of the most recently disillusioned people with Musk is none other than Dorsey. Bluesky is very similar to Twitter, which makes sense since it was originally a side project of Twitter’s and is funded by former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIf you aren’t on the internet as much as I am (which…congrats, that’s healthier), then you might not have heard of Bluesky, a social media app that’s gaining traction as an alternative to Twitter. Writing on Bluesky, Dorsey said “it all went south” once Musk bought Twitter.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/30/why-your-online-friends-are-talking-about-bluesky</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Social Media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/30/why-your-online-friends-are-talking-about-bluesky</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 06:21:19 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The big get bigger: JPMorgan to acquire First Republic</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/e7d227377e43a4302f92c7fc142c494394f263ff-5669x3779.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeAnother one bites the dust: Authorities seized First Republic Bank this morning and sold most of its assets to JPMorgan, the country’s largest bank. First Republic tried to weather the storm itself, but after customers withdrew more than $100 billion in deposits in Q1 and its share price plunged nearly 75% last week alone, the government had to hang the “closed” sign on the door. But by quickly finding a buyer over the weekend, the government avoided the unsavory tactic it had to deploy for SVB: protecting deposits over the federally insured cap of $250,000. JPMorgan said it will assume First Republic’s $92 billion in deposits, which is a welcome outcome since making SVB depositors whole cost the FDIC’s Deposit Insurance Fund about $20 billion. First Citizens collected the scraps of SVB, New York Community Bank snatched up assets of Signature Bank, and UBS absorbed crosstown rival Credit Suisse. Like SVB, First Republic is a midsized California-based lender with a specific client base—in this case, wealthy individuals—that made it particularly exposed to the shockwaves of the recent banking turmoil.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/05/01/the-big-get-better-jpmorgan-to-acquire-first-republic</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Finance</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/05/01/the-big-get-better-jpmorgan-to-acquire-first-republic</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 06:21:18 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>The big get bigger: JPMorgan to acquire First Republic</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/e7d227377e43a4302f92c7fc142c494394f263ff-5669x3779.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeAnother one bites the dust: Authorities seized First Republic Bank this morning and sold most of its assets to JPMorgan, the country’s largest bank. First Republic tried to weather the storm itself, but after customers withdrew more than $100 billion in deposits in Q1 and its share price plunged nearly 75% last week alone, the government had to hang the “closed” sign on the door. But by quickly finding a buyer over the weekend, the government avoided the unsavory tactic it had to deploy for SVB: protecting deposits over the federally insured cap of $250,000. JPMorgan said it will assume First Republic’s $92 billion in deposits, which is a welcome outcome since making SVB depositors whole cost the FDIC’s Deposit Insurance Fund about $20 billion. First Citizens collected the scraps of SVB, New York Community Bank snatched up assets of Signature Bank, and UBS absorbed crosstown rival Credit Suisse. Like SVB, First Republic is a midsized California-based lender with a specific client base—in this case, wealthy individuals—that made it particularly exposed to the shockwaves of the recent banking turmoil.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5VA?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Finance</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5VA?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 03:01:23 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Why your super online friends are talking about Bluesky</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/143568222ba4befdaaa2bc7001d801dbed541d3a-1024x702.jpg?rect=0,9,1024,683&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. On a decentralized platform, one person does not have the power to create rules that govern the entire ecosystem. One of the most recently disillusioned people with Musk is none other than Dorsey. Bluesky is very similar to Twitter, which makes sense since it was originally a side project of Twitter’s and is funded by former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIf you aren’t on the internet as much as I am (which…congrats, that’s healthier), then you might not have heard of Bluesky, a social media app that’s gaining traction as an alternative to Twitter. Writing on Bluesky, Dorsey said “it all went south” once Musk bought Twitter.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5Vf?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Social Media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5Vf?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:01:19 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Hollywood braces for writers’ strike</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/cfa97524e6b96e4a323fa73cb2a35d6444b06966-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Studios have been stockpiling scripts ahead of the May 1 deadline, so scripted TV shows would continue for awhile. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeIf production companies and unionized writers don’t reach a new contract by midnight tonight, the scribes will put down their No. 2 pencils and strike for the first time in 15 years. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Last month, 97.85% of eligible members of the Writers Guild of America, which represents most of the working writers in Hollywood, voted to authorize a strike if an agreement with major studios wasn’t reached. Here’s why…Shorter series: In the previous TV era, shows like How I Met Your Mother reliably churned out seasons with 20+ episodes. What happens if they strike?</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5V5?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Neal Freyman</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5V5?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:01:19 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>How chess became the hot new esport</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/0db2ffd43464d10f9ab35c9d00530d59e794d93f-6048x4024.jpg?rect=6,0,6036,4024&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeUnlike in the chess heydays of the last century, one need not be a Bobby Fischer-level genius to achieve chess stardom now. The sport was likely helped along last year by a perfect hype storm created by Magnus Carlsen, the world’s No. 1 chess player, accusing an opponent of cheating in an in-person game, as well as a Louis Vuitton campaign in which Messi and Ronaldo faced off across a chess board. One of the most popular chess YouTubers, Levy Rozman, is a pro, but he lacks the grandmaster designation of top-tier players. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. The company hopes that the Champions Chess Tour will become the flagship event “for all of chess” in the future, a spokesperson for Chess.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5So?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Sam Klebanov</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5So?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:01:40 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Brew Classifieds: Week of April 23</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/3e37b6a7a51f7ff299b63367b250872326ac26d9-1500x375.png?rect=469,0,563,375&amp;w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5S9?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Business News</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5S9?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:01:30 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>No Shave November in May…but for lawns</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/3251c8eafba3c600ff139f8e728979783f6b2fc1-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. In past years, participants have watched their lawns transform from an “ecological dead zone”—as one professor calls the average American yard—into a tall-grassed ecosystem rife with bumblebees, songbirds, chipmunks, and other forest friends... But some environmentalists say No Mow May isn’t the right way to bring biodiversity back to residential areas because it “teases” insects and other pollinators. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeTo mow or not to mow? —ML That is the question homeowners are debating as more cities and towns embrace No Mow May, a movement started in 2019 to revitalize backyard wildlife by refraining from lawn care for an entire month. The Guelph Turfgrass Institute suggests channeling the benefits of No Mow May throughout the other 11 months by sectioning off a part of the yard as a permanent “wildflower zone.”</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5Uv?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Molly Liebergall</author>
  <categories>Environment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5Uv?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:01:30 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Bed Bath &amp; Beyond store closures will make room for booming discount retailers</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/a1ae5b8631a509d15630a73283d93178960b0aa4-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5Uq?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Retail</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5Uq?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:01:30 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Pour one out for First Republic</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/bca410e55bc347bbf0b8c9df2c449861ba4067e9-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. First Republic got hit extra hard by the crisis because it had successfully pursued wealthy clients in order to grow. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeFirst Republic Bank might be breathing its last breaths. The bank panic that led to the collapse of Silicon Valley Bank and Signature Bank left First Republic’s depositors worried about whether it could stay afloat. Looking ahead…if the bank fails, regulators will have some busy days ahead of them deciding whether to make First Republic depositors whole and assuring the public that the banking sector isn’t in trouble. Things calmed down after heavy hitters, including JPMorgan and Bank of America, deposited $30 billion in the bank last month. Its once enviable client list became a liability since two-thirds of accounts at the bank had balances above $250k—so most depositors knew they wouldn’t be made whole by the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation if First Republic ran into trouble.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5US?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Sam Klebanov</author>
  <categories>Business News</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5US?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>One of Judy Blume’s most frequently banned books heads to the screen</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/10ae61f73569d2557f0d71e85e0ed588c39e0128-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Due to its frank discussion of menstruation and puberty, the book (and Blume’s other works) became a substitute of sorts for the sex ed many tweens never had in their classrooms. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Most recently…Blume’s book Forever was included on a list of 80 books from celebrated authors like Toni Morrison and James Patterson banned last month by a Florida school district. —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! That’s also why the novel received pushbackAre You There God and some of Blume’s other 32 titles were challenged during the first significant wave of banning books from schools in the ’80s.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/judy-blume-banned-books-heads-to-screen</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/judy-blume-banned-books-heads-to-screen</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 08:21:30 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Jerry Springer, ‘ringmaster of civilization’s end,’ dies at 79</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/09db027e23b5ae715940e39b430b2437e58947c4-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Springer was a busy guyWhen he wasn’t breaking up fights on daytime TV, Springer also:Started as a politician. The Jerry Springer Show, which ran from 1991 to 2018, peaked in popularity in 1998, drawing 12 million viewers and surpassing Oprah’s talk show in the ratings. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. But Springer defended his approach.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/27/jerry-springer-ringmaster-of-civilization-s-end-dies-at-79</link>
  <author>Cassandra Cassidy</author>
  <categories>TV</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/27/jerry-springer-ringmaster-of-civilization-s-end-dies-at-79</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 08:21:30 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>A new challenger emerges in the weight-loss drug race</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/763cc0dc0eb28a329f7f3800fd72930543ab0ace-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The timeline: Eli Lilly expects the FDA to approve Mounjaro for weight loss soon—perhaps by the end of the year. Once greenlighted for weight loss, Mounjaro is projected to become one of the highest-grossing drugs of all time with $50 billion in annual sales, driving the weight-loss/diabetes medication industry to what some estimate could be $150 billion per year. The results reinforced previous findings that Mounjaro (generic name tirzepatide) can help diabetic and nondiabetic patients lose more weight than people did in past studies of Wegovy. —ML css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! And judging by how quickly Wegovy went to backorder after being officially approved for non-diabetes purposes, Mounjaro will likely also face a frenzy of weight-loss prescriptions that causes more shortages.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/27/new-challenger-in-weight-loss-drug-race</link>
  <author>Molly Liebergall</author>
  <categories>Health</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/27/new-challenger-in-weight-loss-drug-race</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 08:21:28 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>One of Judy Blume’s most frequently banned books heads to the screen</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/10ae61f73569d2557f0d71e85e0ed588c39e0128-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Due to its frank discussion of menstruation and puberty, the book (and Blume’s other works) became a substitute of sorts for the sex ed many tweens never had in their classrooms. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Most recently…Blume’s book Forever was included on a list of 80 books from celebrated authors like Toni Morrison and James Patterson banned last month by a Florida school district. —MM css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! That’s also why the novel received pushbackAre You There God and some of Blume’s other 32 titles were challenged during the first significant wave of banning books from schools in the ’80s.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5Pe?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5Pe?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:01:31 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>A new challenger emerges in the weight-loss drug race</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/763cc0dc0eb28a329f7f3800fd72930543ab0ace-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. The timeline: Eli Lilly expects the FDA to approve Mounjaro for weight loss soon—perhaps by the end of the year. Once greenlighted for weight loss, Mounjaro is projected to become one of the highest-grossing drugs of all time with $50 billion in annual sales, driving the weight-loss/diabetes medication industry to what some estimate could be $150 billion per year. The results reinforced previous findings that Mounjaro (generic name tirzepatide) can help diabetic and nondiabetic patients lose more weight than people did in past studies of Wegovy. —ML css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! And judging by how quickly Wegovy went to backorder after being officially approved for non-diabetes purposes, Mounjaro will likely also face a frenzy of weight-loss prescriptions that causes more shortages.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5P9?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Molly Liebergall</author>
  <categories>Health</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5P9?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:01:30 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Jerry Springer, ‘ringmaster of civilization’s end,’ dies at 79</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/09db027e23b5ae715940e39b430b2437e58947c4-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Springer was a busy guyWhen he wasn’t breaking up fights on daytime TV, Springer also:Started as a politician. The Jerry Springer Show, which ran from 1991 to 2018, peaked in popularity in 1998, drawing 12 million viewers and surpassing Oprah’s talk show in the ratings. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. But Springer defended his approach.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5OX?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Cassandra Cassidy</author>
  <categories>TV</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5OX?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>AI-generated Republican attack ad has some experts worried about AI’s role in 2024 election</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/e15886ef918770a10db75e937352578b3680b94e-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. While political campaigns have used AI tools to help canvass voters for years, recent breakthroughs in generative AI (like ChatGPT, Midjourney, and other programs) have taken the tech to a whole new level of realism. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/ai-generated-republican-attack-ad-2024-election</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>AI</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/ai-generated-republican-attack-ad-2024-election</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 08:01:32 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Janet Jackson gets hip-checked by the Hawks</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/9e40ffd2dd54a3740e340bb862f9cf2eba3d8d42-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. One night, two queens of pop: Janet Jackson’s rescheduled concert will take place at the same time as the first of Taylor Swift’s three Eras Tour shows in Atlanta at Mercedes-Benz Stadium. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeNo one was counting on the Atlanta Hawks getting booted from the playoffs more than the folks who run the team’s stadium—and maybe Janet Jackson. —ML</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/26/janet-jackson-gets-hip-checked-by-the-hawks</link>
  <author>Molly Liebergall</author>
  <categories>Sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/26/janet-jackson-gets-hip-checked-by-the-hawks</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 08:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Ed Sheeran’s copyright infringement trial starts</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/48a87831c2182bd2a4d3250911e45b8435e1ccb0-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. The case dates back to 2017, when the family of Ed Townsend—Gaye’s co-writer on “Let’s Get It On”—sued Sheeran for $100 million, alleging that he copy-and-pasted a four-chord progression from the song for his Grammy-winning bop “Thinking Out Loud.” Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. On the one hand…the chord progression does sound almost identical. He won one case and settled another out of court. His defense team claims that there are over a dozen songs that use the same chord progression, including some that predate “Let’s Get It On.”Big picture: Copyright infringement claims have been popping up more frequently in the music industry in recent years. And the plaintiff’s lawyer said a video of Sheeran singing a mashup of the two songs at a concert is the star’s “confession.” —MM</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/ed-sheeran-s-copyright-infringement-trial-starts</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/ed-sheeran-s-copyright-infringement-trial-starts</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 08:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Disney takes DeSantis feud to the next level</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/4f22e27a231aeca65a54d7acf388676a95b6bb81-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe battle between Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis and one of the state’s largest employers is getting hotter than the final plate in the Hot Ones Challenge. Disney filed its suit almost immediately after the board hand-picked by DeSantis to govern the district voted to nullify land use agreements made by the previous Disney-controlled board. Back before Disney’s CEO called out the governor in front of investors and DeSantis threatened to build a prison next to Disney World, Disney benefited from Florida’s business-friendly climate. Disney and DeSantis have been dueling like Peter Pan and Captain Hook ever since the company criticized the so-called “Don’t Say Gay” law last spring, and yesterday Disney sued DeSantis, claiming he orchestrated a campaign of retaliation against the company for exercising its free speech rights. The feud hinges on control of the special district where Disney World sits. —CC The suit notes that its existing contracts with the state of Florida would invest $17 billion in Disney World and create 13,000 jobs over the next decade. From a spoonful of sugar to a 74-page lawsuitDisney’s suit accuses DeSantis of a “relentless campaign to weaponize government power against Disney in retaliation for expressing a political viewpoint.”</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/26/disney-takes-desantis-feud-to-the-next-level</link>
  <author>Cassandra Cassidy</author>
  <categories>Business News</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/26/disney-takes-desantis-feud-to-the-next-level</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 08:01:28 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Why are rent prices still so high?</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/1494930b05846b2adc1919ee52a5916f76df6e06-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Rent growth is 17% higher than 2021 levels, despite beginning to moderate in September, according to Rent. In other words: Rental prices could be cooling off, but the official CPI data doesn’t reflect this. Rep. Ro Khanna, a Democrat from California, introduced a federal bill last October that would strip large investors from snatching up single-family homes for tax incentives. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. If that trend continues, then rent prices might fall in line with real-time inflationary measures. But if BlackRock isn’t totally responsible for stubbornly high rent prices, and neither are Airbnb hosts who drill through tasteful architectural details to hang driftwood signs that read “I’M ON LAKE TIME”... ), one other theory has gained steam in the last few years: Investment firms are scooping up homes and constricting supply. But in 2010, as credit and mortgage markets tightened following the pop of the 2008 housing bubble, more than 75% of growth in the market came from renters with incomes of $75,000 or more, according to the Joint Center for Housing Studies of Harvard University. For example, month over month rent growth was 0.5% in March, an improvement from the approximately 0.8% monthly increase we saw in late 2022. Since the pandemic began, housing prices have soared. In the March consumer price index report, rents jumped almost 9% from last year, far outpacing the overall inflation rate of 5%. Some point to spiking mortgage rates driving would-be homeowners into the rental market; others to investment firms scooping up units and limiting the available supply. When asked why renters can’t find a studio under two grand, housing experts and economists often point to one thing: not enough supply.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5LZ?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Lillian Stone</author>
  <categories>Real estate</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5LZ?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:01:33 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Janet Jackson gets hip-checked by the Hawks</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/9e40ffd2dd54a3740e340bb862f9cf2eba3d8d42-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. One night, two queens of pop: Janet Jackson’s rescheduled concert will take place at the same time as the first of Taylor Swift’s three Eras Tour shows in Atlanta at Mercedes-Benz Stadium. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeNo one was counting on the Atlanta Hawks getting booted from the playoffs more than the folks who run the team’s stadium—and maybe Janet Jackson. —ML</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5LM?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Molly Liebergall</author>
  <categories>Sports</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5LM?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:01:24 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Ed Sheeran’s copyright infringement trial starts</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/48a87831c2182bd2a4d3250911e45b8435e1ccb0-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. The case dates back to 2017, when the family of Ed Townsend—Gaye’s co-writer on “Let’s Get It On”—sued Sheeran for $100 million, alleging that he copy-and-pasted a four-chord progression from the song for his Grammy-winning bop “Thinking Out Loud.” Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. On the one hand…the chord progression does sound almost identical. He won one case and settled another out of court. His defense team claims that there are over a dozen songs that use the same chord progression, including some that predate “Let’s Get It On.”Big picture: Copyright infringement claims have been popping up more frequently in the music industry in recent years. And the plaintiff’s lawyer said a video of Sheeran singing a mashup of the two songs at a concert is the star’s “confession.” —MM</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5LH?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Matty Merritt</author>
  <categories>Entertainment</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5LH?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:01:23 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Disney takes DeSantis feud to the next level</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/4f22e27a231aeca65a54d7acf388676a95b6bb81-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. css-y2oq5g[data-hover][data-disabled]{background:var(--colors-primary);opacity:0.5;}SubscribeThe battle between Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis and one of the state’s largest employers is getting hotter than the final plate in the Hot Ones Challenge. Disney filed its suit almost immediately after the board hand-picked by DeSantis to govern the district voted to nullify land use agreements made by the previous Disney-controlled board. Back before Disney’s CEO called out the governor in front of investors and DeSantis threatened to build a prison next to Disney World, Disney benefited from Florida’s business-friendly climate. Disney and DeSantis have been dueling like Peter Pan and Captain Hook ever since the company criticized the so-called “Don’t Say Gay” law last spring, and yesterday Disney sued DeSantis, claiming he orchestrated a campaign of retaliation against the company for exercising its free speech rights. The feud hinges on control of the special district where Disney World sits. —CC The suit notes that its existing contracts with the state of Florida would invest $17 billion in Disney World and create 13,000 jobs over the next decade. From a spoonful of sugar to a 74-page lawsuitDisney’s suit accuses DeSantis of a “relentless campaign to weaponize government power against Disney in retaliation for expressing a political viewpoint.”</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5Lz?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Cassandra Cassidy</author>
  <categories>Business News</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5Lz?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:01:23 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>A tale of 2 prime-time stars flaming out</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/0fe3cbc135b4473f2d992ed3190149e46bf449f2-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. It was one of the top shows on cable news, regularly drawing more than 3 million nightly viewers. css-y2oq5g{display:-webkit-inline-box;display:-webkit-inline-flex;display:-ms-inline-flexbox;display:inline-flex;-webkit-appearance:none;-moz-appearance:none;-ms-appearance:none;appearance:none;-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-box-pack:center;-ms-flex-pack:center;-webkit-justify-content:center;justify-content:center;-webkit-user-select:none;-moz-user-select:none;-ms-user-select:none;user-select:none;position:relative;white-space:nowrap;vertical-align:middle;outline:2px solid transparent;outline-offset:2px;width:auto;line-height:1.2;border-radius:var(--chakra-radii-md);font-weight:var(--chakra-fontWeights-semibold);transition-property:var(--chakra-transition-property-common);transition-duration:var(--chakra-transition-duration-normal);height:var(--chakra-sizes-10);min-width:var(--chakra-sizes-10);font-size:var(--chakra-fontSizes-md);-webkit-padding-start:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-start:var(--chakra-space-4);-webkit-padding-end:var(--chakra-space-4);padding-inline-end:var(--chakra-space-4);color:var(--chakra-colors-white);background:var(--colors-primary);radius:var(--border-radius);}. It’s not entirely surprising: Tucker Carlson Tonight was as synonymous with Fox as Law &amp; Order is with NBC. ’s market value dropped after news of his departure broke.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/24/a-tale-of-2-prime-time-stars-flaming-out</link>
  <author>Cassandra Cassidy</author>
  <categories>Media</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/24/a-tale-of-2-prime-time-stars-flaming-out</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 07:01:25 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Corporations charge more and make more</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/5d9da529eb58daf4beedc9e39b02444c1f617699-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. Consumer giants Kimberly-Clark, Nestlé, and P&amp;G raked in more revenue last quarter after they jacked up prices by about 10%. —SK css-1dlcpt7[data-readonly]{box-shadow:none! Higher sticker prices helped GM add almost $1,800 to its per-car profit in North America and grow its revenue. Looking ahead…execs at companies like Coca-Cola say it’s only a matter of time before they’ll have to stop increasing prices or risk losing customers. Chipotle increased prices and store traffic also increased, the company said. Pepsi’s CFO said its customers have already been opting for cheaper products, and the CEO of McDonald’s told the Financial Times that customers were starting to push back on the company’s beefier price tags.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/25/corporations-charge-more-and-make-more</link>
  <author>Sam Klebanov</author>
  <categories>Business News</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/25/corporations-charge-more-and-make-more</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 07:01:23 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Melatonin gummies give you more Zzzs than you asked for</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/6475c472a19ed54728cf75ec0dac86f714b41990-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. One product even had 347% of the stated amount of melatonin. The study, published in the Journal of the American Medical Association, found that 22 of the 25 melatonin products tested by researchers had inaccurate labels that most often lowballed the amount of melatonin they contained. —CC Meanwhile, in the EU, the UK, Canada, and elsewhere, melatonin requires a prescription. But for kids, higher levels of melatonin can cause health problems. Current US regulations do not require supplement-makers to conduct clinical trials or obtain FDA approval before putting their products on the shelf. Big picture: Industry reps and the FDA agree that the dietary supplement marketplace needs a regulatory overhaul. Pediatricians warn that since melatonin is a hormone, even normal consumption on a regular basis can affect a child’s development in puberty. A study released yesterday showed that the labels on sleepy-time gummies frequently misrepresent the amount of melatonin they contain.</description>
  <link>https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/25/melatonin-gummies-may-give-you-more-zzzs-thank-you-asked-for</link>
  <author>Cassandra Cassidy</author>
  <categories>Health</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.morningbrew.com/daily/stories/2023/04/25/melatonin-gummies-may-give-you-more-zzzs-thank-you-asked-for</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 07:01:23 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Melatonin gummies give you more Zzzs thank you asked for</title>
  <description>&lt;img src='https://cdn.sanity.io/images/bl383u0v/production/6475c472a19ed54728cf75ec0dac86f714b41990-1500x1000.jpg?w=900&amp;h=600&amp;q=80&amp;fit=max&amp;auto=format&amp;dpr=1'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;. Become smarter in just 5 minutesGet the daily email that makes reading the news actually enjoyable. One product even had 347% of the stated amount of melatonin. The study, published in the Journal of the American Medical Association, found that 22 of the 25 melatonin products tested by researchers had inaccurate labels that most often lowballed the amount of melatonin they contained. —CC Meanwhile, in the EU, the UK, Canada, and elsewhere, melatonin requires a prescription. But for kids, higher levels of melatonin can cause health problems. Current US regulations do not require supplement-makers to conduct clinical trials or obtain FDA approval before putting their products on the shelf. Big picture: Industry reps and the FDA agree that the dietary supplement marketplace needs a regulatory overhaul. Pediatricians warn that since melatonin is a hormone, even normal consumption on a regular basis can affect a child’s development in puberty. A study released yesterday showed that the labels on sleepy-time gummies frequently misrepresent the amount of melatonin they contain.</description>
  <link>https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5IF?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</link>
  <author>Cassandra Cassidy</author>
  <categories>Health</categories>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://links.morningbrew.com/c/5IF?mid={{md5(profile.email)}}&amp;cid={{message_id()}}</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 01:37:25 -0700</pubDate>
 </item>

</channel>
</rss>
